It is now the year 4386
on the Cultivation Calendar.
This is a great era
of scientific cultivation.
Don't miss the good deals!
-Class 1 anti-aging agents.
-We have all the spiritual amulets
-and magic wares
-It enhances your beauty.
Both competitors are playing offensively,
giving no chance to the other!
People all over Huaxiu
are practicing cultivation
and enjoying the convenience
brought by the cultivation technology.
As always,
it has been peaceful and prosperous
until…
Look. What's that?
-What is happening?
-What…
Run!
-Breaking news.
-Run!
A Level 5 Giant Frog
has descended in Songhai.
Magic Squad has been sent to the scene.
IMMORTAL
Attention.
Flying swords.
Shoot!
Right on target!
With this tactical bombardment,
even the demon king can't resist it.
Wait a minute.
The Giant Frog stands up again.
Spread out!
Little boy, run!
LITTLE RACCOON
Run!
Little boy, are you all right?
Go back home to your parents.
I'm going to find the monster.
The man who defeated
Giant Frog all on his own
is called Zhuo Yi.
He earned his name in this battle,
known by later generations
as the hero who saved Huaxiu.
Many cultivation factions
-have erected his statue.
-This year's freshmen aren't impressive.
Today
is the first day of the new school year
for Faction 60.
FRESHMEN ROLL OF FORCE VALUES
There is even someone
with a force value of five.
This is so bad.
Freshman,
you must be the Force Value Five
in the photo.
Don't worry, freshman.
The seniors will take good care of you.
Thank you.
It takes a lot of hardship
to take care of someone,
so you wouldn't let us do that
for nothing, would you?
That's right.
This is bullying!
Wait a second.
Look.
Just because your force value is high,
you are bullying a freshman
who has a lower force value.
That is not good.
Who is that?
SUPER
That girl looks familiar.
Isn't she the legendary daughter of
the Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group,
Sun Rong?
A freshman that can produce a golden beam.
Damn.
Get down here!
That looks so beautiful!
Seniors,
here I am.
What do you have to say?
-She's so pretty.
-Indeed.
Boys don't fight girls.
Don't let me see you again!
Whenever, wherever,
and whatever happens,
I,
Sun Rong,
will give you sufficient protection.
Thank you.
Thank you for your offer.
This…
-What was he thinking?
-What does he want?
-Indeed.
My goodness.
And as usual,
there will be a very important test today
to decide which class they will be in.
-I'm nervous.
-How do we show our spiritual force?
I must do my best.
Yes.
Level 1 freshmen, welcome.
SPIRITUAL FORCE TEST
It's Zhuo Yi!
It's Master Zhuo. He's so handsome!
Welcome to my alma mater.
-Newcomers to this school
-He studied here?
will have a mysterious test
on your spiritual force.
The result of the test
will decide which class you will go to.
Those with excellent scores
will be in Class Elite.
I hope you will do your best.
-Yes!
Whoever is called
will go in from here.
-That's feasible.
-That's easy.
So,
on behalf of
the Magic Committee of Huaxiu,
I wish you all
prosper with your magical power.
SONGHAI FACTION 60 CULTIVATION SCHOOL
SPIRITUAL FORCE TEST
KU XUAN
Student number one, Ku Xuan.
Please come in.
Yes.
-Could it be…
-Who is this guy?
He looks like the author of an animation.
-Indeed.
-I've seen him on a magazine cover.
It's so dark in here.
And there is water.
In this darkness,
how are we going to be tested?
HIT HERE
My goodness!
-Gosh!
-My goodness!
-That's frightening.
-That is…
Who would have thought
that the target would be
the demon king that intruded
on the human world ten years ago,
Giant Frog?
Don't you worry.
The real Giant Frog is sealed
under the campus.
This is just the incarnation
of its spiritual force.
All you need to do
is to summon up all your force
to hit the head of the Giant Frog.
That's all.
I remember that a high-level demon king
can clearly sense the force value
of its attacker.
I just need to hit its head hard,
then I'll be in Class Elite.
What an embarrassment.
HIT HERE
I was frightened by an incarnation.
I must destroy this damn frog.
After all,
I'm the original author of this animation.
-What?
Spiritual force of 404.
Class Ordinary.
GYM, LIVE
It seems
the water in the field
serves as a cushion
for those sprung-out students.
I think it is because
it's hard to draw a basketball court.
Even if it is sealed,
the demon king should have
a force value above five digits.
Attacking it with
a freshman's spiritual force
is like hitting a bowling ball
with a table tennis ball.
He's bound to bounce back.
Is this supposed to be a blow to freshmen?
Student number two, Li Hao.
Please come in.
Spiritual force of 75.
-Class Ordinary.
-Get out of here.
Get out of here.
What are you doing here?
This year's freshmen are so weak.
Last year, they had values
up to 700 to 800.
The rival is the demon king.
This is so exciting.
Chen Chao.
Force value of 938.
Class Elite.
Force value of 528.
Force value of 331.
Class Ordinary.
Force value of 201. Class Ordinary.
Guo Hao.
Force value of 886.
Class Elite.
HIT HERE
Stupid students.
Do you think I'm here to be beaten up?
I've been sealed up here for ten years.
Number 138.
Sun Rong.
Yes.
It's Sun Rong.
Every year,
I'm used as the target for the test.
I always absorb some spiritual force
from those young bastards
With the force value she has,
she can go to one of the best schools.
Why did she come to this school?
A little more
and I'll have enough force
to break the damned seal.
Wang Zukang.
Just wait and see.
-This student…
-A rich heiress.
-Who is she?
-I wish I can be with her.
My goodness.
I'm actually her schoolmate now.
It seems that this girl
has quite a high force value.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to hit you with my little fist.
Come and hit me.
HIT HERE
My goodness.
-Goddess!
-Sun…
-Sun Rong.
-Goddess!
-Force value
-of 2019.
-Goddess!
-Thank you.
-Thank you all.
-Goddess!
It's him.
-Is he Force Value Five?
-Wang…
-Who is he?
-Wang Ling.
He is so weak.
-Good.
-He is so weak.
I remember you now.
A value of 400 would be enough
for Class Ordinary.
HIT HERE
A little more and I'll break the seal.
Wait!
This background music…
Could it be…
No way.
How could it be him?
Give me your spiritual force.
Good.
A side dish has delivered itself.
I hate being bothered
while I'm eating crispy noodles.
Why?
I'm sure of it.
Back then,
I was defeated by this bastard
with his own background music.
Force value contained to the minimum.
Right,
I need to pretend to try hard.
No. I must do something.
If he hits me,
my soul and spirit will be gone!
The screen.
-What happened to it?
-What was that white light?
Is it out of order?
-I don't know.
-What is going on?
SONGHAI FACTION 60 CULTIVATION SCHOOL
SPIRITUAL FORCE TEST
What is…
Could it be real?
What's wrong with it?
I didn't hit it at all.
Froggy!
Froggy. Are you all right?
The Giant Frog was killed by that guy.
Didn't you notice?
Sun Rong had beaten
most of the vitality out of that frog.
That Force Value Five
only took the little that was left.
No.
Every time it is hit,
there is a protective membrane effect.
But there wasn't one this time.
I got it.
It is playing dead.
The remaining spiritual force
changed into a spiritual body
and got away.
Wang Ling.
Yes.
You are going
to Class Elite.
What?
CLASS ELITE
Students of Class Elite,
my name is Pan Shengcong,
your main instructor.
Today's lesson
is the first summoning lesson
of this class.
Does anyone have any experience?
The space around us is filled
with spiritual bodies.
What we need to do
is create a passage in that space.
Your spiritual force level determines
the size of the passage you create.
The common ways of summoning
are drawing spiritual figures
or reading incantations.
By drawing a spiritual figure
and infusing it with spiritual force,
you can summon a spiritual beast.
In other words,
the strength
of the spiritual body you summon
is in proportion to your force level.
I'll first teach you
the basic summoning skills.
THE ART OF SUMMONING,
SPIRITUAL FIGURE, SUMMON, INCANTATION
All right,
those are the basic summoning skills.
You can start now.
Yes, miss.
Spiritual bodies nearby,
heed my summons
and drive away all the darkness.
-Show me the path.
-Young man,
you don't need
to be so hot-blooded to do this.
I offer my blood to you.
Come out, divine dragon.
Fulfill my wishes!
That's interesting.
Let me try.
You scoundrel!
Wait a minute. I can explain!
What is it that you summoned, Sun Rong?
A spiritual beast?
She's so wonderful.
So you were able to summon
a spiritual beast.
This seems the spiritual body
of a stray dog,
not a spiritual beast.
I can't summon something that strong.
Damn.
How much spiritual force does it take
to summon a spiritual beast?
I can see that most of you have done it.
Wang Ling,
what about you?
You don't seem to understand
my demonstration.
Do you want me to show you again?
ELITE
All right.
I'll just do it.
There are so many alien beings
in the space around.
I just don't know what will come out.
-Run!
-That Giant Frog?
Why is it you again?
Don't worry, students.
Here I come.
They have been combined.
-It's so lovely.
-It's so cute.
Let's raise him.
All right.
Let's call him Froggy Two. How is that?
Good idea.
Why are you so green?
Because Giant Frog is green.
It feels really good.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE