ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
This guy can see through my disguise.
He does have some capabilities.
Watch him carefully.
With your immortal-binding ropes,
these two students that are still
in their Foundation Phase
can't do anything.
This one seems to be a big fish.
At the school gate,
Ms. Sun Rong cared so much for him.
Jiang Liuying doesn't know that
she is dancing with an extremely dangerous
spiritual force bomb.
If the sealed negative energy bursts,
the world will be destroyed.
What is going on?
Master, why are you bound up like that?
You are a useless person
with only a force value of five.
The amulet can't hold on anymore.
Master, there isn't an amulet now.
You can only rely on yourself
to control your emotions.
What is it?
You don't want to accept it, do you?
Even a simple walk could bewitch you.
Lower your head.
Master.
Wang Ling!
Dry crispy noodles are 50% off today!
That's more like it.
Lower your head further.
Watch them carefully.
Do what I told you to do.
Yes,
Boss.
I had planned to disguise myself
as a student
to sneak in and get rid of Ms. Sun.
But now,
I have a new idea.
You have a student who failed a level
participating in a competition
for freshmen only.
You are indeed a well-known faction.
You are capable of everything.
A Level 1 student can repeat a level too.
Ms. Pan,
everyone deserves an education.
I hope you don't judge someone
by his scores.
Besides,
at least, He Bufeng is a human.
That's better than the dog
you brought for the competition!
Something bad happened!
Wang Ling has been kidnapped!
I'm sorry, young man.
I'm sorry for this.
Be patient.
It will be over very soon.
My boss may have a bad temper,
but she has her professional ethics.
Normally, she doesn't hurt
anyone irrelevant.
As long as you stay calm,
you can go home
after Ms. Sun has been killed.
To be honest,
I've always wanted to join Shadow Faction.
If you untie me,
I'll tell you everything I know.
Is that okay?
That's very good.
You are such a smart boy.
If you join our faction,
my boss will be very happy.
However,
only my boss can handle
the immortal-binding rope.
-So young man,
-Damn you.
take your time
and have a good rest here, all right?
People say that Shadow Faction
uses numbers to rank its members.
You are so awesome, sir.
What is your number?
I don't have a number.
I'm just a driver for my boss.
It seems that the Shadow Faction
is short on players.
They even send someone like you
on a mission.
SPIRITUAL INFANT
This driver has
a very strong spiritual force.
He just doesn't want to show it.
Here comes the wind.
It's time to put on more clothes.
When it happened,
I hid around the corner
and I saw that woman
dragging Wang Ling,
who was already bound up
around the corner and disappeared.
I waited there for a few more minutes
before I came here to report it.
That's what happened.
Was that woman beautiful,
has blond hair,
big bright eyes,
and an attractive figure?
I think so.
I get it.
If I'm correct,
she is the leader of Shadow Faction,
Jiang Liuying.
Boys nowadays certainly know
how to please women.
We defeated Shadow Faction
on our campus not long ago.
Enough.
It is absolutely safe here.
Faction 59 can guarantee that.
Do you call it safe
when someone is kidnapped right here?
Xiaobei,
do your calculations.
The response
of Wang Ling's spiritual force is weak,
so I'll concentrate on
unknown sources of spiritual force.
All spiritual force responses
within 5 km are nearby.
The old dormitory.
It has been deserted.
You--
That should be the place.
I'll send the Seven-Star Squad
to check it out.
Now that Shadow Faction has shown up,
we must take Ms. Sun back.
Her safety is our top priority.
We hope you can understand.
Sun Rong is still Shadow Faction's target.
We must take proper precautions.
If there are not enough people
on Faction 60's team,
they have to abstain from the competition.
Therefore,
I think we must try to rescue ourselves.
Mr. Sun,
we are from the Flower Fruit Group.
Never have we been cowards.
I don't care about the competition.
Nor do I care about the school's honor.
I only know
that Wang Ling
is my most important friend.
This is Jiang Liuying's provocation to me,
to the entire Flower Fruit Group.
As the representative of the group,
I will not fall back!
What a surprise.
Time flies.
Ms. Sun is old enough
to act on her own now.
Team Six,
come with me.
Let's get Wang Ling out of there.
-Yes, miss.
Take your team
to observe their performance
in a real battle.
Don't get yourselves involved
unless it is really necessary.
Yes, Ms. Xie.
Hey, kid.
I know you are hiding your true power.
Back then,
when I destroyed that boy's arm,
you were able to…
How could you fall asleep
with all that noise?
Master.
Wake up. Someone is here for you.
Wang Ling is quite relaxed now.
Finally, he doesn't have to try hard
to figure out
how to evade the competition.
Here I come.
It's time to do my job.
Help!
Somebody, help me!
Stay close to me.
Look over there.
-You guys,
-Wang Ling.
-fly up there to check it out.
-Hang on.
-We're coming!
-Yes.
The rest of you,
come with me.
-Yes.
Tang Jingze.
He Bufeng looks strange.
Be careful of him.
All right.
Watch him from behind.
It's so good to be young.
He is firing wolfberries.
Everyone, follow my orders. Stay alert!
-Yes.
Dodge!
These young men are so bad
at aiming properly.
You should care more about your fitness.
WOLFBERRY HAS ITS POWER
CRUISE TROOP OFFICE
You can't go in.
Is that all you have?
All right.
Let this old man show you
how to play the game.
Mr. Wang, look.
What's that?
YELLOW DISK TREASURE HOUSE
Tomato and tomato, come with me.
Something is not right.
What is it?
I'm sorry, guys.
It's quite late now,
so I'm going to take off.
This is bad! Run!
CAVALRY COMING OUT
INFANTRY COMING OUT
Get down!
It's too dangerous, miss!
You are still at an age
of building your body.
You are supposed
to go to bed early, Ms. Sun.
Go, Ocean!
Why don't you make an exception?
I can't let you in
no matter how important it is.
Come back tomorrow morning.
The Sword Competition
will be held tomorrow.
I don't care what it is…
What is happening?
That would be my night snack.
I remember
when my boss started
to learn swordsmanship,
she was about your age.
Damn.
-But in terms of talents,
-If this goes on, my spiritual force
-can't even sustain my flying.
-you are much weaker than she was.
The master's cavalry is so impressive.
What a naive girl.
The power of the horseless cavalry
is far beyond your capability.
Here I come.
It's time to do my job.
Help!
Somebody, help me!
Stay close to me.
Look over there.
It's all right now.
I've defeated the old driver.
Master Zhuo?
I have rescued the hostages.
The suspect is the spiritual infant killed
by Idle Beauty over a hundred years ago,
the Intention Devil.
-But a thread of his soul occupied
-Have you called an ambulance?
-the body of a dying old man.
-Yes, I have.
He has been in seclusion
for over a hundred years.
No one expected him
to show up here and now.
I'm done over here.
Hey.
He Bufeng,
what is it?
You seem to be unhappy.
There are quite a lot of people,
including this one.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Can I help you get down?
No, thank you.
I want to hang around here for a while.
I'll come to get you later.
By the way,
was this hole due to the battle?
No.
It's already like that when I got here.
It must have been leftover
from the construction.
Construction?
Master,
don't you want them to save He Bufeng?
Jingke,
stay here and watch him.
Don't let him get away.
However,
can you participate
in the competition without me?
Don't worry.
The competition is already over.
Wang Ling has a plan.
-Wang Ling!
-If He Bufeng is unable to participate,
-It's good to see you, Wang Ling!
-the competition will be canceled.
-Wang Ling. What is it?
-Then he will get away
before bringing about any disaster.
But Wang Ling was wrong.
It didn't make any sense.
I hid He Bufeng up, didn't I?
He's indeed a novice.
It is too late to be suspicious.
Dear students,
on behalf of the Cultivation Council,
I welcome all of you to participate
in this year's Sword Competition.
All participants,
please put your mobile phones
in the designated place.
The Organizing Committee
has prepared special devices
for you to use within your team.
Hello. Please take
these communications devices.
Mind reading doesn't work on him.
I wonder what's going on with Jingke.
After going on the field,
insert your sword into the altar,
keep it there for ten seconds,
then you'll have seized the altar
and you'll begin to accumulate your score.
Remember.
You are not allowed to fly on swords
or use other flying tricks
lifting you 5 m or more above the ground.
The battle area is covered
with a special restoring field.
So please don't worry.
Your cultivation will not be affected
even if you are hurt
during the competition.
-Please look over here.
-Please smile.
Destiny knows how to play jokes.
Wang Ling is now participating
in the competition
which he has been trying to evade
from the very beginning.
Although it is against his wish,
seeing that his friends
did all they could to save him,
-he must also do his best now.
-Go for it, Faction 60!
Xiaobei,
it's about to begin.
Don't worry, Tang Jingze.
The analysis will be finished right away.
I will get the data
on the spiritual force features
of every rival.
Ms. Sun,
you will not get away this time.
Finally, I wish you all prosper
with your magical power.
The competition officially begins now.
Lingling!
Your amulet!
Lingling.
Your…
Aren't you Wang Ling's dad?
What are you doing here?
Welcome.
-You are…
-Are you my master's…
Are you Wang Ling's dad?
It's my great pleasure to meet you.
That is
what happened.
What?
The amulet that contains
his spiritual force is breaking?
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE