Darling, why did Lingling stop talking
after he had the amulet on?
The amulet seals his force value
but restrains his passion
at the same time.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
We've hacked into the system.
Hey! Where is He Bufeng?
He Bufeng's spiritual force is different
from that in our record.
Transmission to him failed.
What does it mean?
It means
when you meet He Bufeng,
you must be careful.
I've got responses
from all Faction 60's members.
Chen Chao landed
in the west, near the Altar of Metal.
Sun Rong landed
in the north, near the Altar of Water.
The dog landed
in the south, near the Altar of Fire.
FIRE
He Bufeng's source of spiritual force
is also there.
Where is the weakest guy?
Wang Ling's source of spiritual force
is close to zero.
It's beyond the range of detection.
It's simple.
The four of us are at the center.
Wang Ling isn't in the west,
north, or south.
So this guy
is most probably in the east,
near the Altar of Wood.
ELITE
Leave him to me.
Altar of Wood is mine!
What a teammate.
Wait a minute. There is one more guy.
There is Guo Hao.
That's right. Where is he?
Let me handle him.
No hurry.
Let's seize the altar first.
Do you want me to get rid of him?
That's not necessary.
It'll be enough if we just seize
and hold three altars.
Go and handle the idiot
at the Altar of Metal.
I'm going to the Altar of Water.
Ms. Sun and I
have an old account to settle.
As for the moron
that Liang Fei is going to face,
he will add to our credits.
These guys from Faction 59
are so powerful.
These stand-ins cost me a fortune
and I lost one of them
even before the competition began.
But this guy who is going
to pick on Wang Ling
seems to be the weakest
among the Faction 59's team.
Wait for me, Wang Ling.
Instead of adding to their credits,
you are going to add to their troubles.
Faction 59 seized the Altar of Earth.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 1.
-What?
-Seizure by Faction 60 is 0.
Faction 59 has started seizing them.
Wait a minute. How do I seize it?
Insert your sword into the socket,
wait for ten seconds, and that will do.
Thank you.
How are you, Chen Chao?
This altar
is mine.
SUPER
My family has a motto.
Men don't fight women.
As you kindly reminded me earlier,
you can make three moves on me.
Come on. Do it.
I'm done.
Now it's your turn.
What? Just despising me like that?
Are you surprised?
Do it.
What is going on?
When did you set up the dirty trick?
Web of Dimensions can capture prey,
invade the nervous system,
and produce false neuronal signals
to control the body.
The side of the web
facing the prey is invisible.
Damn it.
This is
so real.
This is the cruelty that every
young man is supposed to experience.
He will not be killed,
but all the wounds and pains
are 100% real, on a 1-to-1 scale.
Chen Chao,
you're having it hard.
Don't run away!
It seems you can truly devour
negative energies.
That was quite a bite of spiritual energy.
Is he dead?
Let me seize the altar first.
If you just die like this,
you should feel lucky.
If I devour more spiritual energy
that is leaked when they are fighting,
I will be able to break the seal on me.
So you are still alive.
Perfect.
Take this!
TAKE THIS
Thank goodness.
I made it in time.
SIXTY
Wang Ling,
I'm not too late, am I?
Morons are still morons,
no matter how many you are!
High energy up ahead!
They have seized two altars
and Guo Hao is in trouble too.
I must seize this altar as soon as I can.
You never changed.
As sneaky as ever.
You are the same as before too.
As skillful as ever.
And
this is like meeting an old friend.
That was my greeting.
You are not my friend.
Okay.
Let's just forget about
the unpleasant things between us.
But the Flower Fruit Water Curtain
Sun family and Tang family
were related thousands of years ago
on the journey to the west.
This long-lasting relationship
is not to be broken off easily.
Even your ancestor, Sun himself--
Shut up.
The name of my ancestor
is not for you to mention so casually!
If you want me to shut up,
you must beat me first.
Faction 59 seized the Altar of Fire.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 3.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 0.
I've encountered the dog,
but it didn't give me much trouble.
That's very good.
Come to the Altar of Water now.
There is someone here
that you want to meet.
He Bufeng has knocked the dog off.
He deserves my trust in him after all.
How did you know where Froggy Two was?
Have you forgotten about Yisha Bei?
I am able to see every move of yours.
NATIONAL SENIOR PHASE
SWORD COMPETITION
This is bad. I must seize
the Altar of Water as soon as I can.
Ms. Sun,
I know what you are thinking.
So you must hurry up.
We are going to seize
another altar very soon.
Chen Chao.
Five. Four.
Three. Two.
One.
Faction 59 seized the Altar of Metal.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 4.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 0.
That looks so nice.
Are you going to use Ocean Dance?
I know it was made
from the Ocean Stabilizer,
but…
I don't think my Blowing Snow
will lose to it.
Tang Jingze is activating
his Blowing Snow.
I must finish this before He Bufeng comes.
Ms. Sun,
you have some skills.
It's a shame that it's not enough
to beat you.
He Bufeng is here.
Are you trying to be smart again?
The situation is not in my favor.
It is better for me
to try to seize other altars
than tangling with them
in an endless fight.
See? I told you.
We meet again, Ms. Sun.
But the lake has been sealed
by Tang Jingze.
I can't get away
with my trick of water escape.
I've got to do something.
What the…
-This…
-What happened?
What strong negative energy.
It seems to be stronger than yours.
She couldn't have gone far.
Go and find her.
I'm going to insert my sword.
I don't care who you are,
but you must do what I say.
After I win,
I'll help you fulfill your wish.
Seizing the altar.
Counting down. Ten.
Nine. Eight.
Faction 59 seized the Altar of Water.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 5.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 0.
Faction 59 has seized all altars.
A speedup bonus is rewarded to them.
Faction 60 seized the Altar of Wood.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 4.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 1.
The speedup bonus is rescinded.
Liang Fei.
Liang Fei
was defeated by something odd.
Wang Ling and the dog have combined!
-What?
-I made a genius out of him.
Never mind.
I must meet up with Guo Hao now.
Altar of Wood.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE