ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
My goodness.
Fatty's Mouth Cannon is terrible.
He shouts out so many words
in a matter of a breath
and none of the words are repeated!
OLD ORANGUTAN
THICK LIPS, BIG LEGS
This is bad!
Mouth Cannon cannot repeat
itself in a short time.
There aren't many words I can think of.
It looks like
you have a limited vocabulary.
Stinky Fatty,
shoot as many as you can!
Damn.
I don't know much about him.
If I can't hit the right point,
this trick will have no use.
The harder you fight,
the more spiritual force you will leak.
And that will feed me.
Why is he here too?
Sit upright, you trash.
I'll come back for you soon.
Wang Ling!
Do you want to remain
"Force Value Five" all your life?
How did he think of
a new phrase all of a sudden?
I may have a limited vocabulary
to use on you.
But for someone else,
I have a basket of phrases to use!
My apologies, Wang Ling.
JERK
Good for nothing. Coward!
You are so lame!
Unfaithful. Irresponsible!
You are so fake!
Stone-hearted!
Cold-blooded!
Pathetic!
Poker face!
-Ignorant!
-Wang Ling knows
-that the amulet can't hold long.
-Arrogant.
-Loner.
-So he cannot show
-Chicken!
-either his spiritual force
-or even a bit of his emotion.
-Heartless!
The more Wang Ling restrains himself,
the more he is misunderstood.
An emotion that Wang Ling
has never known grows in him
and is about to break the amulet.
It's aggravation.
Why is the dog biting its own teammate?
You have to rely on me
to devour your negative energy.
That means
I can use my spiritual force at will now.
Is this a setup?
My goodness!
I have a limited capacity!
Take it easy!
Wang Ling,
is this trick called
"human in dog's form"?
A moron plus a dog.
Is this the legendary stylish waste?
But you are just Force Value Five.
You trash!
Excuse me, my friend.
-I…
-As Liang Fei recalled later,
it was like he was being hit by
a heavy truck roaring from his left side.
Wang Ling,
my efforts have paid off.
I've made a genius out of you.
Now,
-let's strike back.
-Okay!
Faction 60 seized the Altar of Wood.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 4.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 1.
The speedup bonus is rescinded.
Kangkang,
did you teach this human-beast
combination to Wang Ling?
Of course.
I'd like to learn it!
Can you teach me?
After the competition,
Wang Zukang returns home
and teaches his dog
for three days and nights,
but achieves nothing.
How could this happen?
That Force Value Five's spiritual force
merged with that dog's
and knocked Liang Fei off.
What?
What did you say?
-Combination of spiritual forces?
-Yes.
The combined spiritual force
is incredibly strong.
He has fooled us all by hiding
this surprising trick
until the last minute.
Where is he now?
At the Altar of Fire.
Faction 60 seized the Altar of Fire.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 3.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 2.
Don't look at me.
You asked me to come here.
Where are the other Faction 60's members?
The rude one hasn't woken up yet,
and Fatty is on guard
at the Altar of Wood.
I can't pinpoint Sun Rong's location.
She got away
with her trick of water escape.
That explains it.
All right. I'm going to get out of here.
The combined two seized the Altar of Fire
and are heading here.
Go to the Altar of Earth now.
We can't afford to lose
the central position.
Liang Zheng.
Liang Fei.
Liang Zheng!
Go to the Altar of Fire now
and take it back.
Yes, I'm going right away.
We have one down,
but they are also one fewer
because of the combination.
The extremely strong spiritual force of
the combination is to their disadvantage
while holding more altars than they do
is our advantage.
What he's going to do next
is to come here
and seize the Altar of Water.
If I call every one of us
to come here to defend it,
then both sides will suffer a heavy loss.
The four of us against only one of them
are not worth it.
The other altars,
with no one defending them,
will be seized easily.
So
we must avoid that combination.
Try not to face him directly.
This way, we will be able to seize
the other altars very easily.
If we are constantly on the move
and maintain this one-to-four score,
we will have the final victory.
Xiaobei,
go to the Altar of Wood and meet me there.
Keep me updated
on the status of the combination.
Yes.
ELITE
Chen Chao.
SUPER
Come back, you damned woman!
Where is the woman who lied to me?
So you were on a date here, Chen Chao.
It's not what you think, Wang Ling!
Wang Ling, why are you dressed like this?
I have combined with it.
You…
I know.
A bachelor always needs
a dog as a companion.
That's why we are called bachelor dogs.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
-Seven.
-Faction 59 has 3.
-Faction 60 has 2.
-Six.
Five. Four.
-That's to say,
-Three.
-after seizing this one,
-Two.
-we will overrun them.
-One.
Faction 60 seized the Altar of Metal.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 2.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 3.
This is great!
Tell me, Wang Ling.
How did this miracle come about?
You are smiling.
Wang Ling is smiling!
Wang Ling himself doesn't know
why he is smiling
as he has never smiled like that before.
The reason for this
is only known to Wang Ling's dad.
Faction 59 seized the Altar of Fire
and the Altar of Wood.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 4.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 1.
They overran us again so fast.
At this moment, Wang Ling realized
that Tang Jingze
was using the strategy
of three racing horses.
He knows that
to seize the altars
as laid out on this map,
no matter how powerful he is,
he will be like a trapped beast.
Is he the same Wang Ling as before?
Hey! I may be able to devour
your negative energy,
but I have limited capacity.
Stop it!
If I go beyond that limit,
we are all done for.
The only way Wang Ling can think of
is to be faster.
He wants to seize all altars
before the enemy arrives.
The rules of this competition
are not for one powerful player
to beat all the others.
Even if one is fast enough to reach
all the altars in an instant,
the ten seconds required
to start the score accumulation
is something he can never avoid.
Wang Ling, Chen Chao.
Yes, Sun Rong.
What is going on?
Guo Hao and I are together now.
How can that be?
He ran away from the Altar of Wood
and ran into me.
What a coward!
Tang Jingze and that
Yisha Bei or something
showed up there all of a sudden!
Why didn't you fight back?
Didn't you give up on that Yisha Bei too?
You are in no position to blame me!
-I…
-Shut up, both of you!
Guo Hao did nothing wrong.
The key to this competition
is not to beat the rival,
but to seize the altars.
We should avoid engaging
in unnecessary fights
unless the odds are in our favor.
Guo Hao just told me
the Yisha Bei on their team
had an ability to our disadvantage.
Positioning.
Tang Jingze, I've found Sun Rong.
Ms. Sun,
I'd like to see
what other tricks you've got.
NATIONAL SENIOR PHASE
SWORD COMPETITION
We have one absolute advantage,
which is Wang Ling.
What a surprise.
You are being shy.
They will try not to face
Wang Ling directly.
We can tacitly agree that
if Wang Ling seizes one altar,
we will have two altars
firmly in our hands
including the Altar of Metal.
But we are still behind them
with two-to-three.
We need to send someone
to seize another altar.
What if we send someone out
and they send someone to take this one?
We'll count on you then, Chen Chao.
So that's
how it is.
Wang Ling finally understands
-that he is not the key person
-No problem. You can count on me!
in this competition.
ELITE, SUPER
My family has a motto.
A man's muscles are for
the sole purpose of protecting others.
Hard and strong.
I just made a reconnaissance
on the three waterside altars
with the help of my trick of water.
The Altar of Earth is at a key position,
so they put their strongest hand there.
Therefore,
Guo Hao and I will attack
their weakest point.
This is bad!
Sun Rong and Fatty are moving
toward the Altar of Fire at a high speed.
That's not reasonable.
The Altar of Fire
is the farthest to reach.
If they go there from the Altar of Wood,
they must go around the Altar of Earth
which is being guarded by He Bufeng.
They are going
by water.
Here comes your grandpa!
Stinky brother!
Who is calling me?
Come out and kowtow to me, my brother!
You asked for it.
Liang Zheng, are Sun Rong and Fatty there?
Tang Jingze, I only see Fatty
and I'm about to knock him out.
It was I who sent
your stupid brother away!
So you are the one who hurt my brother.
Idiot! Stay with the altar.
Don't let him steal it.
Faction 60 seized the Altar of Water.
Seizure by Faction 59 is 3.
Seizure by Faction 60 is 2.
Liang Zheng,
if you lose the Altar of Fire,
I'll kick you out of the Student Union!
Hey, my brother! Where are you looking?
Your grandpa is here!
Hey! Look at me, your grandpa.
I don't care who you are,
but you must do what I say.
After I win,
I'll help you fulfill your wish.
I believe it is my turn now.
COME BACK!
As long as you win,
I don't care how you do it.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE