As an old saying goes,
when two stars collide,
a mountain will fit into a grass seed.
Where is the baby?
The baby…
Mr. Wang, your baby…
He…
He crawled out by himself.
Mr. Wang!
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
Look at this, my son.
Dad and Mom bought this for you.
It costs my half-year savings.
I stayed online
for three whole days for it.
A Dragon-Slaughtering Sword.
It's a limited edition.
Dear, I didn't know
you would spend so much on our son.
Darling.
It was for our son. It's not a payment.
-It's an investment.
-As the chosen one,
he had to tolerate unimaginable torments
at a very small age.
-You are so great, dear.
-Wang Ling can hear what people think,
so he has to face the pretense
of the world much sooner.
I have always wanted to have this sword.
Finally, I had the excuse to buy it.
So much money was wasted on this rubbish.
A man's romance is always based on waste.
I searched for three days and nights
to find this perfect counterfeit.
-Wang Ling is now facing
-The money should have been saved.
his first philosophy problem.
Come on, my son. Take the sword.
If he didn't take it,
this kind of harassment from his parents
would never stop.
If he did,
this counterfeit
or even a real Dragon-Slaughtering Sword,
wouldn't be able to stand
the spiritual force at his fingertips.
Do you call this a treasured sword?
It can't even stand
a baby's spiritual force!
It's just a toy anyway.
Do you have to be so serious?
-What?
-If a sword breaks,
-they can buy another one.
-What happened to my sword?
If the marriage breaks up,
Wang Ling will feel troubled.
Half a year's savings
and you bought a counterfeit!
I did this for our family,
you useless one.
-Come on. Come take it.
-Stretch out your little hands.
At a rate of 387 times a second,
Wang Ling considered different ways
to react to this.
Then,
the force of origin
that had been accumulating inside him
burst at this crucial moment.
This is bad. He's peeing!
Take care of him now.
I'll get the diapers.
So, that was
a little thought-provoking story
of how one morning urine saved a marriage.
And Wang Ling figured out
the first philosophy
of his life.
You silly boy.
Stop biting the toy. Your milk is ready.
It is better to keep a low profile.
SONGHAI, 10 YEARS AGO
But at the age of six,
Wang Ling failed to confine his force.
The poor Wang couple
never graduated
from the body-building phase.
What Wang Ling did
was way beyond their cognition.
At this moment,
the couple reached a unified conclusion
that they had never done before,
a unanimous vote for the principle
of keeping a low profile in life.
Wang Ling's dad was in charge
of finding a way on the web
to contain spiritual forces
and managed to implement it
before Wang Ling went to primary school.
I'm done.
HARD
Wait.
Give me your hand.
I told you
the effect of the counterfeit
force-containing amulet is not steady.
You must take a golden pill daily
as a supplement.
The black and gold bowl is ruined
and a pair of steel chopsticks
is almost lost.
You have to be more patient, my son.
I'm almost done
with the new version of the amulet.
You will have it within this year.
You have been saying that every day
over the past decade.
It will be done this year.
Most of it has been finished.
The routine argument
is about to begin again.
Darling, I can guarantee
that within this year,
the latest amulet
will have the expected effect.
It may have some resistance to drugs,
but you must have confidence
in scientific cultivation, darling.
ELITE
I wouldn't care about that
if it weren't for our son.
I don't have to remind you
what we have been through these years
for this amulet.
On his seventh birthday…
Come on, let's make a wish.
Blow out the candles.
The entire house was almost burned down.
When he was ten,
while playing with his friends,
he took their clothes off!
I want him to live an ordinary life.
Over the past ten years,
Wang Ling has sensed
his parents' trouble and effort.
I'm sure you know
what he has been taking
are just low-power pills,
special pills
-that reduce one's spiritual forces.
-This is something
Wang Ling found out
for the first time in ten years.
CULTIVATION SCHOOL
So he decided
not to do anything impressive
before the new amulet is finished.
-My fellow students.
-Come have a look.
-Vote for me, Chen Chao.
-Give Chen Chao your support!
-What is this?
-She's pretty.
-Elect the goddess
-and it's a glory for all!
Vote for her and you'll get
a huge gift pack of golden pills.
And a lucky draw chance for Ms. Sun Rong's
bikini photo with her autograph.
Places of trouble like this
should be avoided whenever possible.
Except…
-Sir, give me a pack.
-Sir.
CAMPUS SHOP
DRY NOODLES ON SALE TODAY
Sir, give me ten packs
of the intestine flavor.
-Give me one pack.
-I want five packs of chives flavor.
-Give me one.
-Don't push me, okay?
They even have the intestine flavor.
-Give me some.
-This is tasty.
DRY NOODLES ON SALE
Stop pushing me.
Payment. Spirit Force Pay.
A total of 538,404 yuan.
-What is he doing?
-That's impressive.
-That's too much.
-Indeed.
-How can he do that?
Hi, everybody.
Today, everything in this shop
is free for freshmen.
-Is this really happening?
-He's so good.
-This is awesome!
Please support
Sun Rong of Class 1, Level 1.
-Soliciting votes is a shame!
-We refuse trickery!
Who is slandering me?
It's Sun Rong.
-Look!
-It is Sun Rong, the shining girl.
-She is dazzling indeed.
-It's Sun Rong.
It's dazzling.
That's it. Turn them off.
-She's dazzling.
-It's Sun Rong!
She's looking at me!
-She's amazing.
-I want to be like her.
She's so beautiful.
She's looking at me.
Guo Hao and Chen Chao,
why do you have
that preconception against me?
You…
That's cheating!
It's not fair to solicit votes
by giving gifts.
I'm just demonstrating my capabilities.
How could you call that cheating?
Those who believe in me and accept me
will vote for me naturally.
That's the fairest choice.
It sounds right.
That's a fallacious argument!
The class president is supposed
to help his classmates.
We won't yield to you
for such small benefits.
Chen Chao, I suggest you say it nicely.
That's moral coercion. That's shameful!
-Sun Rong.
-Yes.
I'll give you five votes
for five packs of dry noodles.
At this point, Wang Ling
can't hold himself anymore.
Sun Rong.
All right.
Why is it him who stands out to help me?
-Five votes for five packs of dry noodles.
-What's wrong with him?
It's not right.
Each student has only one vote.
Indeed.
You can give 100 votes if you want.
Give me ten votes.
I mean,
I don't care if you vote for me or not
or how many you want to vote.
I only want to do my best
to give you my care.
I want that one.
-I want the whole box.
-I want this one.
-Me too.
-That one tastes better.
-This is mine.
-Thank you.
-You misunderstood her, Chen Chao.
-Give me one.
-Look at the way it is written.
"Vote for Sun Rong"
and "Everything is free"
are two different things.
You were just too mean.
I will have a showdown with her
in a dignified way.
You have been busy today. Have a drink.
It's free. You don't need to vote.
Is she thinking of using that tactic?
Not giving the tiniest part of me
to benefit the world.
-Give me a pack.
-This is mine.
SUN
The art of seduction is working.
Such small benefits
and the freshmen are all here.
All captured,
including the most difficult one,
Chen Chao,
all thanks to…
Where is he?
Who are you looking for, miss?
The boy who took five packs
of dry noodles.
He has been gone for a while.
But he asked me
to give you this before he left.
A golden pill?
Wang Ling felt that with one vote
for five packs of dry noodles,
he owed Sun Rong a favor.
So he gave her a golden pill
that his mom had forced on him
to make it even.
CLASS ELITE
SUN
Students, did you prepare
for today's lesson?
-Yes, we did.
However, we will skip that today
and study the second lesson from the last.
I'll capture them all today.
The Ancient Arts of Confinement.
The so-called seduction
is to use incantations with hand seals
to project your spiritual force
on other people
so that your spiritual force turns them
into your fans.
-Studies in ancient books show…
-This is bad.
-The instructor saw through me.
-This little wise guy
was good at a mind game,
which is called
"taking advantage of seduction
on other people."
Thousands of years ago,
there was an immortal who called
himself "Little Wise Guy."
He had 3,000 followers.
The spell we are talking about today
was passed down from him.
When the spell works, a predetermined sign
will affect other people's minds.
But there is one precondition
for this spell
which is giving gifts.
When this precondition is met
and the incantation,
"Not giving the tiniest part of me
to benefit the world" is read,
a spiritual force field is created.
Everyone in this field
who has taken the free gifts
will relax their mind guard.
The spiritual force in the field
takes advantage of this to go in
and leaves a sign
of the spiritual force on the subjects.
The subjects know nothing
about the process.
-The imposer, however, can use this sign
-Wang Ling is suddenly aware
-to affect their minds.
-of why Sun Rong did those things
at the shop.
Take as much as you want.
Enjoy the free benefits.
Luckily, I returned her favor.
What am I worried about?
It's natural that someone likes you.
Sir, is there a way to break away from it?
Men of great power
can directly break
or remove the sign with their power.
She's still trying to use it on me.
I've returned her the favor
and no longer meet the precondition.
Could it be that
her bodyguard didn't give her the pill?
Wang Ling is so annoying.
Why is he staring at me like that?
What does this mean?
Something round.
Could it be…
the golden pill?
"Eating it
is good for you.
Please?"
Of course, there are also imposers…
SUN
Could it be a pill of high power?
He wants to help boost my spiritual power
to become the class president?
What Wang Ling actually means is,
"The dry noodles you gave taste good.
Thank you."
What he has been taking
are just low-power pills,
special pills that reduce
one's spiritual forces.
It's matcha flavored.
SUN
This feels like falling
from clouds 30,000 feet above the ground.
The lack of spiritual force
will end the seduction before it works.
Wang Ling,
what kind of pill did you give me?
Now let's have a student come up here
to give us a demonstration.
Sun Rong.
Yes.
You always learn fast.
Come and give us a demonstration
of what is said in the book.
All right.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That was a close call. Be careful.
Now you do it, Wang Ling. Say it.
"Not giving the tiniest part of me
to benefit the world."
That's very good.
Next,
the candidates, Sun Rong and Chen Chao,
let's have the election
for the president of the class.
Congratulations.
-To cheat the world
-Chief Chen.
-rather than be cheated by the world.
-I'll count on you, President.
That's impossible.
Sun Rong is paying for what she did.
Those gestures may look random,
but he cracked the spell
cast on the entire class so easily.
Even I haven't seen anything like that.
Moreover,
mastering the incantation
after hearing it only once
is no ordinary feat.
Okay.
How annoying!
If he wanted to hurt me,
why did he support me at the shop?
"Not giving the tiniest part of me
to benefit the world."
I just can't drive him out of my mind!
SIXTY
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE