ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
For today's pill refining class,
what brand of furnace did you bring?
Brand Mi's new electric furnace.
What about you, Xiao Jing?
Nothing special.
A Fruit iFire Xmax furnace.
A counterfeit bought on Pinxixi!
Do you think I can't see it?
It's nothing
but a smuggled furnace on Goudong.
There's no need to show off!
-Chen Chao?
Chen Chao, why did you bring
the copper cauldron from home?
My great-grandpa used this cauldron
to refine Level 9 golden pills.
You are awesome, Chen Chao.
It can even make golden pills.
He must be thinking
of something unrealistic.
-Good morning, Sun Rong.
-Wang Ling.
At this moment, seeing the sign
of a spell over Sun Rong's head,
he knew instantly
that he had seduced
Sun Rong's heart at some point.
So he makes a prompt decision.
Sun Rong.
WANG
Okay.
It's all right now.
What was that Force Value Five doing?
I don't understand his way of flirting.
EVERYONE IS A GOLDEN PILL
What happened, miss?
Miss!
What…
What happened to me?
Today, we're going to learn
how to make the most basic vitality pills.
The procedures are simple,
so I'm going to make it quick.
I hope you can keep up with me.
-Yes.
STEPS TO MAKE VITALITY PILLS
INSTRUCTOR: PAN SHENGCONG
Steps to make vitality pills.
First, get a Yangcheng pot ready.
Next,
take gold sand,
tortoiseshell, and dragon bone.
Cut up, grind, and put it in.
Cut up some Acorus tatarinowii.
Cut up some Radix polygalae.
Scatter it in.
Add Powder Number 15
and 7 drops of lapis lazuli oil.
Flatten it, put it in the furnace,
and close it.
Tape it, seal up the furnace,
and start the fire.
Set the alarm to 5 p.m.
Are you all clear about the process?
Now let's see what you can do.
It's time for me to show them
what I've got.
First, refining pills is an art of fire.
The big cauldron of the Chen family
was designed for refining
large quantities of pills.
For a small quantity like this,
it's hard to control the time for heating.
Sun Rong behaves like she knows something.
She even brought the refining machine
from her family's factory?
Does that even count as her own effort?
What?
Someone is using a microwave oven
to do the refining.
Forget it.
It's time to show my magic tool.
What is this?
What is it?
It took quite a lot of my money
and effort to get this treasure.
An elegant shape. An antique style.
Built-in temperature control
and display of position and time.
Next, put in the ingredients.
It can automatically judge
the feng shui direction
and take in spiritual force.
-This furnace is so delicate.
-It's just the spiritual essence
-of a copper furnace.
-It looks alive.
Shut up.
This is not bad.
I should get one someday.
-Chen Chao.
-It exploded.
It doesn't take enthusiasm and vigor
to refine pills,
but attention and patience.
My dad is going to kill me!
Is Chen Chao okay?
Don't worry about him.
He must be running around the schoolyard.
It's going to take seven hours.
We'll come back by then
to check the pills you have made.
-Yes.
GUO HAO: MAY LOOK IDLE IN CLASS,
BUT STUDIES HARD AT HOME
CHEN CHAO: FROM A KUNG FU FAMILY,
THINKS MUSCLES SOLVE EVERY PROBLEM
I haven't eaten a spiritual pet
for a long time.
Back then,
by eating things weaker than I was,
I gradually evolved into a demon king.
If I can start over,
I will rise up again.
I knew you were up to something.
Luckily, I came in time.
Stop!
Stupid human.
I jumped from the fifth
to the fourth floor
and he jumped directly
to the ground floor.
How did you end up here?
Let's talk nicely.
Talk nicely. Don't come any closer!
ELITE
Chen Chao ran 12 laps.
He has such a strong body.
SUPER
Dad,
I have a pill refining class today,
so I want to borrow the copper cauldron.
That is the treasure
of our family for generations.
I don't want it damaged.
Doesn't the furnace exist
for refining golden pills
to give credit to our Chen family?
You know what will happen
if you don't get the first place.
Dad!
MEN
Guo Hao, I can explain.
Why do you have
my treasured furnace?
Put it on the ground gently.
Back away!
ELITE
You'd better give me
a reasonable explanation.
At his weakest point,
the mind devil intruded his mind.
Sun Rong.
Lord Wang Ling.
Did she think that even
the Force Value Five was better than me?
-He's not good enough to be president.
-He's so weak.
-Wang Ling's microwave oven
-He'd better quit.
makes better pills.
We refined pills,
but he ended up in an explosion.
Goodbye.
President of Explosion.
No!
Sun Rong.
I'm coming to save you.
Froggy Two swallowed my furnace.
You went after him
from the fifth floor to the fourth floor.
You took the furnace out of his mouth
and then washed it in the bathroom.
Is that what happened?
Do you think I'll believe you?
Ask your furnace if you don't believe me.
ELITE
Is this how you treated my treasure?
You are a dead man, Wang Ling!
My goodness! What did I do?
What did I do?
Thank goodness it's not serious.
A mind devil and weak toxicity.
The art of grand purification will do.
We mustn't let anyone know about this.
Take his head. I'll take his legs.
Come on!
PILL REFINING CLASS
The pentatoxic potion I made
was intended for external use.
It can induce
patches of rashes on the skin.
But Chen Chao drank it,
which made things much worse.
If the toxin is not removed
within four hours,
-he will be in grave danger.
-Actually, it is not that bad.
-I can--
-Wang Ling,
if you can make an antidote for me
and keep this thing a secret,
I will not blame you anymore
for taking my furnace.
Do whatever you want.
Now try to find Level 3,
Book 1 textbook for pill refining.
I've found it.
Now,
get the ingredients for me.
Angelica Sinensis, 30 g.
Vigna angularis rolls, 80 g.
Ligusticum striatum, 90 g.
Scutellaria baicalensis, 90 g.
Astragalus sieversianus, 30 g.
Rhizoma Cyperi, 30 g.
Cistanche deserticola, 90 g.
Cornus Officinalis, 90 g.
Radix Cyathulae, 30 g.
And four hours to refine.
Wait.
The instructor is coming back soon!
We can have the antidote in four hours,
but our instructor and classmates
will be back in two hours.
Where are we going to hide Chen Chao?
When the instructor
collects the pill we make,
what are we going to give to her?
What now?
Don't just sit there, Wang Ling.
Do something!
Don't touch my furnace!
Are you all right, baby?
What was that light?
What did that thing do to my furnace?
Wang Ling, look.
Pre-heating just started,
but it has already turned orange.
Normally, this doesn't happen
in just two minutes.
Maybe…
The heating process was sped up!
-I didn't know you could do this.
-Of course I can.
My spiritual force
is to control timelines.
With enough spiritual force,
I can speed up the timeline
and even reverse the timeline.
That means,
if we give Froggy Two
more spiritual forces,
he will be able
to produce accelerating rays.
We'll get the antidote much sooner.
Now you know my power, don't you?
Why don't you untie me now?
Wait!
What do you want to do?
Why did you make two antidote pills?
I was thinking of testing it on me
to see if it was effective.
But now,
we have a more convenient subject.
Don't touch me!
PENTATOXIC POTION: 1, ANTIDOTE: 2
USE, ABORT
AFTER USING THE PENTATOXIC POTION,
FROGGY TWO IS POISONED!
PENTATOXIC POTION
The rashes are gone.
-Chen Chao can take it now.
-Yes.
Wang Ling,
help Chen Chao up.
I think he'll wake up
by the end of the school day.
This is bad!
Our instructor and classmates
are coming back.
What do we do?
I'll delay them at the door.
I'll leave this to you.
Guo Hao,
why are you here?
Because…
I didn't know
if I set the heating time correctly.
I just wanted to make sure.
Let's have a look at
what you came up with first.
Wait, miss. You can't go in now!
Miss!
Wang Ling was really quick.
So this is your furnace.
Wait a minute, miss.
It still has two more steps to go.
What's going on?
-Guo Hao has made golden pills.
-How did these vitality pills
-get into my furnace?
-They look so fine.
Could it be…
That's my friend.
He put the pills he made into my furnace.
Did he really make the pill
with that microwave oven?
It's not bad. I'll give you a score of 85.
Wang Ling was back early too.
No. What about his vitality pills?
Wang Ling,
we are making pills, not explosives.
I get it.
Wang Ling put the pill
that caused Chen Chao's explosion
into his microwave oven.
Wang Ling,
you are my friend for life!
Actually, Guo Hao was wrong.
When washing the furnace,
Wang Ling didn't take out
the vitality pill.
When Guo Hao was making the antidote,
he made the vitality pill along with it.
Wang Ling did nothing at all.
The microwave oven just failed
to make a pill.
As for Chen Chao's pill…
You are finally awake.
When we were leaving,
we saw you lying on the ground exhausted.
So we took you here.
Right!
My copper cauldron!
Look behind you.
We managed to repair it.
You guys repaired it for me?
Of course.
Wang Ling,
I'm sorry!
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
Taming the demon king,
driving out the mind devil,
and good at many kinds
of spectacular magical arts.
This should be the one
you are looking for.
This year's freshmen
are quite interesting.
Wang Ling.