The fireworks
are so beautiful.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
CLASS ELITE
Class is over.
-All right.
On campus that afternoon,
a scent of hormones floats in the air.
Sun Rong is walking towards her prey,
but the prey doesn't have
a clue of his fate.
At this time,
the hunter becomes the target
of someone else.
The wheel of fate keeps turning.
At the top of the food chain,
a new competitor appears.
Wang Ling.
DILIGENCE PAYS OFF
Do you have time for a date tomorrow?
She is so direct
that Wang Ling is at a loss
for a response.
Sun Rong has Wang Ling as her target,
but she doesn't know
that she herself is also a target.
Target confirmed.
Sun Rong, heir to
the Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group.
She has no brain or armor.
To be killed by one shot.
Waiting for orders.
Do it.
At that moment,
the assassins
felt an overwhelming unknown pressure.
Wang Ling,
please date me!
-What?
-What's going on?
-Why does it have to be Wang Ling?
-Yes. Why him?
You are useless!
The boss just burped.
Why are you so scared?
Wang Ling.
Yes.
ELITE
Come to my office.
Wang Ling won't let go
of this opportunity to get away.
Boss, the target is lost.
We'll follow her
to the next sniping point.
Withdraw.
Yes.
Why? Give me one more chance.
Next time.
There is someone tough on campus.
Where are you going after school?
-Are you coming along?
-Sure.
She should have given up.
Let's invite more people.
-Sure.
-Of course.
I didn't expect
that he would agree so readily.
What Wang Ling meant
was to escape with Wang Zukang.
He didn't know
this would evolve into a love story.
FACTION 60 OFFICIAL WEBSITE
So this is the Force Value Five guy.
-Is this real?
-Who is that guy?
-He is that Force Value Five.
-Is it true?
This is Force Value Five.
My goodness.
-He is Force Value Five.
-I want to skip 20 years too.
-Who is he?
-Indeed.
Let's date!
He's awesome.
Kill him if he refuses
-his wife's request.
-Today is the darkest day of my life.
Darling!
This opportunity
might be even better.
Wang Ling,
this is the Joint Honorary Master Immortal
of the School League,
Master Zhuo Yi.
He has something to ask you.
Hello, Wang Ling.
Mr. Wang, will you…
Okay, I'll leave you two alone.
CALMNESS OF MIND MAKES JOY OF HEART
You were that little boy
who defeated Giant Frog
some years ago, weren't you?
A thousand-year-old demon
and you beat it with just one kick.
All the people think I did it.
Master,
I've been looking for you all these years.
When I saw your great power back then,
I was determined to find you
and have you as my master.
The 50…
The 50%…
trick of forgetting.
The 100% trick of forgetting.
Targets that are beamed at by this trick
lose memory about designated events
and at the same time have the risk
of falling into a vegetative state.
For the safety of his target,
Wang Ling usually
reduces his power by half,
only using 50%
of this trick of forgetting.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Master Zhuo,
did you get the answer?
Assassins?
Wang Ling.
Get up and let's go on a date!
It was just a dream.
Wang Ling.
Are you up, Lingling?
Come and have breakfast.
What is he going to do when a girl
is at his door asking for a date?
As a student, he is supposed
to concentrate on his studies.
Neither his dad
nor his mom
is supposed to agree to this.
Come on, finish it up.
It's bad manners to keep a girl waiting.
It's just a date.
Don't be nervous, my son.
Our family's DNA has great charms.
Not nervous?
There was someone
who went on his first date
and my dog scared him.
A normal girl wouldn't have raised
a wheezing dog.
-You said it was lovely.
-It looks like
his parents are happy
-about this relationship.
-He hadn't bitten me when I said that.
SUN RONG: GET UP, LAZY BUG.
CHEN CHAO: WISH YOU HAPPINESS.
GUO HAO: GO FOR IT, CHEN CHAO.
OUR SON'S SPRING SEASON IS HERE
Lingling, look.
These are high-end nutrition pills
Ms. Sun gave your mom.
-A golden pill gift pack.
-Let me try one.
It is so powerful.
One pill would cost me one month's salary.
After using it,
your mom will become extremely beautiful.
Look.
-It's so smooth.
-Don't touch me. It's disgusting.
Keep the girl in good company.
We don't mind if you come home late today.
Your dad and I
will have dinner without you.
WORLD PEACE
It can be confirmed from their eyes
that they are his real parents.
Now that it's happened, just take it easy.
Wang Ling has never been
in anything like this in his life.
You are finally here.
Get in.
He suddenly hopes
that the assassins that
Froggy Two mentioned would show up now.
-Ms. Sun, look here.
The cars of Ms. Sun, heir
to the Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group,
have just left with her
and her supposed boyfriend.
We will update you with the latest news.
TABLOID NEWS
We couldn't find a good chance.
They got away in a car.
Follow them.
Remember. This is your last chance.
Yes.
I'm taking you to a fun place today.
It is called Heavenly Paradise.
It's my family's real estate project
of combining commerce and recreation.
HEAVENLY PARADISE
-Welcome.
Why isn't there anybody in this place?
That's because my grandpa
built this place for me only.
But I told him
that I wanted to spend my time here
with the one I love.
So
this is my first time here.
I should thank you.
I was kidding.
They have this place cleared
for your sake.
-Welcome, miss.
I'll have the greatest fun
I've ever had today.
This place is like my home,
so you don't have to follow me.
I'll be with my friend.
He'll take care of me.
Let's go!
-Come on.
-Let's go.
VISITOR ENTRANCE NUMBER 3
The warm-up is done.
Target is unprepared.
If you don't kill her this time,
you don't have to come back.
CAVE OF THE UNIVERSE
This is the well-known
Prophecy Wall of the Cave of The Universe.
It's said that it was the best work
of a cultivation stonemason
tens of centuries ago.
So if you put your hands
in the fairy's mouth,
the stone wall reinforced
with spiritual force will prophesize
your relationship's future with an echo.
It's said to be very accurate.
I have a friend. The stone wall said
he would fall into danger.
And he really caught on fire
when he was rising to a higher level.
We have found her.
Let's try it.
Come on, Wang Ling!
Wang Ling.
Were…
Were you smiling at me?
What's next on the itinerary?
Thank you for coming. Take care.
What kind of gun is this?
What a huge recoil.
I told you to wait.
This gun is new to us.
We need to get used to it.
It is so hard to use it.
A backward somersault for every shot.
I can't take this.
Wang Ling, do you want a ride
on the Ferris wheel?
Let's get on the Ferris wheel
and I'll ask them
to set off fireworks for us.
What do you think?
That sounds good.
Wang Ling thinks he can have
a moment of quietness on the Ferris wheel.
Wait for me.
This is bad. Master is in trouble.
There are assassins in Heavenly Paradise.
On this clear and blessed day of spring,
Ms. Sun Rong and Mr. Wang Ling
are happily together,
enjoying their evening.
-What are they talking about?
-What are we waiting for?
-Show me some fireworks.
-How embarrassing.
Wang Ling is distracted by the fireworks.
Who are you? What do you want?
Thank you.
We have been busy all night,
but everyone has been ignoring us.
What a failure.
Wang Ling is grateful to the two assassins
for the moment of quietness
they have brought.
Sirs,
you are from Shadow Faction, aren't you?
You have a keen insight.
-It's a pity--
-You fools!
That was her trick.
She is trying to make you talk!
Damn. I almost fell into it.
I'm the one you are after.
Please let my friend go.
So he is your friend.
We thought he was your boyfriend.
Don't worry.
We don't kill anyone
who is not our target.
At this crucial moment,
if I don't persist,
Wang Ling will be in danger.
So…
Wang Ling,
don't do anything foolish.
Get out of here.
Go now!
What do you want to do?
You damned fools!
Don't kill me, Master!
Why am I up in the air?
This is…
The Mercy of Buddha.
Master.
You are amazing.
This is our secret.
Promise me.
This is the first time in Wang Ling's life
that he has used 100% trick of promise.
This way, every memory
in Sun Rong's mind of what happened today
will be sealed up forever as a secret
and not erased.
Fireworks burst in the sky.
Love-filled hearts
ripple through the night.
We wish the new couple
to be united forever
until the end of time.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE