The assassination failed.
Sun Rong is still alive, safe, and sound.
My client is very unhappy.
Our men
were blasted with the Mercy of Buddha
and you don't even know who did it.
Boss, according to our intelligence,
she may have a very strong
and powerful man to protect her.
That's why our men--
ACE
Over the past hundreds of years,
Shadow Faction has had 100% success
to stay on the top of this trade.
This incident
is a huge humiliation for us.
Issue a Shadow Kill Order.
Boss,
the Shadow Kill Order is still
in Primary Phase.
-It's…
-You don't understand, do you?
-Yes, Boss. We're on it.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
SUPER BODYGUARD, FORCE VALUE 37,824
ARTISTIC BODYGUARD, FORCE VALUE 2,019
The target is right on the street.
We might as well shoot her directly
with a machine gun.
Boss,
I'm afraid that would have
a negative social influence.
Isn't this the guy who went
on a date with her yesterday?
WANG LING, FORCE VALUE: 5, HARMLESS
Wang Ling!
-From the way Sun Rong behaves,
-Wang Ling.
the trick of promise last night
was effective.
Hey, you brat.
You had a date with Sun Rong yesterday.
That was a stroke of luck.
This hand
touched her, right?
Good morning, Wang Ling.
We…
didn't do anything wrong, did we?
Why do you ask, Guo Hao?
Because we are surrounded
by your bodyguards!
Sun Rong,
the assassins who tried to kill you
in Heavenly Paradise are still active.
We'll put you
under special protection today.
Assassins?
Wang Ling and I were having fun
in Heavenly Paradise.
We didn't see any assassins at all.
The trick of promise yesterday
was effective.
Wang Ling feels relieved.
That's because
I found them first.
Master Zhuo.
YESTERDAY NIGHT
Are you all right, miss?
The hostage is safe now.
All units, get ready to escort her.
Well, it's time for me to go.
WORLD PEACE
Ms. Sun Rong is safe now.
Rest assured, Master.
Your Mercy of Buddha
really impressed me.
Zhuo Yi.
Yes, Master.
Remember.
It is you
who got rid of the assassins.
Yesterday, I secretly got rid
of the assassins
that were trying to kill Ms. Sun Rong.
You are Master Zhuo indeed!
It looks like
the 50% trick of forgetting yesterday
was effective too.
But the problem is,
this enraged them at the same time.
Isn't this Shadow Faction's
Shadow Kill Order?
It is said that whoever receives
such an order
won't be able to see the sun the next day.
Is this true?
Is somebody trying to kill me?
So it was Zhuo Yi who sabotaged my plan.
So today,
I designed special security precautions.
-Left, right.
IMMORTAL
I'm only one minute late.
It doesn't have to be like this.
Areas outside the gate are taken over
by the Armored Cruise Troop,
which is directly under
the Cultivation Council.
OPERATION: PROTECT SUN RONG
Come with me, please.
Areas between the enclosing walls
and the building
are covered by
the school's security guards.
They are all strong young men
retired from the Cultivation Army.
Many of them have experience
in fighting demons and monsters.
I didn't know our school's security guards
were so powerful.
Besides the security guards
and the Cruise Troop,
inside the building,
we have powerful aids.
Aids?
-Good morning, miss.
Aren't they the bodyguards
from downstairs?
That's right, Ms. Sun.
I've contacted your dad.
The bodyguards he has chosen for you
are all in Golden Pill Phase and above.
They will patrol the corridors today.
In order not to bother other students…
SEAL
…Ms. Sun Rong,
I suggest you stay in Mr. Wang's office.
I have deployed
a protective force field in this room,
making it secure against any attack.
Master Zhuo is outstanding
in making force fields.
The evil-binding force field
that sealed Giant Frog
is the excellent work of Master Zhuo.
With these four tight protective circles,
no one can get in,
not even a fly.
Master Zhuo,
a fly.
Threat eliminated.
The Seven-Star Squad?
That's right.
To prevent distant snipers
or aerial attacks,
I've invited the Seven-Star Squad
to take care
of defense and surveillance
from up in the air.
Yes, it's all thanks
to the alumnus, Zhuo Yi.
This is the tightest protection ever
since this school was established.
You call this tight?
I saw them all as soon
as they were deployed.
Convey the information to the frontline.
The Armored Cruise at the gate
is almost nonexistent.
With a simple trick of earth tunnel,
I bypassed it.
Next…
Where did this haystack come from?
Xu Feng, the third member
of the Hammer Team.
A late Golden Pill Phase Red Ribbon
from the Shadow Faction.
A master assassin.
Xu Ying,
I've cleared the yard.
-You can enter the building now.
-All right, Xu Feng.
Be careful.
You've been spotted.
We don't need so many Armored Cruisers
at the gate now.
-Don't be afraid, students.
-Send some to help the central lobby.
As long as Master Zhuo and I are here,
-That's right. A few will be enough.
-nobody can hurt you.
What…
CLASS ELITE GROUP
They say that Wang Ling and Ms. Sun Rong
had a date in Heavenly Paradise yesterday
and ran into two assassins.
I also heard that Master Zhuo
was in Heavenly Paradise.
So I guess
it was Master Zhuo who saved the couple.
SHY
I'm in Mr. Wang's office now.
The couple and Master Zhuo
are within 5 m from me.
There are assassins indeed.
I saw on the screen that
many security guards had been knocked out.
They are super fast.
My goodness. It's true?
I'm scared out of my wits.
Aren't you scared, Chen Chao?
Why should I? I'll protect them.
WANG LING
What a surprise!
Force Value Five is alive!
Don't worry, Wang Ling.
Chen Chao is right.
I will protect you too.
WANG ZUKANG:
PLEASE KEEP THIS A SECRET
I don't mind you showing love,
but please keep this a secret.
-Yes, sir.
Attention.
The security guards in the yard
are all down.
I've sent the Armored Cruise
to back you up.
You must hold out.
We are all Golden Pill Phase elites,
different from those
Foundation Phase security guards.
This is bad. It's a toxic gas!
Flying…
Meteor Hammer!
Xu Ying, the second member
of the Hammer Team.
Also, a late Golden Pill Phase Red Ribbon.
An expert in toxics.
Xu Ying,
we are supposed to be
on a stealth mission.
If we finish them all,
no one will know that we are here.
But these Cruisers are coming for me!
I'll leave them to you, Xu Feng.
Hey!
Xu Ying!
Who is so daring to attack me covertly?
Songhai Faction 60 Cultivation School.
A Primary Phase instructor,
Wang Zukang.
CHEN, WANG, GUO, SUN, ZHUO
All right.
There are only four students
and Zhuo Yi in the office now.
That is for sure,
right, Xu Jian?
Leave it to me, Boss.
I've been accumulating my force
on the roof for quite some time.
Even the Seven-Star Squad didn't find me.
Xu Jian, the leader of the Hammer Team.
He's also known as Hammer Xu.
A late Golden Pill Phase Red Ribbon King.
His trick of invisibility
can conceal his existence.
His huge hammer is a magical weapon
with enormous powers.
Actually, Xu Ying and Xu Feng's attacks
were only diversions.
After I have finished
accumulating my force,
any magic formation,
no matter how powerful it is,
I'll smash to pieces.
You have collected all crispy noodles
of the Commemorative Edition.
Congratulations. You received a Gift Pack.
Goudong Customer Service
kindly reminds you
that the gift will be delivered to you
by drone within 15 minutes.
Mr. Wang has started his battle.
The old guy is fighting him personally.
Can a fat man like him still fight?
Does this rubbish school
think I am not strong enough
so they use a Golden Pill Phase
like you as a guard?
Young man,
mind your manners.
Who are you to lecture me?
Watch this!
Grow!
-Mr. Wang.
Did you see that?
In front of my Thunder Hammer,
you have no way to escape.
Shadow Faction guys
are getting more and more disappointing.
You even buy these mass-produced toys
online as your magical weapons.
He is awesome.
I thought he taught history.
A message from Goudong Express.
Your order is being delivered.
Young man,
surrender yourself.
Burst.
How could you use such a sinister means
like Toxic Burst in school?
Goodbye, old man!
I've done my part.
Wait for Xu Jian--
I'm sorry. I'm in a hurry.
Wang Ling.
Don't worry.
Wang Ling has gone to pick up his package.
You are the target of the Shadow Faction,
so don't worry about him.
What just happened?
Young man,
class is not over yet.
Why are you leaving early?
Damn. Xu Ying is down.
How are you, Xu Feng?
Xu Ying is so useless.
Xu Jian,
I have handled the Armored Cruisers
in the central lobby.
Wait.
It's so soft.
Puppy.
What a naughty puppy.
Wait.
The puppy has sucked my spiritual force.
Wait a minute.
Not only my spiritual force,
but also my life essence.
The spiritual force of someone
in the Golden Pill Phase is so nutritious.
This is bad. I have to get out of here.
Damn it.
I'm the only one left.
Don't worry.
I'm almost done with force accumulation.
With my trick of invisibility,
no one on campus can find me.
So here you are.
Stop.
Isn't he one of the students?
I'm sorry.
I've come to pick up my package.
It's clear, sir.
Just ordinary crispy noodles inside.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Your package has been delivered
within eight minutes.
Maybe I was too sensitive.
He was talking about the package.
No,
I meant you.
I'm sorry.
I knocked your friend to the ground.
I'm sorry to tell you
that your assassination plan
has failed.
This is bad!
There's a high-energy reaction above.
To hell with the assassination.
To hell with the Faction's rules.
This is a freak
who can see through my invisibility.
He mustn't be spared!
He is only in the Primary Phase.
How can he have
such a terrible spiritual force?
All assassins have been eliminated.
-Calm down, Boss!
-Boss!
Calm down!
Master!
You are indeed my master.
You beat an assassin
who used a magical weapon.
No.
You did it.
Young man,
try to reform yourself in there.
Somebody help me out of here.
Master Zhuo.
You are awesome.
You beat an assassin
who used a magical weapon.
It's a shame
that I was a bit too late.
-Wang Ling!
Today, Songhai Faction 60 was attacked
by assassins sent by Shadow Faction.
Coincidentally,
Joint Honorary Master Zhuo Yi
of the Cultivation School League
was on campus to do research.
Master Zhuo Yi eliminated
the assassins all by himself.
We will follow up on the case
and bring you the most objective report.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE