ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
Wang Ling is on sick leave.
-In the previous episode,
-He mustn't be spared.
the last hit of
the Shadow Faction's Xu Jian
was bounced back
by Wang Ling's spiritual force.
-Because of this suicidal action,
-He's only
-a Primary Phase.
-Xu Jian fell.
As a low-profile hero,
-Wang Ling pretended to be badly hurt
-It's a shame
-that I was a bit late.
-and gave the credit
to Master Zhuo Yi.
Wang Ling.
-Wang Ling, are you all right?
-Sun Rong didn't know what happened,
-Wang Ling!
-so she was very worried.
She summoned the best medical experts
and constructed a private healing cabin.
An all-immersion experience.
Valuable medicines shower on him
automatically every hour.
It is said to be able
to connect the meridians
as well as boosting the vital spirits.
It's time for breakfast, Lingling.
Okay.
How long are you going to play sick?
It has been over ten days.
Tell them tomorrow
that you have recovered.
Go back to school the day after tomorrow.
Good morning, Mr. Wang.
Lingling,
your friends are here.
-Hello, Mrs. Wang.
Wang Ling,
we are here on behalf of the school.
Thank you for coming.
You don't have to buy these things.
Take your time.
We are going to prepare
some snacks and tea.
-Thank you, Mrs. Wang.
How is it? Are you feeling better?
You are still lying in bed.
Look at this.
It's my pet, Birdie Two.
Camel.
-Camel.
-Damn parrot.
Who would want such an ugly bird as a pet?
It's foolishly cute. It's kind of lovely.
Isn't it, Wang Ling?
Right.
On second thought,
there is some resemblance!
Oh no!
I left Froggy Two at the door.
Where did this green-haired dog come from?
Ms. Sun,
thank you for taking care
of Lingling at school.
Now is the chance
to build my relationship with her!
Mrs. Wang,
these are the ultimate elixirs
-produced by my family's group.
-Take all of them?
-They will help Wang Ling recover.
-I'm afraid he will have nosebleeds.
And these are the same nutrition pills
as I gave you last time.
This is a chicken blood tonic injection.
With this,
Wang Ling will be fully recovered.
All right,
I'll just leave you to yourselves.
Call me if you need anything.
Entertain them well, Lingling.
Be nice to Sun Rong.
Sun Rong seems different than usual.
Wang Ling should feel the difference.
Out of my way.
Are you feeling better, Wang Ling?
You were lying on the ground that day.
You were badly hurt.
I was so worried.
I feel much better.
Sun Rong was so scared.
She even called her family's chopper
to help you.
When Wang Ling was playing dead,
he saw clearly
how Sun Rong was concerned about him.
Let's take
this chicken blood tonic injection now.
Combined with spiritual power perfusion,
it will do miracles to your recovery.
The so-called spiritual power perfusion
means that a cultivator perfuses
his spiritual power into someone else
to help the injured recover.
By the way, Wang Ling,
I almost forgot.
When you visit Wang Ling,
take this to him.
The annual Spiritual Power Test.
Nobody is to be left out.
Mr. Wang asked us to bring it to you.
Spiritual Power Tests
take a lot of vital spirits.
You don't have to do it
if you don't feel well, Wang Ling.
Give him the injection now, Sun Rong,
and see if he gets better.
It looks like it's the only choice.
Wang Ling doesn't want
to take the injection,
let alone the spiritual power infusion.
Wait a minute.
I feel much better these days.
I was going to tell you
that I'm going back to school
the day after tomorrow.
Aren't those my lines?
Look. This is it.
We waited for you
to take the test with us.
Wang Ling,
after seeing you run on the schoolyard,
I knew that
you had been concealing your true power.
It doesn't matter.
I'll start with my poor little power.
Look.
This is how you do it.
Concentrate all your spiritual force
into a sphere.
And then…
Burst!
The diameter of my force sphere
corresponds to a Force Value around 600.
This is not much different
from the value in the entrance test.
Why don't they just use that value?
Why are they testing it again?
You are wrong, Guo Hao.
This is a force
that appears outside your body.
Concentrating the spiritual power
and visualizing it outside the body.
This is not something
an ordinary cultivator can do.
It takes persistent training
because this means you can show
your spiritual power in any shape.
Anyway,
only when you can visualize your power,
will you be a true cultivator.
SUPER
At this moment,
countless students all over the country
are trying to leap over the bar
that Wang Ling simply ignores.
Liang Zheng, it's your turn.
Liang Zheng, 1,950 points.
Is Liang Zheng
not feeling well these days?
Hush.
You know he took a slap
from Tang Jingze during practice.
I'm the next one in the sequence.
Xiaobei, I'm counting on you.
FIRST PLACE:
SONGHAI FACTION 59, TANG JINGZE
This score
is frightening!
He's awesome.
-It must have broken the record
-He's indeed our chairman.
-that Master Zhuo Yi set 10 years ago.
-Faction 59 will surely win
-in the Spiritual Sword Competition.
-Almighty Tang Jingze.
It's over 300 points higher
than second place.
-Faction 59 will win!
-Faction 59 lives!
-Almighty Tang Jingze.
-He's amazing! Faction 59 will win!
-Faction 59 will win!
-Faction 59 lives!
SONGHAI FACTION 60, GUO HAO,
POWER SHOW SCORE: 176
Don't stop me. Let me jump off here.
Calm down. Listen to me.
Look at your sphere. It's almost there.
You should have spent your time
on practices,
not on elixirs.
I had better skip the test.
I don't want to break things.
Sun Rong,
you are more talented
than ordinary people.
And you were born into a rich family,
-but you scored only 2,019 points
-But you scored only 2,019 points
-on the entrance test.
-Your power sphere can only be this big.
All right. I'll just give it a try.
How can it be so big?
Sun Rong,
your power sphere is enormous!
-Faction 59 will win!
-Somebody from Faction 60 is on the list.
-Faction 59 lives!
Isn't she the legendary genius girl?
The daughter of
the Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group?
Interesting.
-Sun Rong's ranked second
-in the top ten list.
-Wang Ling.
-It's your turn.
Although I didn't make any preparations,
I should be able to sneak through it
with a leak of my spiritual force.
Wang Ling,
how is your health condition?
I'm fine.
This little force should do it.
I should have allowed them
to perform the power infusion.
-It's good that the force spillover
-It's so strong!
caused the equipment to malfunction.
However,
I must relocate it somewhere.
WANG LING, POWER SHOW TEST: NULL
Wang Ling,
where is your power sphere?
What does "null" mean?
Does it mean zero points?
I told you Wang Ling
has not recovered yet.
Wait a minute.
It…
FIRST PLACE:
SONGHAI FACTION 60, WANG LING
What does "null" mean?
What is going on?
I've never heard of this "Wang Ling."
Is there a bug in the system?
Shall I check it out?
It might be a system failure.
All right.
Wang Ling didn't expect that
even though he launched
his power sphere into outer space,
it was still detected by the wristband.
This should be
a display error.
Wang Ling, don't try to cover it anymore.
Show us your true power
as the top scorer of the country.
I was kidding. Don't be so scared.
-It feels like a danger to him
-The top of the country is in our school?
to be at the top of the list.
It's time to go, Wang Ling. Goodbye.
-See you, Wang Ling.
-Bye.
My score is too low.
I want to hack into the system
and alter it.
You shouldn't do that.
You should act honorably
even if you got a score of zero.
HAI HOUR
Wang Ling,
I didn't think
a well-behaved student like you
would want to hack into the ranking system
of the Cultivation Council School League.
Now…
It's midnight!
This is the right time
to be connected to the mainframe
of the Cultivation Council.
To hack into the system,
I must have the login password.
Out of my way.
I'll draw a password-grabbing formation.
All assets assemble at noon.
I must have it. Hot.
HEAVEN, EARTH
The formation is done.
Next, I'll grab the password.
LEFT UP
If I succeed,
the password will appear on this amulet.
Don't move.
You must stick to the demand position.
The one in the demand position
needs to do nothing
but name his demand.
That'll conform to cosmic laws.
DEMAND
You just said you want your score changed
to 175 points, right?
I'm in.
I don't see anything wrong
with the system.
Is Wang Ling's ranking normal?
I don't know.
The system ranks him at the top,
but I can't retrieve his score data.
How can that be?
It seems to have
spilled over.
"Spilled over"?
The ranking module of the system
was written
with the most primitive polarity code.
I'll see if I can force it to read.
All right.
I have the password.
How can this be?
Why is the password still hidden?
This is unscientific.
What a damned formation.
I took the risk of getting bald to use it.
Why is it not working?
GUIDE FOR HACKING AMULET
LOG IN SUCCESSFUL
The password is just eight stars.
There is another hacker.
Converted into polarity code, 175 will be
heaven, earth, heaven, earth,
heaven, heaven, heaven, heaven,
written as 10101111.
Do you want your name
written on the list too?
Now, if I can find where it is stored…
Who is this hacker?
He is foolish, clumsy,
and making many changes.
He is about to trigger the alarm.
He will get us involved.
If we are caught,
we will be expelled from our school.
SECOND PLACE:
SONGHAI FACTION 59, TANG JINGZE
"Tang Jingze"?
Is this the guy who was so arrogant
-You are awesome.
-at the immortal cram school?
They say he passed the exam
and entered the famous Faction 59 School.
Let's see if you are still arrogant.
We don't have enough time.
This idiot is rewriting the database.
I seem to have triggered the alarm!
Damn it.
-I must quit now.
-I must leave quickly.
That was close. They almost got me.
Did they catch you?
No.
You didn't change the score.
Did you leave any trace?
Of course not. I'm an expert.
SONGHAI FACTION 59, TANG BIRDIE TWO
Tang Jingze,
the internal practice is about to…
What is going on?
How can a nobody
rank higher than Tang Jingze?
Changing your name now
does mean a lot.
NATIONAL SENIOR PHASE CULTIVATION
SCHOOL POWER SHOW TEST TOP TEN
By the way,
at the Sword Competition next month,
if we have the chance,
we might meet those two from Faction 60.
No,
we will definitely meet them.
When the time comes,
I'll see what they've got.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE