ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
The results of the National Senior Phase
Cultivation School Power Show Test
have been announced.
Wang Ling ranked first?
Is there a problem with the system?
You've been teaching
Class Elite for quite a while.
What do you think, Ms. Pan?
Wang Ling is a little below average
in the class.
He's usually quite silent.
How did he rank first nationally
all of a sudden?
We have two students
on the top ten list this time,
but that's where the problem lies.
SONGHAI FACTION 60
VS SONGHAI FACTION 59
Faction 59?
Why are we competing with
one of the best in the first round?
Because this time, Sun Rong and Wang Ling
raised our average score.
In the past 100 years,
we had 24 contests with Faction 59.
The results
were 23 losses and 1 draw.
That's right.
The only draw we had was ten years ago
and that was because we had a genius,
Master Zhuo.
I have a feeling that
this competition will be very interesting
and we might have a surprising result.
Anyway, let's decide on
our participants first.
Why are you two so calm about this?
By the way,
who is this Tang Birdie Two
that ranked second?
Dear audience,
I'm sure you are just as excited about
this year's National Senior Phase
Sword Competition as we are.
Now, I'm in the training field
of Songhai Faction 59.
As you can see,
the capabilities of their students
are on par with professional standards.
They are indeed
one of the most favored to win this year.
Big Dipper Sword Formation,
action!
In the center of the sword formation
is the chairman of their Student Union,
the ace of Faction 59,
Tang Birdie Two.
TANG BIRDIE TWO, MALE, 16 YEARS OLD
Now, let me ask him a few questions.
Tang Birdie Two,
what preparations have you made
for this competition?
To prepare for this annual competition,
our students have undergone
extremely tough training for a month.
They go through this dull,
but intensive training again and again
in order to do their best
for the competition.
High-level students
who are about to graduate
are looking forward to
the last major battle they have at school.
The vigorous spirit of Faction 59
will be passed down to the new students.
It is a great honor to fight
side by side with them.
Anyway, we will do our best.
This is also the highest respect
we can pay to our rivals.
Then your rivals,
the students from Songhai's Faction 60,
do you have anything to say to them?
I noticed that the princess
of the Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group
is a genius girl.
She got an outstanding score
for the Power Show Test.
I hope at the Sword Competition,
I can see her family's remarkable power.
During the Power Show Test,
there was Wang Ling
from Faction 60 who ranked first.
Of course,
they say it was because
of a bug in the system.
I was wondering if you would like to…
I wish him all the best
in his immortal practice.
Wang Ling? Who is that?
What?
Master Zhuo, Mr. Wang,
are you serious?
Are all of the participants
freshmen and in Level 1?
I'm sure you still remember, Ms. Pan,
that we didn't appear
in the group stage last year.
Our school doesn't have
quality enrolments.
I don't see a force value higher than
1,000 even among the higher levels.
Sun Rong of Level 1 is a genius indeed,
but the other three…
Ms. Pan,
I have confidence
in the quality of your teaching.
But…
I took the time
for their body-building classes
to give them lessons on theories.
According to the rules
of the Sword Competition…
WANG LING, SUN RONG
…each team must have
at least five members.
But we have only
four students on our list.
I've discussed this with Master Zhuo.
Here is the fifth member.
But it's a dog!
Ms. Pan, please don't discriminate
against a spiritual beast.
There are precedents for animals
in the competition.
The team that won the championship in 3497
from a senior phase school
had a fox as a member.
But that nine-tailed fox was an
exchange student from Spiritual World.
Besides, she transformed into a human!
Froggy Two can change into a human
if necessary.
I used the trick of transformation on him.
It shouldn't be a problem now.
This looks more like it.
-My goodness!
-Is this supposed to be
the demon king's face?
All right. It doesn't matter
if he isn't in human form.
It's not in the rules.
But he didn't participate
in the Power Show Test.
He isn't qualified for the competition.
MAKE-UP EXAM
Make-up Exam sequence has been initiated.
Please input the student's information
for the Make-up Exam.
My goodness.
You've planned all of it, haven't you?
Froggy Two should have a score of 5,000.
If you win this time,
I'll consider removing the seal on you.
SECOND PLACE: FROGGY TWO
NATIONAL SENIOR PHASE CULTIVATION
SCHOOL POWER SHOW TEST TOP TEN
Tang Birdie Two. No.
Tang Jingze.
There is another one whose spiritual force
is higher than yours.
FROGGY TWO, FACTION 60,
SPIRITUAL FORCE: 5,000
Hey! And it's a dog!
Good.
Very good.
You are forcing me to do it.
So it is decided then.
Okay.
After school, I'll make a WeChat group
to let them know about it quietly.
So you do know
it's something shameful after all.
Ms. Pan.
We wanted to keep our strategy a secret.
SONGHAI FACTION 60 CULTIVATION SCHOOL
Wang Ling and everybody, see you tomorrow.
Bye.
Recently, I bought a video game
called Spiritual Beast Hunter.
The beasts in it are this big.
I fought one of them four times
before I got over it.
SONGHAI NOODLES
Sir, I want a bowl of extra spicy noodles
with an egg.
SUPER, CHEN
SPIRITUAL BEAST HUNTER
THE CHOSEN ONE IN THE CULTIVATION WORLD
BY KU XUAN
That's it for today.
I'm going to leave now.
I love you.
WELCOME TO RONGRONG THE RABBIT'S
LIVE BROADCAST
If I can't show my face,
my popularity won't go up.
That's it for today.
I'm going to leave now.
CREATE A NEW CHAT
Sun Rong.
Wang Ling.
Guo Hao.
Chen Chao.
Froggy Two. The five of you.
Congratulations. You have been chosen
by the school
to participate in year 4396's
National Senior Phase Sword Competition.
What?
Dad.
ELITE
I made it!
That's it for today.
I'm going to leave now.
Please get your spiritual sword ready
within three days.
SUPER, CHEN
There is no use for this thing now.
This sword is called Li Chao.
My son, take the sword.
Yes, Dad!
My son, the Chen family is proud of you.
Dad.
From now on, use this sword
to chop the firewood.
VIEW FULL IMAGE
This sword is called Li Chao.
My dad forged it when I was born.
It's called Li Chao?
It matches your name perfectly.
CONGRATULATIONS! WE ARE A TEAM!
We can judge from the patina…
-The goddess is giving out a red envelope!
-that the sword has been
very well maintained by Chen Chao.
It's because Wang Ling
is also on the list.
Although I have long been engaged
with the sword,
-and I have been worshipping it
-Wang Ling, say something.
at home all the time, unfortunately,
Li Chao hasn't produced
a sword spirit so far.
You cannot produce
a sword spirit overnight.
Now that Chen Chao is so persistent,
he will achieve it very soon.
Chen Chao has shown his spiritual sword.
Who else?
FACTION 60 SWORD COMPETITION
SCHOOL TEAM
This sword was forged
with the teeth of Night Devil Tiger,
a Level 3 spiritual beast,
as the main ingredient.
It has been with me for eight years.
No spiritual sword
has been produced either.
Guo Hao,
you are also suffering from the pain.
I didn't expect that
these Level 1 new students
would have their own spiritual swords.
Sun Rong, do you have a spiritual sword?
SUN RONG JOINS THE CHAT
Mr. Wang, everyone,
and Wang Ling, good evening.
LIVE
This is my spiritual sword.
It is called Ocean.
This blue color is the corona
of the sword spirit.
Sun Rong has produced a sword spirit.
Sun Rong may have
a favorable family background,
but since her sword shines so brightly,
it means that she must have spent
a lot of effort
to foster a mutual understanding.
WHAT A LUXURIOUS SWORD!
Thank you for your praises.
In case the sword is damaged in battle,
my family forged 13 of them.
Why are you all silent?
A BIT SPICY, MEDIUM SPICY,
SPICY, EXTRA SPICY
Right, Wang Ling and Froggy Two.
Do you have spiritual swords?
Froggy Two is a dog, Mr. Wang.
I'm afraid he doesn't have one.
Sword of Sky.
You beat me there.
To produce a sword spirit,
you have to be patient.
In the beginning, the body of
a sword spirit is in a chaotic state.
After enough effort,
it will concentrate into a solid body.
The initial sword spirit may take
the form of a small beast
or a human.
Then it will upgrade and evolve,
and its intelligence will develop too.
The sword spirits of some
unbelievable cultivators
even have the ability to think.
Is that so? Please tell us more.
Next semester, you will be given
fundamental sword-related lessons.
The sword lessons you are taking now
are all about the maintenance
of spiritual swords.
In advanced sword lessons, you will learn
about flying and fighting with swords.
But that will have to wait
until you go to schools
of higher phases.
What you need to do now
is to nourish the passion between
you and your spiritual swords
and try to produce a sword spirit
before your lessons come to an end.
I'll save these to My Favorites.
"18 tips for producing a sword spirit."
Did we forget something?
Right. Wang Ling, where is your sword?
Don't you want to show it to us?
Where is your sword, Wang Ling?
Do you have a sword?
WORLD PEACE, LITTLE RACCOON
Yes.
SONGHAI FACTION 59 CULTIVATION SCHOOL
Tang Jingze,
are the spiritual swords ready?
I've asked them to hand in their swords
to be taken care of
and I've personally checked them.
But on this list,
there are only four people.
Ms. Xie, that is because the fifth member
is that man.
What?
Tang Jingze, do you really want
to start using that man?
Aren't you worried about the consequences
if you put him in the competition?
We can't afford to lose this year!
So I'll have to rely
on the power of that man.
I got it.
I'll give you a free hand
with everything this time.
Thank you.
I will not allow Faction 60 to win.
If we are going to use that man,
Faction 60 will have no chance of winning.
Who is that man anyway?
He Bufeng,
that is the current situation.
SIXTY
He wanted me to take part
in the Sword Competition.
Does the council know about this?
Yes, He Bufeng.
Interesting.
I'd like to see
what kind of a man he is
that made Ms. Xie want to use me.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE