ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
In the last episode,
Faction 60 is going to take part
in this year's Sword Competition.
Where is your sword, Wang Ling?
No one noticed
that he didn't want to take part
in the competition.
Wang Ling worried that if he showed
his true power at the competition,
it would cause panic.
However,
his friends and instructors
take this competition very seriously.
VIEW FULL IMAGE
This sword is called Li Chao.
My dad forged it when I was born.
This sword was forged
with the teeth of Night Devil Tiger,
a Level 3 spiritual beast,
as the main ingredient.
It has been with me for eight years.
LIVE
This is my spiritual sword.
It is called Ocean.
FACTION 60 SWORD COMPETITION
SCHOOL TEAM
Sword of Sky.
If I just show my sword to them,
it wouldn't be a problem, would it?
Darling, this anti-aging agent
is on sale again.
Damn. It's so expensive
even after the discount.
Do you want me to buy it or not?
All right. Use my credit card.
An explosion occurred
at the Spiritual Force Chemical Plant
in this city recently.
Experts remind us again
that no magic wares
of high spiritual force density
should be brought close
to spiritual figures.
IMMORTAL ART LABORATORY
PROFESSIONAL OPERATIONS
DO NOT IMITATE
Breaking news.
According to sources,
the Cultivation Council's
Armored Cruise Troop
surrounded the Shadow Faction's
headquarters building earlier today.
This is the first time in history
that its lair has been found.
If you want to go into the headquarters,
you must go through me first.
Damn you!
IMMORTAL
This way. Come with me.
So far, the lower levels of the building
have been cleared.
There is resistance only
on the few upper levels.
BILI FRONT
-What happened?
-Master Zhuo,
-please tell us what is going on.
-Master Zhuo, please tell us something.
Master Zhuo, please tell us something.
Master Zhuo, do you think it's safe now?
In the past, I had two encounters
with Shadow Faction.
I foiled their plans each time.
I believe it is no exception this time.
The leader of Shadow Faction,
I look forward to meeting you again.
What a fool.
That was breaking news.
We will follow up with their actions
and bring you the latest news.
Where is my sword?
-Which sword?
Lingling, be careful
when climbing the ladder.
Don't fall off and smash things.
Wang Ling,
we're going to Faction 59 tomorrow
to familiarize ourselves with the venue.
Is your spiritual sword ready?
It has been ten years.
How are…
IN THE HOUSE
Is this Wang Ling's sword?
It's so small.
It's even smaller than that of a kid.
That's right.
I think it's quite cute.
What? Does she like
a spiritual sword like that?
What strong power it has.
Hey.
Are you all ready?
Songhai Faction 60
Spiritual Sword Team is ready.
We can go at any moment.
That's very good.
The competition will last for five days,
so we need to stay there for a few nights.
Wang Ling,
you don't bring anything
for that purpose, do you?
SIXTY
This is because
Wang Ling didn't intend to take part
in the competition in the first place.
He plans to pretend that his stomach hurts
as soon as he arrives at Faction 59.
That way,
he can avoid showing up
in the competition.
It's just five days.
-I can manage.
-Here.
Take mine, Wang Ling.
We are like brothers.
-Don't be shy.
-No, thank you.
Here comes the bus.
Get on board, everybody.
Okay, I got it.
Something unexpected just happened.
I'm afraid I can't go with you now.
Master, all the best.
Are you sure it is her?
Yes, I'm sure.
We found Shadow Faction's
official seal on her.
The leader of Shadow Faction,
we meet again.
Master Zhuo,
I've had a small Thunder Pearl
specially prepared for you.
Its power
is enough to melt every one
of the cells of a senior cultivator.
Follow the school bus in front.
Master Zhuo,
the entire plan was set up for you,
from the tip-off on Shadow Faction's
headquarters to your breaking in,
and taking away the gift prepared for you.
You jeopardized our plan twice.
This time, you are finished.
As for the target, Ms. Sun Rong,
I will take her down personally.
Without Zhuo Yi,
these cute little things
can't do anything.
We agreed yesterday.
A sword spirit can frighten
an ordinary cultivator,
so don't come out tomorrow.
Staying unseen for 100 years
wouldn't be a problem for you, would it?
Welcome, Faction 60 Spiritual Sword Team.
This is really bad.
Ms. Pan Shengcong
and Faction 59's Ms. Xie
used to be close friends and roommates.
But now,
they are rivals.
It has been a long time, Ms. Pan.
There is such a beautiful girl
on your team this time.
So this is the girl from
the Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group.
The lady must have made a great
contribution to Faction 60's poor budget.
I'm sorry, a slip of the tongue.
You must have forgotten, Ms. Xie.
Back then, you filed a request
to the General Administration
to enroll Sun Rong.
Do you remember it now?
It's pity that Sun Rong refused
to go to your school.
She chose to come to Faction 60.
She has her own aspirations.
A wise bird chooses
the best tree to stay in.
I know this one.
I saw him a couple of times
on the television.
Bullying schoolmates.
Cheating in examinations. Abusing animals.
I remember he even received
a public security penalty.
PUBLIC SECURITY PENALTY
One may thrive in one place,
but may just grow rotten in another.
At this moment, Wang Ling is anxious.
He just can't find a chance
to pretend to have a stomachache.
Look. Ms. Xie is going to make a big move.
Could it be…
SONGHAI FACTION 59 CULTIVATION SCHOOL
Here is my chance.
Faction 60 is so impressive.
I just used my Grand Testing Trick
and found a student with a force value
of five on your team.
Does this mean you despise Faction 59
or you are ready to acknowledge defeat?
-Wang Ling.
-Wang Ling!
-What happened to you?
-Are you all right?
-Wang Ling, what's wrong? Are you okay?
-How do you feel, Wang Ling?
-What a mess.
I'm going to finish them all.
Master, it's breaking.
What are you talking about?
Your amulet.
That background music again!
What?
Is there someone with a high level around?
Darling,
my eyelids are twitching
all the time today.
Is it resonance?
That's right.
This is the resonance
of the peach wood sword,
which has stimulated
the counterfeit amulet.
And now,
Ms. Xie's spiritual force impulses.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I wanted to tell you on the bus,
but you forced me back.
The amulet loses its effect
sooner than expected,
-so his great spiritual force is released.
-Wang Ling.
If he doesn't take
-a low-power pill in time,
-Wang Ling.
-Wang Ling will be in a state
-of extreme instability.
-Wang Ling. Are you all right?
Are you sure it was
the Grand Testing Trick that you used?
This student is really good at acting.
He is in such a critical condition.
Do you call this acting?
Tang Jingze, did you have someone do this?
Was it him?
Did he do this?
SONGHAI FACTION 59 CULTIVATION SCHOOL
Boss, we failed.
Thank goodness I acted quickly.
You are so cruel, Boss.
-Wang Ling! Wang Ling, wake up!
-The target cares so much about
-that Force Value Five.
-Wang Ling!
It doesn't matter.
I have a new plan.
Retreat now.
Although something unexpected happened,
Wang Ling's plan
is working for now.
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE