ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE
Was it him?
Did he do this?
This spiritual force shock was terrible.
Ms. Sun Rong,
do you remember me?
I'm Tang Jingze. We went to
the cultivation cram school together.
Get out of my way.
I'm now the chairman
of Faction 59's Student Union.
If you don't mind--
I said
get out of my way!
Let me introduce you
to the secretary of the Student Union,
Yisha Bei.
Sun Rong.
SONGHAI FACTION 59 CULTIVATION SCHOOL
Do you want to fight? Come on.
LEARN
Do you know why I decided
to go to Faction 60?
Because there are scumbags
like you in Faction 59.
No wonder you are so cold to me.
You already have someone you care for.
Don't worry.
Wang Ling will be safe in Faction 59.
I swear on my name.
Fire!
Get out of the way.
Don't just stand there.
Take him to the medical room.
-Yes.
What happened?
Did he go overboard?
How can you treat someone
so cruelly like that?
You won't get away with it!
Mr. Wang.
Calm down, everyone.
Use your sword only in the competition.
Ms. Xie, you'd better
manage your students!
I'm sorry, Ms. Xie. It was my fault.
Now let's go to the gym
and talk about the competition.
That lunatic…
He used such a dirty means.
But on the bright side,
one of them is incapacitated
before the competition.
MEDICAL ROOM
What's wrong with him?
He went overboard.
He doesn't seem to have heartbeats.
Where is the patient
who needs emergency treatment?
He's right here.
Where is he?
Master,
are you sure you're all right?
I'm feeling awful.
Back then,
Wang Ling used the trick of flash,
which caused further damage to his amulet.
If he uses his spiritual force
a few more times,
it will burst out and induce a calamity
that will destroy the world.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Hey, son. What is it?
What?
Your seal is breaking?
Yes, I'm at Faction 59.
I'll sneak out and wait for you.
Wang Ling decides to find a way
to sneak out of Faction 59
and meet with his dad to get the amulet.
With the new amulet in place
before it bursts,
the world will be saved.
What a big gym.
This is impressive.
Rubes.
First, welcome people from Faction 60,
to Faction 59.
Now, I'd like to explain
the rules for the Sword Competition.
The competition will be on
a five-on-five basis.
There are five altars on the field
which are metal, wood,
water, fire, and earth.
Insert your sword into an altar and
it will begin to accumulate your score.
The more altars you occupy,
the faster your score accumulates.
The team whose score
reaches 100% first wins.
SPIRITUAL FORCE
This is the same as Capture the Flag
in video games.
The competition was scheduled
to be held on your campus.
Unfortunately, there was
an attack there not long ago.
Therefore, the location
was changed to our campus.
Outside this gym is the competition ground
for tomorrow.
It is a little too big.
I hope you can adapt to it soon.
Faction 59 is so big.
Master, are you lost?
Yes.
I can't use my spiritual force
to support the trick of guidance.
Master, I sensed an exit over there.
I'll go and have a look.
Dear instructors,
Faction 60's team doesn't seem
to have enough members.
Even with this dog,
there are only four of them.
Is that why you set up Wang Ling?
If you don't have enough members
to participate,
you will be regarded as abstaining.
Hey, you can't do the math, can you?
Count for yourself.
You have four members on your team too.
The fifth member
has been here all the time.
Look out, everyone!
Hey.
Are you crazy?
Be careful.
He generated such a big wave,
but there wasn't a drop of water on him.
This guy is not to be underestimated.
What?
Where is he?
Ms. Sun,
this flower is for you.
He's fast!
I don't know you.
Why do I have to take your flower?
How interesting.
The chairman asked me
to deal with Faction 60.
If you take this flower,
I'll help you deal
with the chairman and his team.
What do you think?
He Bufeng!
Are you going to betray us?
I don't really care.
There is a huge difference in power
between the two teams.
If I join them,
it will make your power more balanced.
Why did you ask this idiot to participate?
Take your dirty hands
off Sun Rong!
This is spiritual pressure.
He is in the Golden Pill Phase.
Ms. Sun,
we know each other now, don't we?
What if
I don't take it anyway?
Ms. Sun,
does that mean you're refusing me?
Go away!
Don't meddle with a man
who has just been refused.
How presumptuous.
He's just one phase lower
and he dared to challenge me.
The Chen family has always been decent.
-We take the safety
-of the world as our responsibility.
We are honorable people.
When we see injustice,
we'll step forward to help.
Whether the culprit is an evil man
-or a devil…
-Or a devil,
we always kill him!
What a coincidence.
My hobby is to break the illusions
of hot-blooded youngsters.
Let me destroy one of your arms first.
Chen Chao!
-Wang Ling!
What happened?
Negative energy.
He is a drop-down.
He practices
the coldest negative energy power.
So what happened in that instant was…
That's right.
It is called "annihilation."
Negative energy is a spiritual force
in the opposite direction.
When it collides with
a cultivator's positive spiritual force,
a huge spiritual energy
called annihilation is produced.
The most striking phenomenon
is that matters are annihilated.
What you did is nothing.
Once Wang Ling's seal is removed
and the negative energy in his body leaks,
the whole world will be doomed.
Wang Ling, be careful with him.
ELITE
I get it.
I can't come out now.
What about your amulet?
Hey!
Don't hang up!
He hung up on me.
Sir, your ticket.
DAD
TALKING…
It is obvious that he will not be able
to sneak away.
This can't be happening.
His arm was devoured
by my trick of annihilation.
Could he have
restored his hand in an instant?
That's right.
In the instant
that Wang Ling turned his body,
he restored Chen Chao's arm
with his grand trick of repairing.
But at the same time,
because he used spiritual force,
Wang Ling's amulet
is on the verge of breaking.
How interesting.
He has such unbelievable power,
but I can't sense
any spiritual force in him.
Now, let me see what you've got.
What?
He doesn't have any spiritual force.
Why is he walking away
like nothing happened?
Are you all right, Wang Ling?
We'll take this flower.
This guy…
When did he…
Master, shall I put him out?
Shut up.
He was beaten up like that?
Now that all participants are here,
please proceed
to your respective preparation room.
I get it.
Get ready.
Come with me to Faction 59.
Why do you stay behind, Wang Ling?
"Sweet potato flavored crispy noodles.
Limited to Faction 59."
All right.
Wang Ling, I'm going with them now.
This is my chance.
He is left behind alone.
Miss,
what are you doing?
I'm on duty to clean the training ground.
How are you doing?
Are you still pretending?
You are not a student
of Faction 59 at all.
Girls in Faction 59 who have
a beauty value higher than 7
are all stored here.
What a bad boy.
You know how to sweet talk.
Think about it. Be my girlfriend.
No matter what you want to do,
I'll help you.
Hey, all beautiful roses have thorns.
I like dangerous women in particular.
Thank you for your kindness,
but I prefer someone younger.
"Younger"?
Old lady,
don't pretend to be a little girl.
What was that?
Pretending to be a little girl
at your age?
Do you really think
I can't see through it?
Silly old woman.
The last person who dared to call me that
is now lying in his grave with grass
taller than you are on it.
After so many years of fighting,
there is finally a rival now
that excites me.
Take this.
Do you think
your negative energy is a big deal?
Even that old driver of mine is capable
of handling it.
What?
Sleep in peace.
LITTLE RACCOON
ADAPTED FROM THE DAILY LIFE
OF THE IMMORTAL KING BY KU XUAN
FROM QIDIAN OF CHINA LITERATURE