[EP. 12]
It was so hot today
If it wasn't for you
I wouldn't have been able to carry all these things to the workroom
Thanks
It's nothing
Ah.. there's no more water?
Do you want to drink some more?
Yeah
I'll get some
S.. S.. Sorry!
I'll.. get you some water!
Ah.. so awkward
Him too.. He never changes
What? Are you crazy, Baek Ha Eun!!
What are you thinking?
Ha Eun
Huh?
Ah.. ah.. yeah?
Well..
I'm not ready yet..
I guess I'll go now
What?
Ah.. sure, you should go
Thanks for your help, see ypu tommorow
What kind of man
just leaves his girlfriend's place as soon as he gets there?
I should have..
told him to stay a bit longer..
Huh? Yeo.. Yeon Woo
Did you come back to see this together?
Yeah
It's something I did because I was feeling a bit better
Don't take it too..
First kiss,
a thrill you can feel only once
A day before us Season 2