[EP. 13]Before Our hearts Meet
Read[I have something to tell you..]
Read [Can you meet me at the bench at 5?]
Wook :[I don't think I can]
Read[Then I'll wait for you until you come]
Why are you standing in the rain like a fool?
Wook..
Are you..
dating her?
What are you talking about?
Yena..
Are you two dating?!
If that's what you wanted to talk about,
Then I'm going to leave
I... I don't like you meeting her
How is that any of your business..?
It is my business!
We..
We'r friends..
I..
I don't want to be your friend any more
Why?!
Because you're with Gon Ha
Gon Ha!
He's just a friend, that's all
I don't know why I'm like this either but..
But I only think about you! what should I do?
I've just barely gotten my self sorted..
I/ve just only given up on you
No..
Don't give up on me
As for me
I don't like anyone except for you
Me too..
You are the only one for me
I like you
Lee Yeo Reum
Dating,
The second paragraph of our relationship thate we write together