[EP. 14]Before We Know Each Other
cheese!
You were waiting for me?
You're hungry, right?
Want to eat this?
Huh? cheese where are you going?!
Hey!
Where in the world are you going
Huh?
No cheese..
you can't eat his food
Slow down, don't eat so fast
You are so adorable
Huh? What was that?
But, why am I hiding
What are you doing?
I think I heard something
Why are you covering my mouth? what is happening?
Maybe I just heard it wrong?
Oh, right!
Guys, sorry! I have to leave for class!
See you guys later, bye
Huh?Ha Eun?
Ha.. Eun?
The running girl with the purple hair
Yeo Reum's classmate,they're in the same department
She's pretty, huh?
Do you want me to talk to Yeo Reum and set  you up with her?
No way..
Why?
Fate,
The first encounter leading to a relationship
Ha.. Eun?
A day before us Season 2