[EP. 15]One Day Before Love
Hey, you go in front..
Okay
I'm about to take it..
One, Two!
Kim Wook!Delete it!
No way! it come out nice!
Hurry up and delete it and take a new one!
Hmm.. it looks good though
Oh, just wait a second
Why?
What are you going to do?
He can't even draw very well..
What's he doing? he looks so serious
Awesome!
It looks just like you, right!
What is that? Do you want to die?!
Give me that!
No way
Looks like I made it a lot pretter than the real thing
Kim Wook, you!
Be.. Be careful..!
Aaahh
Hey.. Lee Yeo Reum
Hey! You!
Huh?
You've got a nosebleed!
No matter how mad you were, how could you do this to your boyfriend..
Isn't too much?
Sorry..
This is supposed to be a date... now I've got a nosebleed
What is this..?
Whew..
First love,
Everyone's clumsy fresh story
You did a great job finishing the contset
I think we.. did well thanks to you
Thank you
Ah.. and..
Why?
I'm sorry, Gon Ha
Thanks a lot for your loving on A day before us Season 2
What's up?
Why did you want to meet?
Well..
You guys too... no way!
It's not that, right?
Actually I..
I'm dating Yeo Reum
What?
Really? seriously?
A day before us Season 2