[EP. 02] Before the Awkwardness Fades
Ha! It’s like I haven’t seen the sunlight for years.
I almost lived in the studio during the break.
Oh right!
You’re preparing for the competition.
What did you guys do during the break?
During b-break?
I just stayed home.
Hmm...
You’re so mean!
How come you never called me?
Sorry, sorry! The class ended late.
Argh! The School of Arts is too far!
Wook! How have you been?
Oh, hey!
I just stayed home the whole time.
Wook…
You never called me during the break, either!
Oh…
I was a bit…busy.
Yeah right.
You don’t have friends anyway.
That’s not true!!
Hey!
She looks prettier
after not seeing her for a long time…
Sh-Should we all eat together?
It’s been awhile.?
Huh? Hello?
Oh, yes.
I’m on my way! Okay.
I’ve got to go.
Hey, but I just got here!
You were late!
I have to go!
Okay…
See you later!
Was it..
Gun Ha..?
Timing
a bus that rarely returns once you miss it.
A Day Before Us Season 2