[EP. 05] Before We Miss Each Other
Are you done with the assignment?
Yeah, you?
I have to finish it
but I just can't concentrate
I can help you out after the class
What is with Yeo Reum?
She's with him all the time
argh..
Am I invisible to her or what?
Huh? Wook!
You're in this class, too?
Y-Yeah
I guess you are too
Hey, we should have come together then
Hello!
I'm a freshman, Seo Yena!
Huh?
Didn't we meet in front of the lab earlier?
Can I sit here?
Uh sure
I haven't seen you since then
Which grade are you in?
Sophmore. I'm a business administration major
Oh
I thought we were in the same department!
What's your name?
Ah, I'm Kim Wook
Whoa? your name is Wook!
I can call you Wook right?
I see
This is a class of group presentations
Go find your partners
Hey Yeo Reum, wanna pair up with me?
Yeah sure!
I was the one next to Yeo Reum
But now Gun Ha's next to her..
Wook!
Let's pair up!
Shall we then?
Yes! what topic should we choose?
I heard that the prof is quite picky...
Rival
a third person that clears fuzzy thinking
I heard thar topics are similar every semester
Uh? Wait a sec
A day before us Season 2