[EP. 06] Before the Secret is Revealaled
What's up? Yeon Woo
What's that... pink thing on your hair?
Oh
This is a nessesity for women
I see
Are you done with the PowerPoint?
Ha Eun
Oh! Gon Ha!
Is he your boyfriend?
What?
No, no way!
Ah he's just.. a friend
we're working on the assignment together!
Oh really?
It's been awhile, huh?
Y-Yeah!
I think so..
By the way
I heard you went to the Venice Binnale
That's awesome
Well, it has a good experience
Any good news these day?
Neh, I'm swamped with assignments
Just saying..
Coz you get prettier than last year
Gosh! S-Sorry
What should I do..?
Such a kind.. friend, huh?
Ri-Right?
No
I don't like my girlfriend touching other guys
So you're her boyfriend
You look good together
I have to go now
See you in the lab
Hey, you..
who is that guy anyway?
Just a senior in my deparetment
I see
What a man, Yeo Woo
Secret,
A worthy sweet moment not just for two
What's up?
You never ask to see us first
Seriously
I have to tell you guys something
Actually..
I'm... dating Yeon Woo!
Everyone knows it already
A day before us Season 2