[EP. 07] Before He Seems Different
I met Wook in front of the lab last time
So I thought he was in the same department
Oh.. that's where you saw him?
But don't you think
Wook is quite cool?
What's with this girl?
Acting like she knows all about him..
Is he? I can't really tell
I think Wook is..
Tall
Cute
And really attractive!
Wow..
I don't think he's all that
Yeo Reum
Does he have a girlfriend?
What?
I.. don't think so
Why?
Why is she only talking about Wook?
Because I'm intersted in him
So if he's not dating anyone..
Neh, you're too good for him
He's not that attractive
You think so?
Of course
What's the deal?
He's wearing a suit and even did his hair..
He looks... nice today
Oh! there's Wook!
Wook, what's the occasion today?
Why are you dressed up so nicely?
Ah, nothing
I have a wedding to attend today
Oh, where's the wedding?
Can I come with you?
Well that's..
Hey, Yeo Reum
What are you doing here?
Seriously?
Jealousy,
A mirror that
reflects hidden emotions
Wook, how was his wedding?
Hmm..is this too boring?
I was busy a moment ago..
-Were you busy while ago?
Huh?
A day before us Season 2