[EP. 09] Before I Get Drunk
There sure are more people than usual!
I guess it's because of the festeval
I heard that Yeo Reum and them start tommorow
I wonder if thing are going okay?
Uh?
Yeo Reum..
Yeo Reum.. are you okay?
What?
Yes! of course!
Drink up!
Uh?!
Hey, Yeo Reum! Don't drink too much
Oh..
Isn't that the popular guy Kim Wook?
Come on.. Are you drunk?
No..?
But why are you alone? where's Yena?
What are you talking about?
Don't pretend it's not like that..
First just sit and have a drink!
I guess she needs to sober up a bit before leaving
Here have a drink
Yeo Reum's your friend, right? I've heard a lot about you
This is the person
The one..
Yeo Reum likes
The one who was by her side
I could never be by her side like that
Yeo Reum!
Yeo Reum, take ahold of yourself
Are you okay?
You didn't know she's not that great at drinking?
N.. No... it's not like that
You shouldn't have kept making her drink like this
I think you have some misunderstanding..
Let's go, Yeo Reum
I'll take her home
No, I'll take her home
No matter how close a friend are you..
It's not right
Alcohol,
A medium that changes sighs into sincerity
I'm sorry to call you out so suddenly
It's okay
But what's up?
Well.. Um.. Just..
I think things got awkward with my friend
Recently it feels like maybe this person not my friend anymore.
I feel like I don't see this person as my friend any more..
A day before us Season 2