මම සම්පූර්ණයෙන්ම නිෂ්ඵල විය ...
ඇත්තම කිව්වොත් මම හිටියේ පාරේ ...
ලී, ඔබ සැමවිටම ධනාත්මක වන අතර
වරක් දහඩිය මහන්සි වී වැඩ කළ විට,
ඔබට
සෑම නිෂේධාත්මක දෙයක්ම අමතක කළ හැකියි නේද?
මම නිකන් එහෙම නෑ ...
මෙය දහඩිය නොවේ.
මේවා බලාපොරොත්තු සුන්වීමේ කඳුළු!
මෙවර, අවම වශයෙන්, මට ප්‍රයෝජනවත් වීමට අවශ්‍ය වූ
අතර මම හොඳින් සූදානම්ව සිටියෙමි!
ඔබට දැනෙන හැඟීම මම දනිමි.
මෙවර මටත් අවශ්‍යයි ...
කකාෂි සෙන්සේ!
- නා-!
- නරුටෝ කොහෙද ?!
ඒ ...
කවුද ඒ කොල්ලා?
සමහර විට ...
වලිග තුන පාලනය කළ හැකි තැනැත්තා ...
මේ පිරිමි ළමයාට
ඒ විශේෂ බලය ඇත.
වලිග තුන
වැවට අතුරුදහන් වී ඇත,
නමුත් මෙය කිසිඳු ආකාරයකින් අවසන් නොවේ.
මුද්‍රා තැබීමේ කණ්ඩායම
සුවය ලබන තෙක් අපි බලා සිටිමු ,
and then we'll attempt the
Four-Corner Sealing Barrier again.
However...
we can't move this child right now.
When he regains consciousness,
we'll move to a safer spot
and make preparations.
Meanwhile, we need to find Naruto.
Naruto...
Don't worry.
Knowing Naruto, he's probably in
the lake doing the breaststroke.
Yamato, Sai, Kiba, Hinata...
And myself.
The five of us will search for Naruto.
Shizune, you come with us
just in case Naruto is injured.
Right.
Sakura and Ino will treat the boy.
The rest of you will keep guard.
The enemy is sure to return
to take the boy.
I won't let them!
I will protect the boy, no matter what!
Everyone, stay alert and
carry out your mission!
Byakugan!
Naruto...
What if we can't find Naruto,
even with Hinata and Kiba with us?
Listen. I know we just tried to seal
the Three-Tails and it's totally exhausting,
but we have to be extremely careful
with our Chakra Control.
I know. I will redeem myself.
I'm absolutely going...
to save this boy.
Well then, the least I can do is make sure
your Chakra Control goes well,
and do votive squats...!
I can't concentrate!
Okay.
We're supposed to be guarding them.
Th-That's right!
It's not smart to stay clustered together.
Shino is here.
Let's go around the back.
What about...me?!
You keep watch on top of the roof.
Got it!
The insects are drastically weakened...
Is this also due to
the Three-Tail's Chakra?
Where is this...?
I know! I was swallowed by
that Three-Tails!
Which means I'm inside his belly...!
It's so hard!
Cripes, his stomach is awful!
What does he eat anyway?
Oh...me...
You're...!
Why you--!
I won't let you have Yuukimaru!
- Yuukimaru is...!
- Die!
Strange Bedfellows
Rinji!
Why you-! What's going on?!
Leaving us in the trenches during a fight!
We went through hell thanks to you!
Now, now. I got an urgent summons
from Guren, so I had no choice.
Huh? Wh-What?!
Why you--!
Wh-What?!
It's rude to stare like that!
Humph...Things change every second
in the battlefield.
H-Hey!
Quit complaining.
Where are you going?
Rinji...!
Isn't he...acting strange? That Rinji.
He's lost it. Running away
in the face of the enemy.
Who ran away from the enemy?
Uh...no... Well...
Cripes... Quit staring!
You and Rinji... What's with you?
Have you ever looked at
your eyes in the mirror?
They're not eyes that look at humans.
At this rate, you guys will die.
A-Are we that bad?!
Liar!
No! You're just kidding...
I'm not kidding.
You're not?
The flow of Chakra is all over the place...
In this case, I'd say you're heading
straight towards destruction.
Destruction?
My, my.
You fought against a terrifying foe...
You, Kihou... In your case,
I'd say...you have less
than two hours left and bon!
Are you serious?!
What about me? Am I...?
Stop! I don't want to know
how I'm going to die!
I-I don't want to die!
Please save me, Kabuto!
M-Me too! Please save me!
I don't wanna go "bon"! No "bon"!
No matter how much you beg,
there are things I can and
can't do with my Medical Ninjutsu...
Ah...
- Huh?!
No... No, I can't.
I can't do such a thing
to my precious comrades!
"Such a thing"?!
Please do "such a thing" to us!
We'll do anything.
We'll endure anything!
I don't wanna go "bon"!
Well, since you insist...
- Huh?
He's being used. He believes
there's someone he can return to...
But he's sure to be betrayed.
When that happens...
He won't have anywhere to go...
If wherever someone thinks of you
is the place you return to...
Then...
I'll keep thinking of him.
So Naruto was talking about this boy...
Huh?
Oh...!
Naruto is okay. I'm sure he's somewhere
thinking about this boy...
Where am I?
It's okay. We're going to protect you
from now on.
Protect...?
It's gone! It's gone!
What's wrong?
Is something missing?
It's gone...!
Gone...!
Gone... Gone...!
This is...
That's...
Yuukimaru...?
Then... Then...you're...
I...
I'm forgiven?
Have you...
You have the gall to ask such a thing
after killing someone...
Forgive you...?
No...!
Absolutely not!
Stop... Please stop...!
I...
My wound...
Did you treat it?
What's the big idea?
What are you scheming?!
Nothing...!
Don't lie!
Your enemy lies unconscious!
Why would you, a Ninja,
pass up the chance to...!
I wouldn't do a shameful thing like hurting
someone who's unable to fight!
Where's Yuukimaru?!
He's not close by.
Back then, I think we were the only two
that Three-Tails swallowed.
Then Yuukimaru is still by the lake...
Either your guys got him...
or one of my comrades saved him.
Then I have to get out of here
immediately and find out.
So it's imperative that we fight.
I'm going to defeat you
and get out of here.
You won't leave here...
unless you can defeat me.
That's true...
I was just thinking the same thing...
But...
Huh?
Wh-What...?
Huge bugs...?!
These are...mini-Three-Tails!
Aw, jeez!
What're you doing?!
I'll use my Crystal Style...!
You can't! Remember?
Not with that injury!
Let go!
I can run by myself!
It's gone...! Gone!
What's the matter?
What are you looking for?
Found it! I found it!
See!
It's a pretty crystal...
It's not even scratched...
I'm so glad. Guren is all right.
Guren...?
Could it be the person Naruto spoke of,
the one this boy thinks of?
Oh...!
Are you all right?!
Guren is all right.
This boy... What's with...
He's being used.
He believes there's someone
he can return to...
But he's sure to be betrayed.
Are you all right?
Why?
Why are you trying to help me?
I don't fight an injured enemy...
You could've left me for
those Three-Tails back there...
That would be disgusting to watch!
You're...naïve...
Humph!
Had it been me, you'd be dead by now.
And I'd leave this place...
and look for Yuukimaru.
You want Yuukimaru that badly?
For Orochimaru's sake?!
Well, what about you guys?
You discovered Yuukimaru's powers
and now you want him!
After all, taking the Three-Tails
means that the Hidden Leaf Village
will be in possession of
enormous military power.
We don't need such a thing!
Liar! The Hidden Leaf Village already
has the Nine-Tails
as well as the Jinchuriki!
People like you with that kind of power
have no right...
to criticize Lord Orochimaru...
or us!
And I'm that Jinchuriki!
Wha--?!
But I...
don't use this power.
The Nine-Tails has this incredible power
that I can't control with my own strength.
I've hurt my comrades before
I even realized it happened...
That's why...I don't use its power.
If I hadn't told him such a thing...
The place where someone thinks of you,
that's where home is.
So if someone is thinking about me,
then that's the place I go back to?
You told him?
But no matter how much someone
thinks of him...
If you're gonna use Yuukimaru
for Orochimaru's sake...
to make him control the Three-Tails...
That's not right.
I don't want Yuukimaru to get near
a Tailed Beast.
If he becomes like me...
No! I won't let Yuukimaru do
such a thing.
I don't believe you.
He needs a place to return to.
When his mother died,
Yuukimaru lost the place to return to...
So I'm taking her place...!
You should talk!
You're a follower of Orochimaru.
I have to tell Yuukimaru that
you're not  the place to return to!
Then that's fine!
But...for me...
that boy...
Yuukimaru is...
the place for me to return to!
You...
Anyway...
this isn't the place
to argue about that.
While you were unconscious,
I took a look around.
It's really complex in there and
I couldn't find anything like an exit.
But if we split up and search...
Split up?
You and me... The two of us...?
More than that. We need a thousand guys.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You three are ordered to take
Yuukimaru away from the Hidden Leaf.
Resort to any means necessary
in order to succeed.
That power...
go and enjoy it
until you're satisfied.
Naruto...!
Naruto...
Here's to the First Naruto Cup Challenge!
The Let's-Get-Out-of-This-Crazy-Place;
Find-an-Exit Contest!
Let's do it!
- Yeah!
In your positions!
Ready, set...!
Go!
With this many guys searching,
finding the exit is a cinch!
All right! I'll find it!
No, I will!
Whatever I do, I have to get out...
and find Yuukimaru...
Yahoo!
I know!
I know where Guren is!
Huh?
I'm sure Naruto is with her!
They're in the Three-Tail's tummy!
According to Yuukimaru,
Guren the Crystal Style user is alive...
And he says that Naruto and this Guren
were swallowed by the Three-Tails?
That story may have some truth to it.
But how do you know that Guren is okay?
If something happens to Guren,
this crystal will break, as well...
But it doesn't mean that Naruto is okay.
We need to believe he's still alive
and find the Three-Tails first.
Next time:
"Guidepost of the Camellia"
Tune in again!