Before he died,
Jiraiya said to me,
"go store yourself inside Naruto."
Are you crazy?!
The key that corresponds to
Naruto's Eight-Signed Seal
is transcribed on my belly!
Each year,
the Fourth Hokage's seal weakens!
The key remains in order
to re-seal it
when it becomes necessary!
To place such a key right next
to the safe is unheard of!
Still, Minato entrusted it to us.
It was always meant to be
returned to Naruto.
It's too soon!
Once you talked me into loosening
the Tetragram Seal…
You haven't forgotten
what the results were, have you?!
Yeah…
However, the fact that Minato left me
the jutsu for the key
convinces me that
he intended for Naruto
to perfect that jutsu one day.
Great Lord Elder!
Are you sure this is the right thing?
Jiraiya claimed that Naruto
could completely control
the power of the Nine-Tails,
but when we tested him,
it didn't go well.
But Jiraiya refused to give in,
saying that it was for that purpose
that Minato had sealed
half of the Nine-Tails' chakra
inside of Naruto.
Great Lord Elder, Gerotora himself
is the key to Naruto's Tetragram Seal.
Is it safe to hand him over to Naruto?
What do you think?
Have Naruto Uzumaki come here.
I shall do a reading on him.
We will then see what
we must do.
Huh? Is that true?
It hasn't been officially
announced yet, but it's clear,
judging from the activity in front of
the hut where she was resting.
It seems that all of her attendants,
who were all in such low spirits,
have been gathering
there smiling!
I guess their prayers
have all been heard.
Please eat more slowly!
This is not enough!
My chakra hasn't returned
to normal!
Bring me more food!
If I'm not careful,
I'll become an old hag!
Uh-oh, no, no!
The Hokage Quarters' supply stores
have run out.
I'll go and requisition
more provisions,
so please take a short break.
No! Don't do it!
What are you thinking?!
This one is completely off limits!
What are you talking about?
Huh?
K-Kakashi…
I'm glad to see you so well.
This is nothing,
I'm just getting started.
After all you've eaten,
it doesn't make any sense.
I am relieved.
I was dangerously close
to becoming the Hokage.
But well, I'm not really
the Hokage type.
Considering the present situation,
we need someone like you,
Lady Tsunade, with wide influence,
to be the Hokage.
I must say I am amazed to hear
about the Allied Shinobi Force.
And I'm surprised that
the Tsuchikage and the Raikage
agreed to cooperate.
That just goes to prove
what an awful situation
we are faced with.
Madara Uchiha…
He's really still alive?
We don't have absolute proof,
but considering what
they are trying to do,
I'd say there's no doubt about it.
Another war, huh?
Who would have thought
the karma of the Uchiha
would engulf all the shinobi
in the world.
I will call a meeting immediately
after this meal!
We must prepare for war!
Prophecy of the Great Lord Elder
You must rest for a while.
It takes some time to become
accustomed to the Mangekyo.
Are you in pain?
No.
It feels right. I can feel
Itachi's visual powers.
I can feel myself getting stronger!
INTEL DIVISION
And then, Orochimaru forced me
into hard labor.
And when Sasuke took over
he kept giving poor old me
the most unreasonable demands.
In the end, he treated me like dirt.
I'm a victim too!
I see. It must have been
hard on you!
Jeez…
We're not asking about
your personal history.
We are asking for intel on
the Akatsuki, Sasuke, and Kabuto.
And don't get emotionally involved!
What good will it do if
you get swayed?
F-Forgive me.
All right. But only if you
accept my conditions.
Conditions?!
First of all… I'm starving!
If you interrogate someone,
you're supposed to give 'em
a fried pork cutlet bowl, right?!
What do you mean
"a fried pork cutlet bowl"?!
I didn't think there was
a fried pork cutlet bowl shop in the village.
Even if there were,
would it still be in business under
these circumstances?
I heard that Ichiraku has started up
again in temporary quarters.
Would ramen do?
No way. It has to be
a fried pork cutlet bowl.
Then, shall we see if
we can get delivery
from outside the village?
You can get a fried pork cutlet bowl
from a noodle shop too, can't you?
It would take about two days.
Cripes! What a pair!
– F-Forgive me.
They're alike.
What is this?
This village is cheerful…
and warm.
Just like him.
Hey, Naruto!
Haven't seen you for a while.
Where were you?
Well…umm…
You see…umm…
It gets lonely when
you're not around.
Your liveliness gives the whole village
the energy to recover.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, man…
I saw that.
Yeah.
His head is getting big,
I tell you.
Just look at him smiling away.
It's unpleasant.
– This is a problem.
– Thank you, thank you.
We, the mass media,
have created a terrible monster.
If we don't take Naruto down
a peg or two,
the village is going to suffer.
Yeah.
I wonder where he's trying to go.
Nowhere good, I'm sure.
I've got it! We'll focus in
on the decisive moment!
– Yeah!
Wait for me, my love!
I've been waiting to see you!
I was right!
It's them again. Do they think
I haven't noticed them?
They're following me everywhere.
Naruto…
You're the village hero,
Naruto, aren't you?
Huh?
No, I'm no hero.
By the way,
where are you headed, ey?
"Ey"?!
You're Konohamaru, aren't you?!
I am not Konohamaru, ey!
Don't lie!
Why you—!
What's the big idea?!
In that case, I'll do this!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You can't get away, ey!
Harem Jutsu!
– What?!
I want a word
with the village hero, ey!
We got a tip that
you have a sweetheart, ey!
– Cripes!
– Who is it, ey?
Aren't you going on
a date now, ey?
The village hero, huh?
But…
Where are you going, ey?!
That time, when Naruto stood up
to Pain in order to protect me…
the Nine-Tails appeared in Naruto's body.
That's…
Do you hate me?
I could feel its intense anger,
but I couldn't feel any
of Naruto's will.
It was like his anger had
taken over his heart.
All because of that Nine-Tails.
Now that the First Hokage's necklace
that Naruto received
from Lady Tsunade is lost,
if the Nine-Tails should
ever run loose…
even I couldn't stop it.
True, it would be
tremendously risky
to take on the Akatsuki
with the Nine-Tails inside him.
But…
– O-Oh no!
– Wait up! Naruto, ey!
He is Naruto.
He's not the Nine-Tails.
For this battle,
we don't need the Nine-Tails.
We need Naruto's strength.
If it looks like the Nine-Tails
is going to take over,
we have to stop it.
That's right.
This is also a battle in which
we must protect Naruto from
the Akatsuki and the Nine-Tails.
That's how I…no…
I'm sure this is how
all of my classmates feel.
We will protect Naruto,
and we will fight with Naruto.
I wonder what Lady Tsunade thinks.
Is everyone here?
We shall now start our war council
to discuss strategy!
First, assemble reserves of
ninja tools and foodstuffs.
We must divide our shinobi into
main battle units and support forces,
and consider how we should
build the platoons
within the fighting forces!
Bring me the complete list
of all our shinobi!
So it's war.
So it's finally come to that.
You were invited to this war council,
but you're still young.
Keep your ears open
and don't miss a thing.
Yeah. I know that.
I will make full use of my head
and hammer everything in!
I guess I finally lost them.
Now, finally, I can enjoy
my love to the fullest!
Old man! One large tonkotsu miso
with BBQ pork!
Naruto!
Huh?!
So Grandma Tsunade is fine now?
Yes!
All right!
Is that right?
I'm happy about Lady Tsunade.
Okay! Since this is good news,
the ramen is on me!
Huh?! Are you sure?!
Why don't you have some too, Sakura?
No thanks.
I still have more people to notify.
Well, I'll see you later, Naruto!
Now that that's off my mind,
I feel hungrier than ever!
Okay! I'm eating my fill today.
One bowl, two bowls, three bowls!
Here you go!
It's a special tonkotsu miso
with BBQ pork slices
to celebrate the Hokage's recovery!
Whoa!
Thank you for the…
Oh? He disappeared.
…food!
I'm surprised he dug right
into the food.
Looks like he really loves
my bug cooking!
What am I doing here again?
I did a Reverse Summoning on you.
The Great Lord Elder will
divine your future, Naruto-boy.
Divine?
Follow me.
Don't throw it up!
I have brought him.
Hey! Long time no see,
Giant Gramps Sage!
It was indeed I who
summoned you…er…umm…
Who're you again?
Naruto Uzumaki!
I wish you'd hurry up and
learn my name, Giant Gramps Sage!
Oh, that's right, that's right.
It's Naruto.
Do we have to go through
this every time?
Listen, Naruto.
I have seen
a prophecy involving you.
A prophecy?
Okay, I'm ready for it.
In that case, listen carefully.
You will soon be meeting
an octopus.
An octopus?
Why an octopus?
Well, I couldn't see too clearly,
but I'm sure
they were octopus arms.
And then, it will come to pass that
you will fight a young man
whose power lies in his eyes.
And…
Yeah… I know.
What do you mean, "you know"?
I don't plan on changing.
Nor am I interested
in understanding you.
And I don't plan on dying!
You're the one
who's going to die!
If I die, we both die, Sasuke.
Fine then!
I'll kill you first.
It's clear you still haven't
acknowledged me yet.
Enough, Naruto.
I'll take Sasuke on.
You have your precious dream
of becoming the Hokage.
I can't let Sasuke take
you down with him.
How can I become the Hokage
if I can't even save one friend?!
I'll fight…
Sasuke!
So you saw it?
Yeah.
That young man whose power
lies in his eyes…
Do you know who that is?!
Yeah, and I've already
made up my mind.
Gerotora…
I also saw a dream where
you stored yourself inside Naruto.
W-What?!
Give him the Fourth Hokage's seal.
I have no choice but to do
as you say, Great Lord Elder.
What is this?
It is the key left by
the Fourth Hokage
that locks and unlocks
the sealing jutsu on your belly!
With this you can let
the Nine-Tails run free,
if that's what you want.
Press on that square area
with your hand.
With this, you will have
the means to perfect that jutsu
that Jiraiya was talking about.
The key to release…
the Nine-Tails' seal.
Are you unsure, Naruto?
In battle, feelings of hatred
can come out.
So I thought I didn't want
the Nine-Tails' power anymore.
But I need the Nine-Tails' chakra
to fight Sasuke.
I can't hide from that forever.
No use getting depressed!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Storage"
I'm going to conquer
this thing, Dad!
Tune in again!