Judging from their headbands,\Nthey belong to the Hidden Rain...
Which scroll do they have?\NHeaven or Earth?
All you do is run away!
Just be nice and\Nhand over your scroll!
That's not happening.
Ajisai...
Fire Style!
Unsealing Jutsu! Confetti Storm!
They ran away?
Our strength scared them off!
Just when we almost had their scroll!
Tenten's Troubles\N\N
Lady Angel...
Lady Angel,\Nwhat is our special mission?
Take advantage of the Chunin Exams\Nto find a Jinchuriki.
A Jinchuriki?
Suiren, Fuyou...
Use your Sensory Perception skills\Nand look for a shinobi
who harbors\Nan enormous amount of chakra.
Is that what a Jinchuriki is?
Even if you don't find a Jinchuriki,
bring back intel of any extraordinary\Nshinobi from other villages.
– Yes.\N– Yes.
You will follow these two, Ajisai.
I understand.
The Hidden Rain is in\Nthe midst of a reformation.
Other villages must not find out.
They must continue to believe\Nthat Hanzo of the Salamander
rules the Hidden Rain.
– Yes!\N– Yes!
What is it, Ajisai?
You can so see many stars\Nin other villages...
Stars, huh!
So this is what a starlit sky is like...
Oh...a shooting star!
It's the first time I've seen one...
We'll see them too, someday,\Nin Hidden Rain Village.
Now then...
There's no other shinobi\Nin the area.
Okay, we can relax\Nand have a meal.
We're having okonomiyaki\Npancakes for dinner!
Okonomiyaki?
Okonomiyaki in the desert…\NWho would have expected that?
We all need to eat well\Nand maintain our strength.
It's convenient\Nhaving you around, Tenten.
What do you mean\Nby "convenient"?
It's so great that\Nyou're so convenient!
Excuse me?
I may have convenient tools,
but I am not\Na convenient tool...okay?
No, no!\NYou're absolutely convenient!
Come on!
I am not convenient!
You can prepare your own meal.
Hey, Tenten...
Don't follow me!
I wonder what happened?
I don't know either.
What do we do?
Don't look at me.
That was just me venting, wasn't it?
8 Trigrams: Air Palm!
Third Gate of Life... Open!
You've improved greatly, Tenten.
Thank you.
You've perfected your skills.
But it's not good enough,\NGuy Sensei.
Oh? What's wrong?
Mastery with weapons\Nin one-on-one combat
is fundamental for a ninja, correct?
Fundamentals are important.
I know that.
But the issue is going\Nbeyond the fundamentals...
Neji honed his Gentle Fist\Nand developed a new jutsu.
So I understand.\NHe's brilliant!
Lee only has\Nfundamental taijutsu skills,
but he can open\Nthe Eight Inner Gates.
It's the fruits of his labor!
But all I have is the basics.
I want to apply my skills too.
At this rate,
all I'll ever do is stand behind them\Nand support them.
You know, Tenten,\Nsuch a role is crucial in teamwork.
I realize that both Neji and\NLee are taijutsu users
who are close-contact fighters...
We're able to fight aggressively\Nbecause we know that you have our back.
We're grateful that you're here for us.
Rather than gratitude,
I'd like to have\Nmy own special ninjutsu.
Isn't there something, Guy Sensei?
How about the Sansetsukon?
That's no different from this!
That's right, Tenten!
You have a trait no one else\Non this team has.
You should polish that.
A skill no one else has?
You're really convenient\Nto have around.
Please don't talk about me\Nlike I'm some tool, Sensei!
Oh no, I didn't mean it\Nlike that at all.
I'm asking you after giving this\Na lot of thought, you know.
Tenten...
The okonomiyaki pancakes\Nare done.
Let's eat!
How do they taste?
I'm not too confident\Nabout them, but...
Looks like it's going to\Nbe another hot day.
It's the complete opposite\Nof Hidden Rain Village.
A little dampness would be nice.
I see a little bit of green over there.
Byakugan!
What do you see, Neji?
There's no one around here.
Let's keep moving.
As we approach the finish line,\Nothers are bound to appear.
You're right.
It's better than lying in wait.
If we're going to wait,\NI see a good spot.
Where?
Want to go and check it out?
This place is eerie.
I see caves all around us.
It seems to be a ruin.
A ruin?
Yeah...of the Land of Wind.
Just as I expected.
They're Hidden Leaf shinobi.
They look different from\Nyesterday's bunch.
Yesterday's trio was\Ntotally unimpressive.
I wonder what these guys are like?
They're heading right for us.
They have\Na Sensory Perception type too.
We'll ambush them.
They're lying in wait.
What about their scroll?
We'll fight and snatch it away.
Looks like they plan\Nto do the same thing.
They're coming straight for us!
Let's not waste time\Non senseless fighting.
I'll be blunt.
We have the Heaven scroll.
HEAVEN\NIf this is what you're after, let's fight.
Unsealing Jutsu: Shuriken!
That jutsu...!
Rotation!
Summoning Jutsu,\NGate of Rainwater!
You...!
You're not the only one who\Ncan use Transportation Ninjutsu.
Those guys are pretty good.
Yeah, however...
None of them are oozing with\Nlarge amounts of chakra.
Ajisai...
Unsealing Jutsu! Confetti Storm!
FIRE
They ran away!
Byakugan!
Let's go after them!
They're coming after us.
They definitely have\Na Sensory type with them.
Water Style!
Hidden Drizzle Jutsu!
What happened?
There's little moisture around here.
My Water style doesn't work well.
I know we don't have\Nground advantage.
It's an impossible battle,\Nbut we have no choice but to fight.
Leaf Hurricane!
Above you, Lee!
– Senbon Rainstorm!\N– Senbon Rainstorm!
You're pretty good!
Gentle Fist!
Leaf Drop!
ROPE
Tenten!
Ajisai!
I sense their chakra underground...
but it's deep down.
The sand and gravel are in the way.
We can't waste time\Nfighting senselessly.
We're going to save our teammate,\Nso we request that you not interfere.
Same here.
Yes, let's call a truce for now.
We're not at war.
This is just the Chunin Exams.
Our teammate's safety is more important\Nthan passing or failing.
We agree to your plan.
But we'll conduct our own search.
This looks like a ruin\Nof the Land of Wind.
Ajisai and the other shinobi fell\Ninto an underground corridor.
If it's a corridor,\Nit has to connect from somewhere.
Should we just use brute strength\Nand dig from above?
There's a risk of collapse.
We should search for\Na passageway into the ruin
and follow them underground.
Yikes...
What's wrong?
Burn with the passion of youth!
Let your youthful energy seethe!
Fill up with burning chakra!
But Guy Sensei...
I thought this is\Njust strength training!
You're too easygoing, Tenten.
Somewhere along this cliff,
your physical strength\Nwill reach its limits.
Then you will fall and die.
Die?
To prevent yourself from dying,
you must overcome the limits\Nof your physical strength.
Overcoming the limits of\Nphysical strength requires a strong will.
Yes sir!
Hi there.\NAre you guys cliff-climbing too?
Hang in there.
Kakashi?!
Why is your arm\Nbehind your back?
It's a little habit of mine.
Well, see you later!
"See you later"?
Wait up! This is a contest!
I'm finishing first!
Don't get so worked up.\NThis is only training.
What's wrong with\Na little rivalry during training!
Hey, please wait, Guy Sensei!
You can take it easy!
Jeez!
Damn, damn it...
Damn it...
Good job, Tenten. You made it.
Well? Did you overcome your limits?
I'm not quite sure...
But I think I overcame something.
Water?
Here you go.
You're convenient, after all.
Please stop saying that already.
I mean, your jutsu is convenient.
Storing items in a scroll,
or using a scroll to pull things\Nfrom a distance...
The Transportation Technique,\Nwhich is a type of Summoning Jutsu.
You either have the skill\Nfor it or you don't.
You're saying that\NI have the skill for it?
Seems that way.
Honing that skill is the path
to gaining the strength\Nand usefulness you desire.
Hone my skill?
Isn't that only going to increase\Nmy physical strength?
Your spiritual strength too.
You know that chakra\Nis the combination
of physical energy and\Nspiritual energy, right?
Of course.
Each individual can increase\Nchakra simply by training.
Simply put, if you increase\Nyour physical and spiritual power,
your chakra will increase too.
Increasing my chakra\Nis good for me?
With Summoning Jutsu,
the caster's chakra\Nis directly proportionate
to the quantity and size\Nof what is summoned.
This is the amount of water\Nyou just summoned.
By increasing your chakra,
you can summon enough water\Nto fill a bathtub,
or a lake, or even an ocean.
An ocean...
OCEAN
And that is why we will continue\Nto train to increase our chakra, Tenten.
Right!
We just climbed up,\Nso why are we climbing down?!
This is training too!
Burn with the passion of youth!
Let your youthful energy seethe!
Fill up with burning chakra!
Huh?
Where am I?
Hey, are you all right?
Hey...come on!
Lee, did you find something?\N\N
No, I thought it was an entrance into\Nthe ruins, but it was just a boulder.\N\N
I see...\N\N
We have to find\Nthe entrance quickly.\N\N
We don't know how long we have\Nuntil everything caves in,\N\N
due to that previous shockwave...\N\N
Oh no!\N\N
Can't you find them with\Nyour Byakugan, Neji?\N\N
Well, it seems they fell down\Na considerable distance...\N\N
Tenten...\N\N
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:\N"The Imprisoned Pair"\N\N\N
I hope you are safe!\N\N\N
IN NARUTO'S FOOTSTEPS ~\NTHE PATH TRAVELED\NTHE IMPRISONED PAIR\N\N\N
Tune in again!\N\N