මෙය ... විය නොහැක.
සිදුවන්නේ කුමක් ද?!
එතකොට හරියටම,
ජෙනින් බවට පත් වූ තරුණ ෂිනෝබි ,
ජොනින් නැති වූ ගමක් කරා ගමන් කළහ.
ඒ අතර
අනාවැකියේ දරුවා ... නරුටෝ ද විය.
ජිරයියා නින්ජා ලියවිලි:
නරුටෝ හි වීරයා
පිළිබඳ සෙවීමේ මෙහෙයුමේ කතාව
සිදුවුයේ කුමක් ද?
ඔබ දන්නා යමක්
ඇත්නම් කරුණාකර මට කියන්න ... ඒ කුමක් වුවත්.
මට කණගාටුයි.
ඉසුමෝ සහ කොටෙට්සු
හදිසියේම අතුරුදහන් වූහ
මම පුළුවන් තරම් වේගයෙන් එතැනින් පිටව ගියෙමි ...
ඇත්තම කිව්වොත්, මම
මෙතැනට ගියේ කෙසේදැයි මට මතක නැත .
මට තේරෙනවා.
ඒ සියල්ල ඔබට ඉදිරිපත් කිරීම ගැන මට කණගාටුයි
.
නමුත් ඔබට
සුළු දෙයක් මතක තිබුනත් කරුණාකර මට කියන්න.
අගේ…
අගේහා සමනලයෙක් ...
ඔහු කතා කරන්නේ
ෂිනෝබි අගේහා ගැන විය හැකිය ...
මෙම සමය තුළ,
it's not unusual to see them
in the forest near that village.
Is it a poisonous butterfly?
No.
Its powdery scales
stimulate chakra flow
and it's even a main ingredient
in food pills.
I can't believe Izumo and Kotetsu
were beaten so easily…
Looks like we're all set.
No, Team 7 is still…
Sorry, Team 7 is late.
We're all here now.
I know it's sudden,
but let me go over the mission.
I hope its way more exciting
than looking for a lost cat.
This mission is very important.
Three teams of shinobi that were
dispatched on secret missions
have all gone missing.
Your mission is to
search and find them.
Yahoo!
However, you are to contact
the Hidden Leaf
the moment they are found.
Any attempts at rescue
are forbidden.
Why?!
Considering who's been chosen,
the answer should be
pretty obvious to everyone.
Is it because we're all elite ninja
overflowing with talent?!
Nearly all the shinobi who
went missing are capable jonin…
But the only one who was able to
make it back to the village,
was a genin.
So it could mean, experience
and maturity are being targeted.
Which means?
In other words, we were picked
because we're newbies
who just became genin.
Well, you could put it that way…
What?
Is that all?
Naruto, you will most likely
be the one who—
Everyone, stop!
What is it?
Isn't our target village
further ahead?
Look.
What's that?
Shinobi Ageha?
All right! I'm gonna go catch 'em!
Hey! You!
That's really not necessary…
I'll bring him back!
Oh really?
Come on!
Oh boy…
Eight Trigrams Grid Palm!
This is…
Kakashi Sensei!
Naruto! Get back here right now!
What the hell?
I almost had it!
Don't go off on your own
during a mission.
What did you just say?
I don't take orders from you!
What? This isn't an order!
I'm telling you to act
more like a shinobi!
Going off on your own
puts others in—
Sasuke!
Kakashi Sensei's in trouble!
– What happened?
– Kakashi Sensei's…
When I noticed, he…
He was dragged underground, huh?
No way!
What—!
Asuma!
Damn it…
They got him.
What? What happened?
Where's Asuma Sensei?
I-I don't know…
Is this…
…sensation, chakra?!
What happened, Akamaru?!
Akamaru's barking not because of
something happening.
It's because
he lost track of Kurenai Sensei
who should be present.
What is this?
Byakugan!
There's a current of chakra
underground…
Where is it coming from?
Neji! Where are you going?
I want to check something!
Stay with Guy!
Guy Sensei!
Does your chest hurt?!
It's nothing that
a little perseverance can't…
Guy Sensei!
Don't push yourself!
I'll go get some water.
Tenten, stay and watch Guy Sensei.
All right!
What happened?
Guy Sensei felt sick and…
Where's Guy Sensei?!
Black vine-like things sprang up,
wrapped around Sensei,
and pulled him underground.
What?
The current of chakra is gone.
Hey!
Kakashi Sensei is probably
in enemy hands.
What are we supposed to do?
What else is there to do?!
We're gonna find him no matter what
and get him back!
Damn it.
I'm never giving up!
Hey, what are we going to do?
What's going to happen?
First, we should contact
the other teams,
then contact the Leaf Village
like Lord Hokage ordered, right?
Wait.
Don't move!
What?
Damn it.
What the Fourth Hokage feared
would happen just happened…
Huh?!
It's probably safe to assume that
the same thing has happened
to the other team captains.
The other teams?
So it's not only us…
But Sasuke and Kiba and…
Everyone's been left behind?
Yeah…
I just hope Kakashi's team isn't
arguing with each other right now…
Since they have someone
who can be a real drag.
Why you—!
Wait, you loser!
I already told you!
I'm not giving up!
But where are you going?
Well, I don't know, but…
Are you really the son of
the Fourth Hokage?
What did you say?!
Do you really think the Hokage
would send us out
without making any
preventive measures beforehand?
I saw the Hokage
pass out special kunai
to the captains, back then.
Special kunai?
Yeah…
The one he marks when he uses
the Transportation Ninjutsu
to teleport.
As long as the mark is there,
he can track anyone, anywhere.
Transportation Ninjutsu?
You know what
the Summoning Jutsu is, right?
Uh…yeah!
Think of it as
a type of that jutsu.
The special kunai is the target
and no matter
how far away you are…
you can transport to the kunai
in an instant…
Lord Fourth is the only one
who can use that jutsu right now.
I see. I gotta admit…
My Dad's pretty awesome!
Wait!
I don't think…
that's going to happen.
Huh? That's…
I found it at the spot right now.
This is the worst situation
we can be in…
I think I can visualize Lee making
a big fuss over Guy Sensei.
Guy Sensei! Guy Sensei!
Wait, Lee!
Calm down!
That's impossible for me!
Is the Shinobi Code more important
to you two than Guy Sensei's life?!
Don't get the wrong idea!
You blockhead!
Guy…Sensei.
What are you doing?
Just listen!
Just before Guy went missing,
there was an unusual current
of chakra underground.
You saw it with your Byakugan?
Yeah. But it's disappeared now.
So, I'd like to check in on
the status of the other teams.
Linking up with the other teams
is our priority right now.
So, the key players
will be Kurenai's team.
How so?
Kiba's sense of smell,
Hinata's Byakugan and
Shino's Parasitic Insects…
With their sensory skills,
it will be easy to find the current
locations of the other three teams.
And they can probably find
the location where
the team captains are being held.
You're right!
That would make it way faster than
just proceeding blindly.
In situations like this,
panic and proceeding without
thinking is our worst enemy.
It makes more work for everybody.
So until we join up
with Kurenai's team…
…we'll just sit tight.
Choji must've had
barbeque last night…
– Kiba!
– How is it going?
– Hey!
Asuma's team is over that way.
Those guys aren't moving at all.
They know we're looking for them.
They're just sitting back
and resting.
In any case, let's join up
with Shikamaru quickly.
Then we'll pass on his ideas
to the other teams,
and come up with a unified plan.
That's because I have a feeling
there's someone who's going to
act without thinking through things…
And that's where
our abilities come in.
Exactly!
Shikamaru's acclaimed intellect
still needs us!
According to the plan,
Kurenai's team should be over here.
Right.
Blood?!
I have already cursed you.
Huh?
Preparations for the ritual
are complete!
Now!
Let's experience
the ultimate pain together!
What's with this guy?
He keeps talking about
curses and rituals?
He's dangerous!
– Naruto!
– Naruto?!
Doesn't it hurt?
It's gonna be excruciating
so prepare yourself…
It's god's commandment!
Tremble in fear!
He's fast asleep.
He may seem so,
but he wakes up sharp and alert.
Besides,
it helps replenish his energy.
You're too easy on Choji.
And you're too tough.
I knew something was up.
I totally thought it would
happen later though.
I should have known they weren't
going to let us rest so easily.
It's coming!
Paper Shuriken!
Wind Style: Gale Palm!
Damn it… We have to
get out of this Paper Storm…
Choji! Can you break it apart?!
I've had enough rest!
Expansion Jutsu!
Human Boulder!
Roll, roll, roll, roll!
– Roll, roll, roll, roll!
– Water Style: Raging Waves!
You're the ones!
You guys took Asuma Sensei, right?
Bring Asuma Sensei back!
Just who the hell…
…are you?
Don't think you can
escape my curse!
The shinobi world is cursed!
Just give up!
When the man in the strange cloak,
impaled himself
with his pointed scythe
Naruto felt an excruciating pain…
බැලූ බැල්මට
පෙනෙන්නේ මෙම පුද්ගලයා ඔබට දරාගත හැකි ප්‍රමාණයට වඩා වැඩි බවයි.
ඊළඟ වතාවේ නරුටෝ ෂිප්පුඩන්:
ජිරයියා කණ්ඩායම
දීර්ඝ කාලයක් දකින්න නැහැ!
JIRAIYA Ninja පාලුයි:
ඔයාව වීරයා ද ටේල් ඔෆ්
කණ්ඩායම JIRAIYA
නැවත සුසර කරන්න!