A N I M O J O
වෙනුවෙන් Kazuma Satou කල පරිවර්තනයකි
හ්ම්…
මොන උභතෝකෝටිකයක්ද ...
කකාෂි උතුමාණනි, ඔබට ඇති ප්‍රශ්නය කුමක්ද?
කරුණාකර "ස්වාමීනි" අතහරින්න!
කෙසේ වෙතත්,
මම සෑම කෙනෙකුටම පැවරූ මෙහෙවර මතකද ?
මම
සෑම දෙයක්ම තක්සේරු කළ යුතුද?
ඇත්ත වශයෙන්!
ඕන්ක් ඕන්ක්.
මීපැණි වයින් ඇත්තෙන්ම නියමයි,
එය
විශේෂ අවස්ථාවක් සඳහා සුදුසු ය.
ඔබට කියන්න පුළුවන් 8 කණ්ඩායම
මේ සඳහා සියල්ල කළ බව.
සහ
රාත්‍රී ආහාරය සඳහා මෙම තෑගි සහතික
උණු දිය උල්පත් නිවාඩුව
ඉතා කල්පනාකාරී ය!
චොජිගෙන් සහ ෂිකාමරුගෙන් මම මෙය බලාපොරොත්තු නොවෙමි .
ඔවුන් තමන් අභිබවා ගියා.
ගැහැණු ළමයින්ගේ පෞද්ගලික රුචිකත්වයන් ඔබට සැබවින්ම දැකිය හැකිය
ඔවුන්ගේ තේරීම් වලින් පිළිබිඹු වේ.
ඒක හරිම හුරුබුහුටියි ...
නමුත් මේ බලන්න.
ජර්මනියට සහ HINATA
WEDDING GIFT
විය පුද්ගලයෙක්ම
ෙරොක් ලී
පමණක් හැඩයි ඒ ...
නමුත් මේ බලන්න මේක දිහා.
එය විශ්වාස කළ නොහැකි දෙයක් නේද?
අපොයි, කොනොහාමරු
වාර්තාවක් වත් හැරියේ නැත .
කෙසේ වෙතත්, එය හොඳින් සිදු විය.
දැන් ඔවුන්
පිළිගැනීමේ දිනයේ රාජකාරියේ නියුතු අය විය හැකිය .
ඇත්ත, මම තෑගි තක්සේරු
කර මගේ තේරීම් කිරීමට නම්,
මේ තිදෙනාම
අපේක්ෂකයින් විය යුතුයි .
නමුත් මේ සියල්ල ඇත්තෙන්ම හරිද?
රහස් මෙහෙයුමේ ප්රතිඵලය
කකාෂි සෙන්සෙයි?
ඔහ් ?!
හිනාටා! කාලයක් ගත වුනා!
මොකක් ද වෙන්නේ?
මම සකුරා
සහ ගැහැණු ළමයින් හමුවෙමි. මෙච්චර වෙලා ගියා.
තනිකඩ කාන්තාවක් ලෙස ඔබේ අවසාන කාන්තාවන්ගේ එකතුව , නේද?
ඔබේ මංගල සැලසුම් කොහොමද?
මම හිතන්නේ නරුටෝ හොඳින් කරනවාද?
හහ්? ඔහ්, ඔව්.
ඔහු ඇත්තටම හොඳින් කරනවා!
කකාෂි සෙන්සේ , ඔබ කොහෙද යන්නේ ?
මම ඉක්මනින් නින්දට යන්නෙමි.
ඔහ් ... ඔබට කරදර කිරීම ගැන මට කණගාටුයි.
කරුණාකර මට සමාවෙන්න!
ඔහ්…
හ්ම්…
මොකක්ද ප්‍රශ්නය, ඉරුකා සෙන්සෙයි?
රාමන් නරකද?
නෑ නෑ!
රාමන් රසවත්!
එය එය නොවේ…
ඔබ මෙහි සිටින බව මම දැන සිටියෙමි, ඉරුකා සෙන්සෙයි!
කේ-කොනොහාමරු!
මෙය බොහෝ කල් ගොස් ඇත.
මට ඇත්තෙන්ම
ඔබේ සුභ පැතුම් පණිවිඩය ලබා ගැනීමට අවශ්‍යයි !
එසේ නොමැති නම්,
මගේ මංගල තෑග්ග ලෙස මට මෙම වීඩියෝ පටය හැරවිය නොහැක !
මට සමාවෙන්න!
ඉතිං,
ඔබ දුක් වන්නේ එය ගැනද?
ඔව්, කුමක් කියන්නදැයි මට සිතා ගත නොහැක.
හොඳයි, ඔබ ඕනෑවට වඩා දුක් විඳිනවා!
සූදානම් වෙන්න,
මම දැන් ඔබව පටිගත කරමි!
හෙහ්, ඉන්න!
එය එකට එකතු කර ගන්න, ඉරුකා සෙන්සෙයි!
කොනොහාමරුගේ දකුණ, ඉරුකා සෙන්සෙයි.
සුබ පැතුම් පණිවිඩයක කුමක් කිව යුතු යැයි යමෙකු නොදැන සිටින්නේ කෙසේද?
ඔබ නරුටෝගේ ගුරුවරයා
නේද?
එයට හේතුව එයයි!
- ඒකද හේතුව?
නැවත
කසකගේ සාමිවරයා ඉචිරාකු වෙත පැමිණෙන විට ...
මම
නරුටෝට ගෞරව කිරීමට යන්නේ කසකේගේ ලෙස නොව,
නමුත් ඔහුගේ මිතුරා ලෙස.
මම එය ඇසූ විට,
මම
ඔහුව සමරන්නේ කුමන භූමිකාවේදැයි මම කල්පනා කිරීමට පටන් ගතිමි.
ඔයා අදහස් කරන්නේ කුමක් ද?
වෙන මොනවා ද? ඔබ ඔහුගේ ගුරුවරයා ය.
සැකයකින් තොරව, ඔබ සැමට
මා ඔහුගේ "ගුරුවරයා" ලෙස දැකිය හැකිය .
ඒක හරි! ඉතින්, ඉක්මන් කර
මට ඔබව පටිගත කිරීමට ඉඩ දෙන්න,
නැත්නම් මට එය අවසන් කළ නොහැක!
ඔව්…
නමුත්
එය කෙසේ හෝ නොපැමිණිය යුතු යැයි මට හැඟේ
ගුරුවරයෙකුගේ දෘෂ්ටිය ඔහුගේ ශිෂ්‍යයාට.
ඔහුගේ ගුරුවරයා වශයෙන් මෙය කිරීම නිවැරදිද නැද්ද යන්න මම නොදනිමි ...
නමුත් මට දැනෙන්නේ නරුටෝ
ටිකක් වෙනස් බවයි
මගේ අනෙක් සිසුන්ට වඩා.
ඒ නිසාම මට
ගුරුවරයෙකු ලෙස ඉදිරියට යා නොහැක .
කෙසේ වෙතත්,
ඔබ අපව "මිතුරන්" ලෙස හැඳින්විය නොහැකි යැයි මම සිතමි.
කකාෂි දෙවියන් විස්තර කළ ආකාරයට.
කොහොම හරි මම ඒ ගැන හිතන තරමට,
නරුටෝ සඳහා මගේ පණිවිඩය ගැන මම වඩාත් අවිනිශ්චිත වෙමි .
එය නිසැකයි ...
ඔබ සහ නරුටෝ මිතුරන්
වීම හරියට දැනෙන්නේ නැත.
කොහොම උනත් මම ඔය පාත්තරේට අය කරනවා
...
හා? හා?
සියලුම දේ සූදානම් වේ
පිළිගැනීමේ අවසන්?
ඔව්, එයින් වැඩි හරියක්.
කෙසේ හෝ,
අපේ කණ්ඩායමේ පළමුවැන්නා විවාහ වීම ගැන මම පුදුම වෙමි
are you and Naruto!
How is Naruto lately?
Is he helping you at all?
Of course!
More than Naruto,
it's my father who keeps telling me
what I should do.
It's true about the father
of the bride being a pain.
I guess planning a wedding
is a huge task.
Of course it is!
Even with us…
Kakashi Sensei gave us that…
Ah!
Hey, Sakura!
What's the big idea—!
Even with us, Kakashi Sensei
gave us that mission…
Damn it!
– Oh!
– Ah! Ah!
What about Kakashi Sensei?
– Huh?!
– Er…um…
He's going through a lot trying to
wrap up all the missions
before the wedding.
That's all.
Yeah!
And unlike us, you already
have Naruto, so you're lucky.
That's all.
Yeah, that's right!
Well, I guess so.
So? So?
Are you going to wear a kimono?
You're gonna look so pretty
as a bride!
Yeah, yeah!
Hey, Hinata!
Long time no see!
Kiba, Shino!
Have you been doing all right?
Yeah! You two seem great as well!
Of course, since we'll soon be
celebrating your wedding soon.
It's because…
How's Naruto doing?!
We rarely see him these days.
I guess he's busy getting ready
for the big day.
Yes.
Naruto's busy with his missions,
but he's been helping a lot
with the reception.
He's really dependable.
Oh, yeah?
Well, we're completing
a huge mission
and we're gonna make you happy…
Kiba!
Huh?
Oh!
Make me what?
Anyways…
What he means is you and Naruto
will definitely make a happy home!
We're looking forward
to the reception!
Oh, thank you.
MISSION REPORTS
Lady Tsunade!
It's been a while, Shizune!
How have you been?
Great, thank you!
How has your wagering
been going lately?
There's Naruto and Hinata's
upcoming wedding,
so I'm not spending excessively.
That is a wise decision.
Anyway, what did you
want to discuss?
Yes…
Actually, it's about Lord Kakashi…
Kakashi?
What's the matter with Lord Sixth?
I have no choice…
I don't have footage
of Iruka Sensei,
but I'll report this as
my wedding gift for the time being.
Wedding gift items?!
Yes, in addition to shinobi
gathering for the reception,
there's the standing rule
to assess the gifts everyone
will be presenting
in order to determine who will
be attending the wedding, correct?
I remember that rule…
Lord Kakashi has been
in a dilemma about
how he will judge and
who he will eliminate.
When you think about it,
having anyone
not being able to attend,
will make Naruto and Hinata
very sad.
And yet, someone still has to go on
missions and be on guard that day.
He's worrying about that?!
Damn it.
This is really bad!
Everyone's acting a little weird.
Hey! I'm not lying!
Our gifts will be judged
to determine
who can attend the reception?
What's the meaning of this?
I don't get it at all!
Please stop!
I'm not to blame for this!
This is the worst!
Well…it's like this…
Most shinobi of the village
WEDDING RECEPTION
RECEPTION HALL
will attend
Naruto and Hinata's reception.
THE VILLAGE HIDDEN
IN THE LEAVES
That said, it doesn't mean that
we won't have missions on that day.
THE VILLAGE HIDDEN
IN THE LEAVES
We'll need people on duty.
Plus, we'll have important guests.
And it'll be crucial
to have sufficient security
for the reception.
That's right.
Many of Naruto and Hinata's friends
are top-ranked jonin.
So, what does that mean?
We'll have to draw lots to see
who can attend the wedding?!
No way!
If that's the case,
we won't be able to
truly celebrate with the couple!
I didn't think our wedding would
cause so much trouble…
It seems this is troubling
Kakashi Sensei as well.
I see how it would.
Why did it turn into
such a big affair?
Naruto's someone who connects
the entire village.
So, I guess it would
turn into a big deal.
So, we just sit and wait
until the final judgement?
There's no need for that.
I'll do the dirty work,
and that'll be that.
Yes! I want everyone
to attend the reception, so…
I'll volunteer for duty!
That's right! I'll do it too!
Fine, I'll sign me up too.
That's not right!
If Team 8 isn't there,
Hinata will be sad.
But, I'm not okay with someone
missing the reception
just so we can.
We feel the same way.
Now then,
sleeping won't solve anything.
Kakashi Sensei!
I'm so sorry!
Huh?
What?
W-What's wrong, Hinata?
What happened?
I just heard…
The dilemma you're going through,
all because our wedding reception.
Huh? What?
What's this about?
You haven't decided
who can attend on that day, right?
What? You heard?
Yes!
About the mission too?
Yes.
Everything?
I see…
We would never want to
put anyone through any trouble,
just to celebrate our wedding day.
No, no, no, no!
We have to have a reception
for you two!
Then is it possible, at least…
…to have the Hyuga Clan fulfill
the missions and guard duty
for that day?
There's no need for that!
Huh?!
The day of your wedding
is a happy day
for your clan too, right?
It's my duty as the Hokage
to make sure
every member of your family
is there for you.
I…see.
I'll do something about
duty assignments.
So don't worry about anything.
All right.
Focus on yourselves, that's all.
Oops, I'd better get back!
See you!
What?!
What's going on, you guys?
We heard.
About Naruto and Hinata's
reception…
And that some of us
won't be able to attend.
And the mission
to find the wedding gifts
was in order to assess them.
I see… So, you all found out too.
And also, that you've been
agonizing over this.
It's my job as the Hokage.
And what about it?
You're here to oppose?
No, actually the opposite!
What?
Everyone here will handle
the assignments.
But if you do that,
Naruto and Hinata
are sure to be sad.
That's why we're all going to
the wedding reception.
What do you mean?
Simply put, we'll make a schedule
of assignments and guard duty,
and work in shifts.
If everyone puts in some time,
everyone can wish them well!
Helping each other out
is something Naruto taught us.
Well?
This way, you won't have to
bear the all the burden,
right Kakashi Sensei?
You guys…
Thank you!
But if we do this,
we'll have to change the rule.
Don't worry.
Through hell or high water,
I'll think of something.
You'll drown…
Besides, there won't be a need
for all that.
Lady Tsunade.
Lord Sixth…
Actually that rule
was put into effect
when there was a sudden
upswing in weddings…
…and there was
a serious shortage of manpower.
In addition, that was during
the Great Ninja War.
The situation is different today.
And more importantly,
the present Hokage is you, Kakashi.
Don't get caught up in old rules.
Choose the path that you believe
is most fair and just.
Then you'll choose to
let us all work, right?
That won't do.
Why not?!
My job is
to ensure that anyone who wants to
celebrate with Naruto and Hinata,
is able to attend.
I won't allow any early departures
or any late arrivals.
But there's no way around it.
I'll do something.
Hinata?
If it isn't Hinata!
Iruka Sensei…
What?!
Did Naruto do something?!
Huh?
Forgive me, Hinata!
I never taught him about
how to treat women!
I mean, I don't even know
about that kind of thing!
I don't know what happened,
but please…
For me…
Please forgive Naruto!
I beg of you!
What's so funny?
Iruka Sensei…
I didn't say anything,
but you decided that Naruto
must've done something bad
and started to apologize…
Oh? That's not it?
It didn't even cross my mind
that having a wedding
would trouble so many people.
But thinking back on this,
I guess I should have known.
It's not just for us…
but Naruto's a hero that connects
every village together.
I was probably being naïve
just thinking about marrying
the man I'd loved for so long.
You're wrong, Hinata!
Huh?
No matter how great he becomes,
no matter how big a hero
he becomes,
Naruto will always be Naruto…
To me and to everyone.
Iruka Sensei…
Nothing will change our desire to
wish the best for you and Naruto…
So, don't think of it
as a big fuss.
Yes!
I see…
I feel bad for
what I put Hinata through.
I'm sorry too, Iruka Sensei.
Oh no, I understand how
Hinata feels too.
Naruto's someone that connects
everyone in every village together.
Every village…
Thank you, Iruka Sensei!
I know what I have to do!
Huh? What do you mean?
I just have to
bow my head a little, that's all.
Iruka Sensei!
I know you're in there!
At this rate, I'll be the only one
without a wedding gift!
What is it?
Now that Hinata's found out about
the wedding gifts from everyone…
it's no longer a surprise.
So Konohamaru, I think
I'm going to put you to work!
Huh? Huh?
What is it?
WIND
And so,
would it be possible to dispatch
some Hidden Sand shinobi
on the day of the wedding?
I kindly implore you.
Please raise your head, Lord Sixth.
The Raikage, Tsuchikage
and Mizukage,
and I have all been thinking about
what we can do.
We didn't want to overdo things…
I plan on celebrating with them
personally as Naruto's friend,
but I also wanted to do something
as the Kazekage.
Now then, we'll gladly cooperate.
This is all possible because of
the peaceful bond that was forged…
And it was through
Naruto's strength.
It's only fitting that we help
to make Naruto's wedding
a great success.
Thank you very much.
Then may I be so bold
as to ask for one more favor?
What is it? Please tell me.
Konohamaru! Come here!
Yes, sir!
RECORDING
Oh, a video message!
Gaara, say something!
RECORDING
Say what?
Like a proverb or something!
RECORDING
I can't come up with
something just like that!
RECORDING
Come on! You're no Kazekage if
you can't come up with a proverb!
RECORDING
That's right.
6 MORE DAYS
UNTIL THE WEDDING
I didn't have any parents either,
no one acknowledged me.
I did a lot of stupid stuff
to get attention.
Naruto, I think we were
very much alike.
I was your teacher back then,
and at times,
it felt like we were brothers.
But now, you're a shinobi hero.
You've really come far…
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Hidden Leaf Story,
The Perfect Day for a Wedding,
Part 7: The Message
Tune in again!