Anyone here who is
not following this animation?
Dear fellow practitioners from
Class Elite of Faction 60,
welcome to visit my company.
I'm the general manager of Bp Animation.
With over 80 employees,
we are one of the biggest
animation companies in Huaxiu.
We cover key animation, art, 3D,
action, photographing, and everything.
Mr. Surprise of Huaxiu, High Above,
My Unbelievable Magic Ware.
"Down Below" "My Unbelievable Magic Ware"
Those are our early projects.
We are now participating
in the production of
Time Is Like A Sharp Knife and
The Adventure Of The Crown Prince.
Will we have the opportunity
to practice cultivation here?
Of course.
The company has institutes
in many places across Huaxiu.
You can have a complimentary experience
of the art of liver bursting there.
If you have passion for animation,
you are welcome to join us at any time.
All right, here we are.
Welcome to Bp Animation.
The storyboard is such a scribble.
I just can't recognize it.
Where is the director?
It's been 49 days,
and you haven't submitted your materials.
Is this the place
where an animation is made?
"Adapted from the story of the same
title by author Ku Xuan from
Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen Group"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King
Season 2"
"Episode Ten:
Extra: The Director Is Not Home Today"
Sorry, the party you
are calling is in retreat.
- Please dial again one cycle later.
- Damn it.
Let me introduce
the producer of the company.
A project needs the
collaboration of different sections.
Therefore, we need a producer
to coordinate their timetable and staff.
Perfect timing, boss.
She is the producer of the company.
She has very strong capabilities
and is one of the key
employees of the company.
Mr. Tang, the producer seems
to have something to say.
What is it?
Well... Mr. Tang,
the director has run away.
What?
It's going to go online very soon,
and you are telling me
the director has run away.
He was drawing the storyboard in retreat.
Somehow, he seemed to be bewitched.
He rushed out of his room.
God knows where he is now.
What are you waiting for? Go find him.
But someone has got to take
care of the production site.
My fellow practitioners,
now that this is your practice trip,
I'll give you a chance to experience
how it feels to be a director.
Are you serious, Mr. Tang?
Mr. Tang, don't mess around like that.
Don't worry.
Most work of the early phases
has been completed anyway.
The only job left to the
producer is content review.
Think twice, Mr. Tang.
Attention, all sections.
As the old saying goes,
viewers are our best directors.
Our director is not home today,
but we have our fellow practitioners
from Faction 60 visiting our company.
Now let's invite these
Class Elite practitioners
to take over the
director's job, temporarily.
I hope you'll follow their directions.
Am I too late to resign?
"Key Animation"
First, let me show you
the key animation section.
One season of an animation
consists of a dozen episodes.
It is not possible for the
director to attend to every detail.
We therefore need a conductor
to oversee each episode.
Simply put, a conductor can be seen
as the director of each episode.
After meeting with the director,
the conductor will allocate the cuts
to key animators who are good at drawing.
This is terrific.
It's cool.
Did you draw all of these?
That's what a key animator does.
Are you satisfied, acting directors?
Not bad,
but there is a minor problem.
I wonder if I can say it.
Shoot.
There seems to be some frame loss,
and the sketches are kind of scribbled.
It doesn't look like the
animation I watch every day.
I am the initial animator.
The sketches I make will be
modified by the conductor.
Then, the 2nd animator will develop
these sketches into line drawings.
After that, there is the animation
supervisor to modify them,
and assistants to make
the in-between pictures.
It takes so many people
to complete one picture.
Who will be taken responsible
if the picture is ruined?
We have limited manpower.
Films for theaters have developed
to 120 frames per seconds.
How come animations
have lower and lower frame rate?
I remember that
Disney animations are all 24fps,
but other animations are only 8fps.
Films are shot,
while animations are drawn.
You can't require an animator to do that.
Shut up!
You want to see
24fps animations, don't you?
Biblibablibo.
Of all martial arts,
speed beats everything.
This is...
The art of liver bursting.
That's right. You know quite a lot.
The animator enlightened his pen
allowing the digital pen
to draw by itself.
It's a skill only someone of the
golden pill phase can master.
Why don't they draw
like this all the time?
Because this skill
hurts your liver so much
that you'll end up in the
ICU if you use it too often.
Come.
I've made this cut into 24fps.
Oh my god.
Is this the long-lost
full frame animation?
It plays so smoothly.
Acting director,
are you satisfied now?
Probably because
I've played so many 3A games,
I still feel the frame rate is a bit low.
Can you make it 60fps?
What shall we do, Mr. Tang?
Another key animator is down.
It seems that 60fps
animations do not exist.
You want to see 60fps animations?
This is the photographing section.
After receiving the backgrounds
and the key animations you just saw,
"Open " "Abort"
photographing uses post-composite
software to combine them
and make the pictures move.
Special effects like blur
or fireworks-like water surface
are also post-composite's job.
Photographing and composite cannot be done
until all other materials are finished.
Normally, photographers
are in a state of dormancy.
When the time to go online comes close,
the producer will wake them up.
All right. Come on.
It's time to witness the miracle.
Is this some kind of magic?
No.
This is an AI complement frame plug-in.
60fps is a small case.
I can create 120fps,
even 1,200fps if you want.
Then why do they go to great pains
to draw the pictures by hand?
That's because AI has problems like this,
only that at such a high frame rate,
nobody notices it.
Are you satisfied now,
frame rate detective?
I think animations made by
a computer don't have souls in them.
You do it if you can.
Come on. Come into my body
and make animations with souls.
You do it if you can.
- Come on. Come into my body
and make animations with souls.
- Do you feel it, master?
"Scene"
Next, I'll show you our art section.
Is this the great man in his infancy?
The art section's job
is not just drawing the scenes.
It determines the artistic
style of a production.
For example, a scene about vigorous
youth is best depicted by a golden dusk,
while sad stories are usually
set in a gloomy rainy day.
Coming up with convincing scenes
requires accumulation of numerous
materials and long-time experience.
If you have any comments on art, please...
I beg you, Mr. Tang.
No more comments.
Mr. Zhu has been exhausting
his liver for over half a year.
He can't hold on much longer
no matter what a high status he has.
All right. I appreciate
your hard work, Mr. Zhu.
When this episode is completed,
go back to your hometown to get married.
- Mr. Zhu.
- I didn't mean to do it.
What is it, Brother Wang?
Master, the total value of the world's
spiritual force is dropping rapidly.
There is nothing I can do now.
We've lost so many hands.
This episode will never be done.
Don't give up, producer.
You need more hands, and you have us.
You?
That's right.
We've been learning quickly when
we were touring around your company.
We have full knowledge
of the production process now.
But it takes at least 30 years' endeavors
to make a qualified key animator.
Miss Wong, don't forget,
when our company started,
we were exactly like what they are.
We grew from green hands that didn't
know anything to what we are now.
Bravo. Good for you.
Look at the sincerity
and enthusiasm in their eyes.
That's the passion for animation.
We must have belief in these youngsters.
They are the future of Huaxiu.
On your desk, you should have
your part of the storyboard.
Draw your picture as
described in the storyboard.
What's this?
Sometimes the director is busy,
so the storyboard he made
might be kind of scribbled.
Needs key animator's
improvision for 30 seconds.
What the hell is this?
Some directors are not good
at drawing action scenes,
so they will ask the key animators
who are good at it to improvise.
Oh my God. It's so difficult.
All I need to do is trace
the original picture.
Why is it still so difficult?
Of course it is.
Beginners are required to practice drawing
solid lines in their first 3 months,
countless circles and straight lines,
until they can draw proper lines
without any zigzags.
I don't have a talent for drawing.
My pen is moving by itself.
Whatever I have in my mind,
my pen draws it by itself.
This is...
The art of liver bursting?
No, I previewed the art of
enlightenment for the next semester.
No worries about my hand trembling.
You are a genius, Brother Wang.
"Key Animation"
Here are the key animations, Supervisor.
Please modify them.
Producer, why must the supervisor
modify the key animations?
Different animators draw
the same face with slight differences.
In the best cases, the supervisor
just modifies the outline of the face
to unify the style.
But key animators nowadays
are not all that good.
In that case, the supervisor
will have to modify the head and hands,
sometimes even the whole picture.
If the key animation is worse than that,
the supervisor will give his comments
and ask the animator to redraw it.
No way.
It takes so long to draw a picture.
It's going to take forever to redraw it.
I don't believe it.
I won't allow such twisted
things to exist in my computer.
"twisted"
"twisted things"
It's so difficult to make an animation.
There's really nothing I can do now.
What shall we do, master?
The total value of the world's
spiritual force is coming to 0.
The dimensions are going to collapse.
The world is destroyed again.
Producer, where is the director?
They are working so hard.
Are you ready, master?
The battle is about to begin.
When are you going
to finish the storyboard, director?
In a minute.
The director is back.
Conductor, how are
the key animations going?
How many scene cuts are not done yet?
Move the lips 2 frames
backward in this cut.
He's so professional.
This is a genuine director.
Thank you all
for creating this beautiful world.