Anyone here who is not
following this animation?
Richman, what... what are you doing?
I understand it now, finally.
Our real enemy is not
the Sun's descendants.
It's that sidekick.
He is the real wolf
pretending to be a dog.
But you can't destroy
the human world like that.
We must conquer it.
My counsellor, let him go.
Well...
Yes, Your Majesty.
Thank you...
...Your Majesty.
This time I'm on it personally.
I will not miss it again.
While I die, I will drag the
human world along with me.
"Songhai Department Store"
"Little Raccoon"
Richman.
My counsellor,
light the dimensional lamps.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Brother Wang,
it's not easy to come
up to Fort Skyloop.
Why don't we hang around here
for a while before we go back?
Let's go, Brother Wang.
I have a strange feeling.
What happened to us?
We've...
...become three-dimensional.
Wait a minute.
It is still normal outside the window.
"Adapted from the story of the same
title by author Ku Xuan from
Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen Group"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King
Season 2"
"Episode Eleven: The Coming"
Why didn't you set up a spiritual
formation and have this meeting online?
I was practicing cultivation
hard in my retreat.
I almost got bewitched breaking
out of retreat all of a sudden.
It must have been the interferences
from the meteor shower
that cut communications
from Fort Skyloop.
It's such a critical moment
and you only think of you retreat.
The demons are rushing
to the human world.
Send the Seven-Star Squad.
What does the Department
of Cultivation feed you for?
Most of the squad members
are busy evacuating citizens.
They can't launch an
effective counter strike for now.
Are we just going to
sit here, to be beaten?
I've got a plan, but―
Say it.
The spatial crack through which
the demons invade us this time
is right above Faction 60.
And on the schoolyard is a
doom breaking formation I set up.
Three months ago in this formation,
a cultivation practitioner
initiated unbelievable
thunder strikes.
Do you mean
if we find a powerful
cultivation practitioner
and put him in the formation
to function as a battery,
we'll be able to initiate
thunders and kill the demons?
That's right.
This plan requires
massive spiritual energy.
However, we've lost contact
with world's No. 1 practitioner
"World's No. 1 Practitioner"
What do we need that coward for?
He never shows up.
You want spiritual energy,
and I have it.
But your status is not high
enough to be world's No. 1.
Shut up!
I'll show it to you
that I am as good as
this No. 1 practitioner.
Go, Ocean.
Ocean has completed a loop.
That means
we cannot get out of this
passage, forward or backward.
Let's try the sides.
Sides?
I'll break through the wall.
But it's outer space outside the wall.
Don't worry.
The Guardian Light will protect you.
Great. There's a passage next door.
Wait a minute.
There's somebody over there.
This is... This is impossible.
What is going on?
We are trapped in a spatial cycle.
What are we going to do?
Jingke could break the
dimensional wall if he were here.
Master, why did you throw me so far?
My counsellor's
dimensional seal is a wonder.
It traps our greatest threat
from the human world
with just 3,090 dimensional lamps.
My noble Emperor of Demons, Sire,
Apart from dimensional
spiritual treasures,
nothing can break my
three-dimensional seal.
But 30 of the lamps were
knocked over accidentally.
The remaining 3,060 lamps cannot power
the formation to its full function.
Just a few lamps.
No hurt will be done.
How is the battle going
on in the human world?
Master Zhuo,
you have successfully
attracted the demons' hatred.
Have the civilians
been evacuated?
Almost.
And the doom breaking formation?
Is it ready?
Construction will be completed soon.
We just need to wait...
Hello? A-34. Hello?
A huge portal formation has
just appeared above Songhai.
Thousands of demons are rushing
in through this spatial crack.
At the moment, the Seven-Star Squad
is fighting the demons in the urban area.
All citizens, please follow
the Squad's instructions
and evacuate the central area.
We must go now, darling.
Lingling. Where is Lingling?
You're not supposed
to worry about him.
Sounds right.
Back to where we started.
Brother Wang,
are we going to be trapped
here for the rest of our life?
Moreover,
even if we were able to get out of here,
the human world would
have been destroyed.
I got it.
You got what?
"Setup"
"Visual | Interface | Audio | Operation"
I've pulled up the control panel.
Control panel. What is it?
Edit.
Polygon.
Brother Wang,
we are high modulus now,
and our actions are smooth like silk.
I‘ve adjusted to
highest picture quality
and removed the limit on frame rate.
Wait.
What is happening now down there?
You foolish humans. You are surrounded.
Put down your weapons
and surrender to me.
Surrounded?
Don't you see you are
the ones that are surrounded?
Thunders biblibablibo. Go!
These are doom breaking
thunders of the highest level.
They are catastrophic to you demons.
Attention, Seven-Star Squad.
Protect the great master.
Yes.
"IMMORTAL"
One of the great masters
is taking action.
We will win soon.
Something is not right.
Brother Wang,
how can we possibly lose
with the thunders to our aid?
They erected the flag.
It's getting interesting.
What the...
Finished. All finished
The world... is destroyed.
Wait. It can still be saved.
Brother Wang,
we have tried it many times.
We can't get out of here by lift.
The lift is not the point.
Brother Wang,
what do you take off the mirror for?
This seal is like a
3D game in principle.
The world as we see it
is rendered in real time.
I see. No wonder it stuttered.
There was some frame loss.
I got it.
If we overload the graphics card,
the seal will crumble.
That's right.
What crashes rendering
most effectively is...
...a mirror.
What... What is going on?
It's working, Brother Wang.
Frame loss is becoming
more and more apparent.
Sun Rong, call out your Ocean.
Now I see it.
Brother Wang wants to utilize
Ocean's particle effect.
Damn it.
Air cooling is not sufficient.
Ray tracing...
...on.
What the...
This is impossible.
My 3060!
We did it, Brother Wang.
The spatial seal is removed.
Sun Rong, wait here.
I'm going to save the world.
If you go back now,
your identity will be revealed.
I don't care.
It's showdown time.
Master.
My master is back.
The battle in Songhai
took a sharp turn.
The demon carrier
that had just landed
was sunk by a
mysterious practitioner.
Who is he?
Breaking news.
The mysterious practitioner who
had just sunk the demon carrier
was taken away by a butterfly girl.
Master. Where has he gone?