My counselor, why is there a whine
in the abyss of my holy throne?
My noble Emperor of Demons, Sire,
deep in the abyss there appeared
a crack that leads to the human world.
The human world?
I remember having sent one of the
demon kings to conquer the human world.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The one that was sent three years ago
was my humble apprentice, the Giant Frog.
Of all the demon kings,
he is the most ferocious.
So soft.
So lovely.
Feels so good.
It's three demon years already,
but the Giant Frog hasn't
presented the human world to me.
Besides,
I can feel that the hole
that leads to the human world
is absorbing the spiritual
energy of my world.
Backfire?
That shouldn't be happening.
I wanted to conquer the human world
so that I could have its
abundant spiritual energy.
Is their Gross Spiritual Force
Product lower than ours now?
What is that good-for-nothing
Giant Frog doing over there?
I will go to the human
world right away personally
to pay my useless
apprentice a home visit.
"Notice: Home Visit By Your Master"
"Ignore"    "Accept"
"Adapted from the story of the same
title by author Ku Xuan from
Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen Group"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King
Season 2"
"Episode Two:
A Home Visit By The Demon Master"
Worldwide atmospheric spiritual
energy has been dropping for days,
which has resulted in worsened
immortal herb harvest.
Due to material shortages
in the pill refinery industry,
- Coming.
- the price of magic pills keeps rising.
Here is an exclusive
interview by our reporters.
Coming.
Nobody is here.
It's Froggy 2.
Come on in.
Herb harvest is very bad.
Please help us.
What are you doing here?
I... I missed you.
"Calmness Brings Happiness"
Why do you want to give Wang Ling
a home visit all of a sudden?
His scores had been the
lowest last semester.
I had thought he would be reallocated
to Class Ordinary after the test.
Are you suspecting that
he cheated in the test?
No.
After his test,
"Due"
the cost of spiritual energy
in our faction skyrocketed,
which is almost bankrupting us.
I wish you a smooth home visit.
I'm leaving now.
Instructor Wang,
aren't coming along?
Sorry,
I have some personal
matters to attend to.
The spiritual force in the
human world feels so nice.
Incoming.
No, wrong number.
"Master  unanswered   2 min"
You little froggy brat. Do you
think you can evade this home visit?
DeCom. Bai De Map. Navigation starts.
Go south. 200 meters.
"Demon Master@Froggy 2"
"3 min ago"
"Demon Master: Here I come, my boy."
"Demon Master@Froggy 2"
"3 min ago"
"Demon Master: Here I come, my boy."
Here I come, my boy.
Who is your master?
He is the aggregation of all
wisdom of the demon world,
an ancient demon that has
lived a million years.
He is as old as the universe,
an immortal being.
Your master is so awesome.
He was my primary instructor
for a few centuries
and that was the most
miserable time in my life.
Even now, he still shows up
frequently in my nightmares.
So, that's why you are
hiding yourself here.
Dinner is ready.
Here.
Lingling, try my newly-developed
spiritual figure after dinner.
Let's hope the problem affecting
your normal speech is solved.
You will give me a hand, Froggy 2.
I do hope it will be a success this time.
The price of magic pills
has gone up sharply.
We could hardly afford
even low-power pills.
By the way, you have been
stuck for quite some time.
How come you came
out of it suddenly?
His remote cousin sent
me some source materials.
I heard that had gone to join
the military in the meta world
and is doing very well.
I wish Lingling could find such
a secure job when he graduates.
Oh, yes. Hurry up with your dinner.
Lingling's instructor is
going to pay a home visit.
Strange. How come there are residues
of Froggy's spiritual energy here?
I use chips of Pu Lao's
horn on these figures.
They should lessen the
inhibition on his speech abilities.
"This Side Down"
Come here, son. Sit down
and sit still. Empty your mind.
Froggy 2, come and help me.
If I weren't evading the home visit,
I wouldn't be here to help you.
Froggy, do exactly what I say.
You take the new figure.
I tear off the old. You put on the new.
Putting it on is easy.
Tearing it off is hard.
Any careless move when tearing it off,
Lingling's spiritual energy will spill,
leading to a catastrophe
that no one can imagine.
Come here. Press on his
acupoint of Baihui and hold.
For five seconds.
"0.4"
"0.5"
Next, press on his acupoints of
Danzhong and Baihui and hold.
For ten seconds.
Last, release his Baihui
and hold on to his
Danzhong for five seconds.
Now.
Success.
What?
It's upside down.
Didn't you see the big red characters?
"This Side Down"
I'm color blind.
Oh my God. I'm done for.
His spiritual energy spills.
The world will be destroyed.
Darling, I love you all my life.
Oh yes. I forgot.
You can devour spiritual energy.
Let me digest it for a while.
It's strange.
Froggy's spirits are so strong,
but I just can't locate him.
Coming.
Instructor Pan.
I've been waiting for you.
Thank you for coming.
Come on in.
Sit down and drink some water.
Froggy 2 is here too.
How are you, Instructor Pan?
Does the new figure work all right?
I don't see any changes in him.
How do you do, Instructor?
Please sit down, Instructor Pan.
Sir and Madam,
I'll cut the cliché and
go straight to the point.
I'm here today to let you know
about Wang Ling's situation at school.
Madam,
Wang Ling's scores last
semester were not satisfactory.
I don't care. It is fine if he can make
some friends and enjoy his time.
Wang Ling didn't finish all the
assignments for the summer vacation.
I've finished all the spiritual
figures for this week.
Do I give them to you now,
or shall I bring them to school tomorrow?
Madam,
Wang Ling didn't do well
in his pill refining practice.
Instructor Pan,
I made these reviving pills
and respiratory pills last semester.
You can try one if you don't mind.
The reason why I'm here today
is that Wang Ling has not been
enthusiastic about his studies.
This is what you asked us to preview.
The art of enlightenment
for this semester.
Turn left.
Actually, one pencil and one eraser
would be enough for school's sake.
- Wang Ling, you did very well in
previewing the art of enlightenment.
- Darling, what spiritual
figures have you developed?
- Wang Ling, you did very well in
previewing the art of enlightenment.
- Is this still our son?
- Wang Ling, you did very well in
previewing the art of enlightenment.
- Excessive emotion adjustment, it seems.
- That's quite a success.
- I hope that on all of the other
subjects, you will do as well as this.
- You try to distract Instructor Pan,
and I'll give him another figure.
- I hope that on all of the other
subjects, you will do as well as this.
Instructor Pan,
this is your first time to visit my home.
Let me show you around the house.
Around the house?
Distance to destination:
unmeasurable.
Froggy,
you are trying to evade me, aren't you?
This way, Instructor Pan.
The kitchen is well decorated, isn't it?
What are they doing?
They are...
They are massaging for milk.
I didn't know dogs do this too.
Yes, they do.
Instructor Pan,
let me show you the second floor.
I've adjusted the logic
for the spiritual figure.
It should be fine now.
Lingling, say something.
Dad, I have a strange feel about this.
Is it my illusion or something?
What illusion?
Instructor Pan, do you like
the decoration of the bedrooms?
It's nice.
This is my first time to see
bedrooms during a home visit.
It's been quite a while.
They should have done it.
- Madam.
- Instructor Pan.
Madam,
you are...
Instructor Pan,
I want to talk to you in private.
Lingling, you've enlightened
all the furniture.
Dad, the spiritual figure has a
deadly bug left from your adjustment.
I can't do anything about it.
Use your invincible power now.
"3 Years Cultivation
5 Years Easy Life"
It's working.
Froggy 2,
let's do it.
My husband and I are
not talented cultivation.
We have been stuck in the body-building
phase and can't break through.
Lingling has very
week spiritual energy.
He hasn't had any
friends all these years.
I don't know how he
made it to Class Elite
and made so many friends there.
Wang Ling has never told
anyone about his history.
I don't expect him to
be an excellent boy,
to be above all others.
I only hope
that he spends every
day of his life happily.
Then I'll be satisfied.
All right.
Back to normal.
Lingling,
stand where you are and don't move.
You have used too much energy.
The spiritual figure is overloaded.
Froggy 2, tear off the figure.
Froggy 2. Froggy 2.
Here...
Here... he comes.
Bai De Map indicates...
You little froggy brat.
I've detected your
spiritual pressure.
Oh no.
I used my spiritual force
and revealed my location.
I'm a dead dog.
Froggy 2, come and save the world.
My boy, here comes your master.
So you've been hiding
in such an awful neighborhood.
"This Side Down"
Lingling, don't move a bit.
It's going to burst up.
I'm coming in, my boy.
Forget it. Just tear it off.
What was the noise?
What happened?
No... nothing.
Thank you so much for the
home visit, Instructor Pan.
You care so much for Lingling.
We appreciate it.
You are welcome.
I didn't know until
after we had that talk
that academic scores are not
the only thing to judge a kid.
I'll concentrate more on the students'
emotional education and growth.
It's late now.
I have to go.
Thank you again, Instructor Pan.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Instructor Pan.
Take care.
Lingling,
you have such a nice instructor.
Did I pass out?
Oh yes. Have you
changed the spiritual figure?
Everything is settled.
Time for me to go home.
Master.