Anyone here who is
not following this animation?
"VOGUE"
Idler, am I beautiful?
We are on a mission now.
Don't show your art of
beautification in public.
I prepared this cheongsam
especially for you.
Don't have anything else
in your mind except work?
Yue,
don't you feel something is unusual?
The Seven-Star Squad that's been following
us. Are they going to make a move?
That was that?
Turbulence. Turbulence.
It spilt on my pants.
"Toilets out of Service"
It startled me.
Dear passengers, the spiritual impulses
in the Songhai airspace are not steady,
causing occasional bumps of the liner.
Please return to your seats
and fasten your seatbelts.
The lady over there,
please return to your seat
and faster your seatbelt.
The passenger over there,
please follow Air Spirits regulations.
Go back to your seat
and fasten your seatbelt.
Shut up.
With the power I've mastered,
do I need to fasten my seatbelt?
Yue.
Idler.
"Adapted from the story of the same
title by author Ku Xuan from
Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen Group"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King
Season 2"
"Episode Three:
The Idle Beauty"
The swordliner with the Idle
Beauty on board crashed.
The world's No. 1 assassin disappeared.
There has been no sign of
him for the last 10 years.
This is the only video
image he left behind.
Was he killed in the crash?
No. Rumor has it that the
Idle Beauty was severely hurt
and has been living in
seclusion in Songhai ever since.
Besides, rumor also has it that
someone saw him near our faction.
Does that mean the Idle
Beauty's secret abode is nearby?
Didn't you hear the bell?
The doom breaking test a
few days ago had a little accident,
but was concluded smoothly.
One of the Class Ordinary
students performed excellently
and is transferred to Class Elite.
Let's show our welcome.
It's a girl. She's so cute.
Oh dear.  Brother Wang's
eyes are on me again.
So he has been
watching me all the time.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Lin Xiaoyu from Phase 2, Class 1.
Lin Xiaoyu has excellent academic scores,
but her family has some difficulties.
So, please take care of her, everybody.
This new girl looks familiar somehow.
Instructor Wang has
something to attend to.
I'll be taking his place today.
Open your books and turn to page 58.
Instructor Wang, how is it going?
120 meters to target.
Her spiritual energy
focus is right ahead.
Be careful, Instructor Wang.
She is a supreme assassin.
And I am a supreme instructor.
You have any doubts
about my capabilities?
All right. Got it.
Target spotted. I'm going to hang up.
Jiang Liuyue, you are surrounded.
Don't make any
meaningless resistance.
Surrender yourself now.
For all these years,
where have you been?
these cultivation cruise fools
haven't had any progress.
That was such an obvious
trick to lure him away,
but he still took the bait.
My silly sister, here I come.
"Sealed Place"
Rumor has it
that after being captured
by the Seven-Star Squad...
...Jiang Liuying has been
imprisoned in faction.
"Gentlemen"
Are you kidding?
With the poor security at Faction 60,
there is no way to keep her securely here.
Don't forget
that the Giant Frog was sealed
underground at Faction 60.
That's why rumor has it
that there is a giant
supreme jail at our faction,
a jail of a high level, enough
to suppress a demon king.
That was the lady in the photo.
What are you waiting for? Go after her.
Where is she?
This is a lumber room, isn't it?
Where is the lady we just saw?
It seems that someone lives here.
Is this Idle Beauty's secret abode?
Interesting.
The owner must've been hiding in
this place for quite some time.
He doesn't tidy his bed.
He doesn't empty his trash bin.
What an idle life for
world's No. 1 assassin.
Somebody is coming.
The Idle Beauty is back.
Let's hide. Now.
Who is there?
We...
We didn't mean to pry.
That's right.
You psychos.
You... What's your name...
Little sister, I can explain.
Her name is Lin Xiaoyu.
What are you doing in my room?
What? Isn't this the Idle
Beauty's secret abode?
Isn't it? We didn't know you lived
in such a messy place.
None of your business.
What are you doing here?
I missed my lovely little sister.
Isn't it OK if I come to pay her a visit?
Where are the guards
of the supreme jail?
Those useless things
have nothing to stop me.
Good. Sister, remove my restraints.
We can join our forces
and revive the Shadow Faction.
My silly little sister,
do you think I broke into
the supreme jail to save you?
In Cultivation Year 4396,
there was a contract to
assassinate Ms. Sun Rong.
Did you fulfill it?
So, you were sent here by party A.
How did you get involved with them?
Mission unaccomplished.
You should know the consequences.
It was nothing but a mission of the
demon world. Kill me if you dare.
Before I do that,
I want to settle a score.
Sorry. Keep going.
Master, I've found a secure room.
Good.
Finally landed.
What is this place?
It's so dark.
I can see anything.
You rascal. Take your hand away.
My goodness.
Is this place...
"B"
the Idle Beauty's secret abode?
Did you pick this room on purpose?
In other rooms, there are
either traps or fierce beasts.
This is the only one secure.
This is the Li's Kitchen Knife
that the Idle Beauty uses.
It seems that the rumors are true.
Have a look over here.
Isn't this the legendary wall of clues?
Is the Idle Beauty
investigating something special?
A swordliner crash 10 years ago.
In-fighting of the Shadow Faction.
Changes of Senior Personnel.
Wait a minute.
This lady. Isn't she...?
I met the Idle Beauty
on one of my missions,
and fell for his
unspeakable features.
We began to join
hands in our actions.
We traveled on lands
and oceans near and far,
and I became leader
of the Shadow Faction.
That was the
climax of my life.
It gave me the best memories
of the 100 years I've lived...
...until...
...that incident deprived
me of everything.
Ten years. I dropped into the demon
world and endured it for 10 years.
I was separated from the
one I loved for 10 years,
and spent every day in pains.
I was locked in that sick palace,
translating documents of
the human and demon worlds.
One day I camp upon
an assassination contract
assigned to the Shadow
Faction by the demon world.
"Contract"
"Party A"
"Party B: Jiang Liuying"
Then I realized
it was you
who blew up the
swordliner with me on board
and seized my position as the
leader of the Shadow Faction!
Sister, I did intend to seize
your position at some point,
but the crash had
nothing to do with me.
Shup up.
The demon world has sent me
to get rid of you the traitor.
Farewell, leader of the Shadow Faction.
Who is that?
That was not the truth of
the incident 10 years ago,
Yue.
Come on.
Let's straighten out the information.
First, time, which is 10 years ago.
"60 Songhai"
"Faction 42"   "Songhai Faction"
Then, place, Songhai Faction 60,
which is the coordinates
we are sitting on.
At that time in this place,
three things happened.
The first thing.
The swordliner with the Idle Beauty and
the leader of the Shadow Faction on board
was hit in the air above Faction 60.
The leader of the Shadow Faction
wasn't wearing her seatbelt
and was thrown out of the liner,
thus becoming the only
passenger that was missing.
The second thing.
Do you remember what happened
in Songhai 10 years ago?
Do you mean the
invasion of the Giant Frog?
That's right.
At that time, the portal to the alien
world opened right above Faction 60.
What is the third thing?
On that day, Master Zhuo beat the
Giant Frog with only one blow of his fist.
I'm beginning to understand everything.
Look. What's that?
Run.
Give your spiritual force to me.
Come on.
A side dish has delivered itself.
Yue.
Idler.
"Little Raccoon"
I hate being bothered while
I'm eating crispy noodles.
Yue.
Then the Idle Beauty set up a
secret base under Faction 60
to wait for the return
of his companion.
That was the truth behind everything.
The world's No. 1 assassin
is such a spoony man.
The Idle Beauty waited for 10 years.
Yue, I concealed my identity
and waited in the exact
place where I lost you.
Finally, I see you today.
Kang,
You've gained so much weight.
To ease the pain of losing you,
I devoured foods
whenever I felt downhearted.
The thick fat reflects my
heavy thoughts for you.
Kang.
First you came out of
nowhere to kill me for nothing,
and now you are showing your
love right in front of my eyes.
I'd rather you kill me now.
Kang, do you still remember
you said that you would take me
to see the stars and the moon,
to play on the swing, and to
swing to the end of the world.
I'm taking you now to
the stars and the moon,
to play on the swing.
That's enough.
Somebody please kill me.
I had thought we would be trapped
in the secret abode forever.
Thank God Wang Ling found the
elevator behind the bookcase.
And I cut classes the first day
I was transferred to Class Elite.