Anyone here who is not
following this animation?
Who was it?
Who the hell was it
that transformed my Ring of
Chaos into this vulgar sword.
Soul Search.
I'm sorry, Sister Lin.
We just learned to forge it from the
tutorial in the Know-How sector, so...
Thanks to His Majesty
the Emperor of Demons,
the offspring of that
monkey is brought to me.
The time has come.
Tomorrow night,
I'll avenge my demon race.
"Adapted from the story of the same
title by author Ku Xuan from
Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen Group"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King
Season 2"
"Episode Five:
The Four Bizarre Tales of Faction 60"
You wanted to see me, A?
What is it?
This... This sachet is for you.
A went for it. She went for it.
Did you make it yourself?
Is this sachet for school work
or for wellness?
What are you doing?
This campus is a place for
cultivation, not for fun and joy.
You are supposed to concentrate on
your studies, not on well-wishing sachets.
Confiscated.
Today is the Autumn Reunion Day.
"Knowledge Has No Boundaries"
Cultivators give well-wishing sachets
they make themselves to their friends.
Legends say whoever gives out sachets
will get whatever he wishes for.
All his dreams will come true.
Please give it back to me, Instructor.
I'll never do it again.
- Oh, no. Instructor Wang is here.
How am I going to give out my sachet?
- Today is the Autumn Reunion Day.
Please spare me just once. Please.
You can wait until he gets off work.
It's Xiaoyu.
But students are not allowed to be
on campus at night, aren't they?
Have you forgotten about it, Sister Sun?
I live on campus.
"Sealed Place"
My feeling is right.
The total value of the world's
spiritual force has dropped.
The refrains on the
supreme jail are week.
Have you given out your sachet, A?
It was confiscated by Instructor Wang.
Why don't you ask him to meet
at the Mirror of Moon Bridge?
No. It's too scary on campus at night.
The Mirror of Moon Bridge.
What is that?
You don't know about it, do you?
It is one of the four bizarre
tales of this faction.
Legend has it that at
midnight on August 7th,
if you go to the grooming
mirror on the first floor,
you'll see your future.
Today is the 6th.
There must be a lot of people
coming on campus tonight.
No.
According to senior girls,
many supernatural things
happen on that night.
Supernatural things?
Such as a spiritual girl
singing at midnight,
an uncanny hand out of
the toilet, a lift leading to hell.
Wise men never talk about weird things.
Stop your bullshit, Guo Hao.
Apparently, they are not true.
I guess whoever made up these
tales just wanted to scare people.
"Little Raccoon"
Tap the head three times
and close the back door.
I wonder if Brother Wang understands it.
At midnight. Back door of campus.
It's a hint, Brother Wang.
Back door? A hint? What does it mean?
Brother Wang.
Great. Brother Wang does understand it.
But...
...why the two of you are also here?
It's midnight. Brother Wang may run
into some danger if he comes alone.
That's right. He will be
more daring if we are all here.
I hope you don't mind, Sister Sun.
Of course not.
It's more fun if we go on
the adventure together.
Darn it. How am I going
to give out my sachet?
Wait. It's dark here.
"Gentlemen"
The campus does feel evil at night.
Wh... What's that noise?
Relax, Chief Chen. It was just a wild cat.
What? Are you so scared of a wild cat?
Nonsense. I'm not scared at all.
Come on. I'll lead the way.
Wait a minute, Chief Chen.
What is it?
None of you dares to follow me?
Ghost. Ghost.
You said you were not scared. Look at you.
It's Lin Xiaoyu.
Xiaoyu lives on campus,
so I asked her to be our guide.
I'm sorry to have
scared you, Chief Chen.
I... I'm fine.
How come your hand is so cold?
Here it comes.
One of the bizarre tales of Faction 60,
a spiritual girl laughing.
All right.
Next, how do I get
out of the supreme jail?
The laugh was horrifying.
It almost scared the shit out of me.
Same here. Is there really
a spiritual girl on campus?
Of course not.
It's more like some
other girls playing pranks.
It's so late at night. Who else
can be on campus except Xiaoyu?
G-Guo...
Don't panic.
Chen Chao. Are you all right, Chen Chao?
What's happening?
Could it be the uncanny
hand out of the toilet?
Chen Chao? What happened
to you, Chen Chao?
Be careful, Brother Wang.
Finally... coming out.
"B"
What is this place?
It has my sister's smell.
Wonderful. There is a lift.
What happened in the toilet?
Why did they pass out?
The toilet leaks. They fell.
So Chief Chen's meta spirit
was knocked out of him?
It doesn't matter.
They will come to in an
hour with these figures on.
We have nothing else to do,
so let's go on with the adventure.
But they haven't come to yet.
That's right. They haven't come to yet.
Right.
This is the perfect time for me
to be with Brother Wang alone.
Master, the leader of the
Shadow Faction has escaped again.
Where are you going, Brother Wang?
After I go out, shall I terminate
Zhuo Yi or my sister?
Right. It should be Miss Sun.
Come on. Forget the sequence.
All those who disrespect me must die.
What happened, Brother Wang?
Why is there such a big hole on the floor?
This must be the lift leading to hell.
Another bizarre tale verified.
There is only the
Mirror of Moon Bridge left.
I'm going to use the restroom.
Sister Sun, you go ahead
with Brother Wang first.
All right.
Watch out for the uncanny
hand out of the toilet, Xiaoyu.
Master, what is this demon up to?
She is not really helping
Sister Sun, is she?
Don't worry. You have me here.
It'll be midnight soon.
When the portal opens,
I'll take this little girl
to the demon world.
Your ancestor killed so many members of
the demon race on his way to the west.
Tonight, your Sun family
will pay for it with your life.
Finally surfacing.
Isn't that...
What bloody luck I have,
Miss Sun.
The crystal bridge leading from
the human world to the Moon broke,
and the fragments
fell to the human world.
This Mirror of Moon Bridge
is said to have been forged
from those fragments.
Legend has it that the mirror has
the magic of transcending space.
At midnight on August 7th,
if you go in front of the mirror,
the magic mirror will reflect your future.
It's almost midnight now.
Brother Wang Ling...
...this... this is...
Brother Wang Ling.
Sister Sun, I'm back.
This mirror has the magic
of transcending space.
The human world uses it
to restrain the crack in time and
space leading to the demon world.
I can now use it to open the
portal to the demon world.
I don't think your human race
has ever expected that.
Miss Sun,
welcome to the demon world.
Miss Sun is mine.
I will not let that happen again.
I don't believe it,
you good-for-nothing value 5.
Brother Wang,
my sachet.
"Diligence Pays Off"
I've got it.