Anyone here who is
not following this animation?
Hello. Is that Mr. Ma?
Yes, this is Sun speaking.
Excuse me for calling you at such
a late hour, and sorry for bothering you.
You must have heard
that the spiritual force chain of my
company ran into some problems recently.
I need a sum of spiritual energy
urgently to save my company.
We were schoolmates
and have been good friends.
Besides, the sum I need is not too much,
just around 200 million
spiritual energy.
Your dad can take care of it, madam.
Why don't you go back to
your room and have a good rest?
What?
What do you mean you'll think about it?
I'm in difficulty now.
Aren't you going to give me a hand?
Hey, don't hang up.
Ungrateful bastard.
I checked in for him
whenever he cut a class.
Look what he is doing to me now.
Mr. Sun, sorry to
bother you late at night.
This is a notice from
the Songhai court of law.
The liquidation will be
carried out tomorrow.
Please be there on time.
"Adapted from the story of the same
title by author Ku Xuan from
Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen Group"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King"
"The Daily Life of the Immortal King
Season 2"
"Episode Seven:
The Worker Bee Spirit in the Sun Family"
Are you sure this is
Sun Rong's native place?
Of course, I followed map directions.
"Flower Fruit Water Curtain"
It's such a big mountain.
How can we find Sister Sun?
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Sister Sun,
we know your family
failed in doom breaking,
but that doesn't mean you have
to go back to the stone age.
What else can we do?
We have mortgaged everything else.
This ancestral property
is all that's left.
Why did this happen all of a sudden?
The Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group
is a pharmaceutical company
focusing on magic pills.
The drop of the total value
of the world's spiritual energy
brought about poor
immortal herb harvest, so...
Don't worry, Rongrong.
Remember that our Sun family thrived
in this small place in the first place.
Our company is just the
mover of the spiritual vein.
This is nothing but coming
back to the starting point.
The herbs may be gone,
but we can plant more.
We may be short of money,
but we can make more.
If we keep on working hard
generation after generation,
the Sun family will rise again someday.
Is this the hardworking
worker bee spirit?
Worker bee spirit.
I like the expression.
To the worker bee spirit.
Cheers.
The Sun family is down.
The two families have been fighting
for over one thousand years,
and finally, our Tang
family has the last laugh.
Thanks to Uncle Richman
for operating the stocks
and helping us short sell the
Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group.
It was nothing but a
game of spiritual capitals.
The total value of the world's
spiritual energy is at a low level,
but the price of their stocks
was unreasonably high.
If I spread some negative information
and dumped the great number of
shares I had stealthily bought earlier,
all the other major shareholders would
definitely jump off board to survive.
But remember,
the spiritual vein of
Mt. Flower Fruit is still there.
We must continue our scheme as planed
in order to eliminate the
Sun family once and for all.
Thank you for your advice, Uncle Richman.
May I know why you are offering
this great help to the Tang family?
Because I need the spiritual energy.
Back then,
the Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group
was the biggest enterprise in Huaxiu.
It had tens of thousands of employees,
and was the center of national attention.
What are you thinking of?
Brother Wang,
look at this.
What clear spiritual spring water.
Actually, this is the curtain
of the Water Curtain Cave.
There used to be a waterfall
hanging at the cave entrance.
but now there is just this
tiny amount of water left.
When the pool down there dries out,
the spiritual vein of
Mt. Flower Fruit will be cut off, too.
We can help you.
Thank you for your
kindness, Brother Wang.
The Sun family may
have lost everything,
but we still have
our worker bee spirit.
From now on,
I will depend on myself.
Time to go, Wang Ling.
How are we going back?
By the light rail or taxi?
What's the matter with you?
Don't you watch
the road when driving?
Are all drivers so bad nowadays?
Damn it.
I had thought Sister Sun would be
depressed because of the bankruptcy.
Seeing her family's worker bee spirit,
you have nothing to worry about.
A lean camel is bigger than a horse.
Her family may be bankrupt,
but they still have this magic mountain.
We now bring you breaking news.
A moment ago,
Tang's Finance announced
that it would take over the
Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group
at a cost of 140 billion spiritual energy.
The takeover ceremony
will be held tomorrow
at the Water Curtain Cave
of Mt. Flower Fruit.
The heirs to both companies
will sign a bloodborne agreement
at the takeover ceremony.
Sun Rong will sign a bloodborne
agreement with that Tang Birdie 2?
We just came back from her place.
How could this have
happened so abruptly?
The number you are
calling is out of service.
I can't get through to her.
There must be something wrong.
Let's go back and ask about it.
Do you remember the limo
when we were leaving?
Of course. It was going
very fast on a country road
and almost hit me.
"TANG"
"Tang's Finance"
It belonged to Tang Birdie 2's family.
Sun Rong must have been
forced to agree to sign this.
What shall we do now?
Set off to Mt. Flower Fruit.
"Flower Fruit Water Curtain"
"Tang's Finance"
What a blessed Flower Fruit place
and a scenic Water Curtain Cave.
It's a pity that you used such
a nourishing spiritual vein
to grow primitive immortal herbs.
Level these woods.
Plant chives instead.
No, you can't do that.
There are herbs of hundreds,
even thousands of years old.
That is why your Flower Fruit Water
Curtain Group has gone bankrupt.
It takes natural immortal herbs
a hundred years to mature.
Chives, however, grow all year round, and
can be harvested five or six times a year.
With proper care, each harvest
produces more than the one before it.
B-But it will exhaust the aura
of the spiritual vein in the end.
Do you care about what the chives think?
Here they come.
Are you here for Miss
Sun's signing ceremony?
I suggest you be nice and
move your ass out of the way.
Weren't you beaten badly enough
at the sword competition?
I don't know whether you
cheated or used other means
to drive me out of
the competition field.
Today,
I must take my revenge.
First, I'd like to thank you
all for coming here today.
As you all know,
the Sun and Tang families have had
grudges for over a thousand years.
But today, all those
grudges will be history.
Tang's Enterprise will take over
the Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group.
My humble son and the daughter of the Sun
family will sign a bloodborne agreement.
We have double happiness today,
so, I invite all of you
to join me in a toast
to celebrate this joyful moment.
Cheers.
Wait a minute. Something is not right.
One of them is missing.
Where is the value 5?
Brother Wang,
we'll leave Sister Sun to you.
Now let's invite the two
parties to sign the agreement.
"Party A:
Party B: Tang Jingze"
Your turn, Miss Sun.
Come on, Miss Sun. Sign it.
Brother Wang.
Go after her.
Don't worry.
I'll get you out of here.
Wang Ling, we won.
Sun Rong!
Have you forgotten what
you promised yesterday?
I'm sorry, Brother Wang.
It's out of my own will.
Sun Rong, don't talk bull shit.
I don't believe signing that bloodborne
agreement is out of your own free will.
Yesterday, right after you left...
Mr. Sun,
I heard the Flower Fruit
Water Curtain Group
was not doing very good
business these days.
Are you here to humiliate us?
No, no, no.
On the contrary,
my Tang's Enterprise is willing to invest
in your Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group.
Go straight to the point, Mr. Tang.
At what cost?
Simple.
Your daughter and my son
Jingze sign a bloodborne agreement.
No way.
We would rather farm
the land here all life long
than bow to your Tang family.
Exactly.
Let me know the details
of your proposal.
Rongrong, think about it.
Even though we work
as hard as worker bees,
it will still take hundreds of years
for the Flower Fruit Water Curtain
Group to recover its business.
To make matters worse,
the water curtain is drying out.
Mt. Flower Fruit has no future.
But, Father,
my future is for me to decide.
What about the worker
bee spirit in our family?
The Sun family must take care of
more people than just the three of us.
The Flower Fruit Water Curtain Group
has tens of thousands of employees.
Every one of them has his own family.
Have you ever thought about it?
If the Sun family goes down,
your Uncle Sun and his wife,
what will happen to them?
After what happened yesterday,
I became aware that
as the heir to the Sun family,
I must not only enjoy
my status as its daughter.
I must also fulfill my
obligations as an heir.
If sacrificing myself
can get the happiness of
the whole family in return,
then that's the route I'll take.
Madam.
Sorry,
Wang Ling and everyone.
Which faction are you from?
I'll call the police if you don't leave.
Just the few of you inferiors
and you want to
fight the Tang family.
Being wealthy doesn't mean
you can do whatever you want.
Sorry. Being wealthy does
mean I can do whatever I want.
What are you doing, Brother Wang?
What is that?
Isn't it... a starworm?
What is a starworm?
It's a fearful subterranean
ancient demon
that sucks earth's spiritual vein.
Is this the cause of the exhaustion
of Mt. Flower Fruit's spiritual vein?
They found out about it.
But it's too late.
The starworm has sucked all
the spiritual vein of Mt. Flower Fruit.
I have transferred
the spiritual capital to...
Wait a minute.
Why is the spiritual
energy flowing back?
The Sun family may
have lost everything,
but we still have our worker bee spirit.
From now on,
I will depend on myself.
Sun Rong family's spiritual vein.
Give it back.
Oh no. It's going to collapse.
"Asset Transfer Agreement"
Now let's have the two parties
press their bloodborne fingerprints.
That's the right thing to do.
The waterfall of the Water
Curtain Cave is flowing backward.
Don't panic, everyone.
Some minor incidents
happened outside.
Nothing serious.
Let's go on with the ceremony.
Something is wrong, boss.
Tang's Finance has triggered the
circuit breaker on the stock market.
What?
Great news, madam.
The Flower Fruit Water Curtain
is rebounding on the stock market.
Mr. Tang,
we found Tang's Enterprise
in collusion with the demon world.
We have frozen the suspicious capital.
"Investigation Warrant
Seven-Star Squad
(Sever-Star Internet Information Center)"
It can't be.
The Sun family's spiritual
vein will be revived.
Where is Wang Ling?
You were crazy, madam.
- Why did you do that?
- It's all over, madam.
It's all over.