Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
It Rains, and Shirota Freezes Up
It rains, and Shirota freezes up.
Today is the day when President
is helping me study...
or it was supposed to be...
Wow, Takane-chan, your room is super tidy!
Actually, I gotta thank you for not only
letting me crash your study group,
but also lending me a notebook!
About 30 minutes back...
As I was on my way to President's house,
I randomly ran into Ellie-chan.
When I told her about the plan of
having a study group at President's house,
she badgered me into letting her join as well,
and so here we are.
So we're starting with math?
That's good. I'm not so good at it,
so I was hoping you could teach me, Takane-chan.
President clearly looks displeased.
I guess she really doesn't feel
comfortable with Ellie...
Ellie-san,
if you need to study,
wouldn't it be more fruitful if you
let your girlfriend teach you?
If she's willing to date someone as vulgar—
pardon, wrong word—
a girl as sweet as you,
she will surely teach you
with the utmost magnanimity.
Oh, you mean Rurika?
Yeah, she's been so busy with her
job lately that she barely hangs out with me.
Well, if you are looking for playmates,
why don't you try the kindergarten?
The hostility is off the charts!
Wait, did she say "girlfriend"?
Not boyfriend?
That reminds me,
Ellie-chan did say in grade school
that she liked girls better than boys.
I already have a question.
These trigonometric addition formulas...
High School Mathematics II
I don't have a clue what's going on here.
She touched her?
No, that was just accidental...
She did it on purpose?!
Wait, did Ellie-chan come here today
to do something to President, then?
No, no. I'm reading into it too much.
Shirota-kun.
Y-Yes?
Could I ask you to go to the convenience
store to get some drinks and snacks?
Oh, then please get some for me too!
Uh...
Won't it be all kinds of bad
to leave these two alone...?
But...
Now.
Yes!
This is perfect.
There's something I want
to talk to you about privately.
What a coincidence. There's
something I'd like to say, too.
I'll cut to the chase.
Could you please go home?
Overseeing both of your studies
at once is just too bothersome.
I bet it is. I'm really sorry.
I'll go home after I ask my question.
What is it?
Are you and Kou-chan already going out?
What?
Why exactly would I have to be dating
someone like Shirota-kun?
So you're saying you're not dating yet?
Weren't you listening to me?
I can't control what your imagination cooks up,
but please don't try to shove that onto me.
Oh, it's fine, you don't have to hide it.
But I said—
But you know...
Kou-chan seems pretty dense.
I bet you have it rough.
Kou-chan has low self-esteem,
so I bet he doesn't even realize that you're
putting out signals that you like him,
no matter how hard you try.
Now that you mention it...
No matter how boldly or how
determinedly I put a move on him,
his reactions are so muted,
I feel like he's not seeing me as a girl...
It makes me feel insecure.
Oh, I knew it!
... That's what a friend said when she
came to me for advice.
The way she covered it up
so obviously is so freaking cute!
So what kinds of moves
did that friend of yours make?
Well, from what I heard,
she tried cuddling up to him in cat cosplay,
suddenly joined him
while he was taking a bath...
I'm so jealous!
I mean, it makes sense to lose
confidence as a girl
if his response is muted when
you go to those lengths, right?
By the way,
this friend is so absolutely gorgeous
that wars could be started over her.
That's nuts!
It's weird that he hasn't done anything yet!
Y-You think so too?
Crap, I got too heated.
But Kou— I mean, this guy—
it's not like he isn't
responding at all, right?
Isn't there something he's done for her?
Yeah, I suppose there have been a few things.
Like dashing over to a park because
he worried about my friend's safety,
worrying more about my friend's
well-being than his assignments,
trying hard to come up with a date plan,
among other things.
But amidst all that,
what made me the happiest
is that he's trying hard
to get accepted to the same university as me...
Is what that friend said.
I'm going to die from cuteness overload!
But while that boy has nothing going for him
and is basically the embodiment
of peak ordinariness,
his loyalty goes above and beyond.
That's why I worry that the things he does
aren't coming from a place of affection,
but simply from a sense of moral obligation...
Is what my friend told me.
Yeah, there's absolutely no reason to worry!
Please tell your friend!
The mere fact that anyone wants
to do anything for someone else
already means they like them.
Besides, if he's trying hard to
improve his bad grades
so he can make it to the same university,
meaning he's investing
a majority of his life for her...
That's not something you can do
unless you really like someone.
Did I say that boy had bad grades?
Oh! Uh, I mean, I just kind of imagined that...
W-Well, I suppose this was
somewhat informative.
That friend of mine might be happy
if I passed this on to her.
I bet. Please do pass it on.
But anyway...
You really came here to talk about this?
I was convinced that you came here to
fake an accident to touch my breasts.
Urp!
I-I'm sorry!
I didn't really mean to,
but when it seemed like I
could get a touch in, I just...
I'm surprised you haven't been arrested yet.
You don't have to stoop
to the level of a groper.
If you just ask me, I'll let you touch them.
What?! Really?! I can?!
As long as it's not in front of people.
It's not like having you
touch them does anything for me.
I'm back.
I wonder if those two are all right...
What if Ellie jokingly tried to
cop a feel or something?
President's punishment would be brutal.
What's with that face?
Does it feel that good?
It's kinda lively in there.
What are they talking about?
So squishy!
And soft!
Could you please not squeeze them so much?
It tickles.
So squishy!
And soft!
Could you please not squeeze them so much?
It tickles.
Don't tell me...
No, there's no way.
That tickles!
Don't lick my stomach...
This is not an everyday occurrence, you know?
That... tickles.
Don't lick my stomach...
This is not an everyday occurrence, you know?
What happened while I was gone?
Soon after,
I realized that had just been a fantasy
my mighty imagination cooked up.
But it seems I was right that
the two had grown a bit closer.
Please
Put Them On, Takamine-san
Please Put Them On,
Takamine-san
A few days after the second semester began...
They said it would rain
well into the afternoon,
but it's already stopped.
Looks like this umbrella
wasn't really necessary.
I'm glad it stopped early.
Me too.
I won't have to be wearing a wet uniform.
I'm quite fond of this blazer.
I hear that our uniforms are quite popular.
The design is good too,
but before I acquired you,
it used to serve me really well.
If I used my ability multiple times in a row,
my summer uniform would become
see-through from perspiration and such.
So then I needed to change
every time I used my ability.
But with this blazer on,
I didn't have to worry about that
and could use it repeatedly.
Uh-huh...
Wait, so that means last winter...
Remember to
Greet Month
there was a high chance that President was...
...not wearing a bra or panties?!
Shirota-kun?
What's with the extreme
blank look on your face?
Are you suggesting that me extolling the
virtues of the blazer is boring you?
N-N-No, not at all!
Then why don't we play a game
to ward off the boredom?
A game?
Turn around for a second.
Sure...
I used my ability to make it so that
I didn't bring my umbrella.
Wha?
Now, here's the question.
When I used my ability,
did I get rid of my panties or my bra?
Sorry?!
Your time limit is...
yeah, until we get to the station.
If you can figure it out before
we get there, you win.
If you can't, I win.
It'll be more fun with a prize, so...
How about the loser has to listen
to one command the winner gives,
no matter what it is?
There's no way I can figure it out
from your appearance.
So it's more of a gamble with
50:50 odds rather than a game.
Oh, come now, don't be so humble.
Humble?
With your powers of perviness,
you can easily deduce
from the sound the cloth makes
if a nipple is rubbing against the shirt or not.
I see!
Or from the subtle difference in my stride
if I'm wearing panties or not.
I see!
Do I look like some kind of psychic?!
Well, even if you can't make an informed guess,
you have a 50:50 chance of making me
obey a command of yours.
For example...
"For our next study session, I want you
to teach me in your bathing suit."
For someone like you,
a chance to make me obey a command
may never come around again in your life.
Someone like me?
Besides, I wouldn't make you
do something like that.
What would you order me to do if you won, then?
Let's see...
If I had to pick something on the level
of doing the study session in a bathing suit...
I'd sew your eyes and mouth shut,
restrain your arms,
put headphones over your ears,
and make it so the only thing you can sense
for the rest of your life is my voice.
What's wrong with you?!
How is that on the same level at all?!
You're right.
That's too little if you compare it
to me in my bathing suit.
Well, I suppose I'm just being kind.
Is my life that worthless?!
Let's begin, then.
Hey, wait!
The odds are 50:50.
Which means
if I can confirm
Missing
that either piece of underwear is missing...
then I can easily figure out
the right answer...
The problem is, how do I do that?
One way might be to see if I can spot
her bra through the gap in her shirt.
Stare.
That would make me a pervert!
Besides, if I did that...
Oh, I see you openly staring now.
Have you leveled up from Pervy
Shirota-kun to Brazen Pervota-kun?
What should I do?
The moment she steps over that puddle...
maybe the reflection will show
the inside of her skirt!
That way I can figure out the answer
without her noticing!
If her panties show up,
she will have used up her bra for the ability!
If they don't show up, then...
Wait?!
If she used her panties for the ability...
then the reflection will show...
Well, time's up.
Which did I discard, bra or panties?
You discarded...
your bra!
Too bad.
I took off my panties.
Sheesh, what were you doing
all that time until we got here?
You could have easily gotten it right
if you'd just snuck a glance under my skirt.
Were you so preoccupied thinking about
studying with me in a bathing suit
that you couldn't think?
No, I had it figured out!
The reflection in the puddle!
But I couldn't look!
I mean, sneaking a look
when you weren't aware of it...
Even if I won, it wouldn't sit right with me.
Either way, managing to hit the wrong
choice is such a me thing, though...
To be honest, I'm a bit disappointed.
I was a little curious.
To see what kind of obscene
desires you'd force on me.
Why is it predetermined that
my command would be indecent?!
And I even gave you a bunch of hints.
What hints?
For instance, the reflection in the puddle.
Sh-She... actually purposefully
stepped over that big puddle?!
When she's not wearing panties?
She's crazy!
Oh, right, I have to give you a command.
Let me think...
Why don't we go with sewing
your eyes and mouth shut and—
You are joking, right?!
I suppose that depends how you are today.
They assigned the roles for the cultural festival
in today's homeroom class, right?
Oh, our class is putting on a Cinderella play.
I'm not one for getting attention, so
I figured I'd be a stagehand or something.
Your class did a haunted house
last year, right?
Haunted House
You weren't an actor then either,
just inviting people in, looking bored.
Well, cultural festivals aren't events
where people like me have fun.
I'm surprised you even remember that.
I more or less know what
every student at our school does.
That's only natural as
the student council president.
Is it really natural?
I'm sorry, but you'll have
to be an actor this year.
Huh? But why?
I'm going to have to deliver a perfect
performance as Cinderella.
Oh, so you already know what you're doing.
And for that, I will need your support.
If a stagehand jumps on stage
to put panties on me,
it would be suspicious.
It will be suspicious if an actor does it too!
Anyway, you get it, right?
When they are deciding on the roles,
you have to apply for a part
with a lot of stage time, so you can
put underwear on me at any point.
Wait, hold on!
All right. I'd like to begin the casting
for the Cinderella play
that our class will be putting on.
President!
Since I believe you're the only one
who ought to play Cinderella,
I think we should just
write you down already.
Cast for the Cinderella play
Cinderella
I agree.
If President is Cinderella,
we're sure to have a full house!
More importantly, I wanna see it!
I just want to see her as Cinderella!
Thank you.
If you're so adamant, I humbly accept.
Cast for the Cinderella play
Cinderella
Takamine Takane
That's amazing. She got the
role without even trying.
Then I'd like to continue
in the order as it appears in the script.
We'll begin with the stagehands.
We need two people for the sound.
Please raise your hands if you're interested.
Sound, huh?
It sounds relatively easy.
While she said otherwise,
I'm sure she won't be crazy enough
to make me put stuff on her on stage.
Here.
Jump.
Eternal Virgin Road.
Then I'd like to begin the casting
for the Cinderella play
that our class will be putting on.
President!
Since I believe you're the only one
who ought to play Cinderella,
I think we should just
write you down already.
Cast for the Cinderella play
Cinderella
She honestly wants me
to be her closet even on stage?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Could someone take notes for me?
Huh? She did it herself last time...
On duty today is... Shirota-kun?
Oh, sure.
I see.
She wants me to put them on
from behind the teacher's desk.
Then I'd like to decide
on the other main role, the prince.
There it is!
The prince?
She started with the sound guys before...
P-President... um...
The prince, huh?
He'll have a lot of lines
and stage time, but...
But it means you get to
be lovers with the president for a moment.
And you even get to put a shoe on her foot!
So, are there any candidates?
T-This isn't that something's touching her...
She's making it touch?!
Is she telling me to apply for
the prince role?!
I know the prince will have
a lot of stage time,
and a lot of opportunities
to put panties on her...
Here, I nominate myself!
Then I nominate myself, too!
Wait, me too!
I will be the one to put the glass
slipper on President's foot!
Are there any more candidates?
I know what she's wants, but this is...
Her bare butt is touching me
and I can't think straight...
I think I will be a candidate as well, then.
Ouji...
I knew he had his sights set on her.
Ouji Seiya. He's smart and
in the same top caste as President.
But I don't hear any positive things
about his relationships with girls.
I retract my candidacy.
I can't win anyway.
Me too.
At this rate, he's going
to get the prince role.
In that case, showing him my ability
and having him become my second
closet could also be an idea.
But since he seems to like me,
he might use keeping the secret
about my ability
as a bargaining chip to pursue something...
For instance...
something like an adult doujin...
Please
Beat
Me
Off,
Takamine-san
Well, it's a tiny risk one has to take
to put on a perfect show on stage.
What kind of value system does she have?!
I can't imagine that she'll
make a blunder against Ouji
and allow him to blackmail her,
but never say never.
All right, fine!
I will be a candidate as well!
Who even is he?
Oh?