Cinderella
Takamine Takane
Well, I'd like to decide on
the other main role, the prince.
I think I will be a candidate as well then.
I knew he had his sights set on her.
I will be a candidate as well!
Who is he, even?
Oh?
I would like to open a vote for the role, then.
Please submit your votes anonymously.
Cast for the Cinderella play
Cinderella
Takamine Takane
Prince
Shirota Koushi
(1 vote)
Ouji Seiya
(26 votes)
Nooo!
I'm so sorry...
I couldn't get the role.
I knew she was going to be mad...
Um, so that thing about
making Ouji your closet...
What?
That was a joke, of course.
My aim was to get you inspired
to try to get the Prince role.
Huh?
After you lost the vote, you applied
for the role of Prince's Guard.
Stage Visitor C
Shindou Nobuchika
Guard of the Prince
Shirota Koushi
Why's that?
Well...
If I'm the Prince's guard,
I figure I'll get roughly
the same amount of time as him,
so then you won't need to ask Ouji
for help because I can be there for you.
Wait, she foresaw all of this?!
Besides, it wouldn't be any good if you
hid away behind the scenes again
and I had to see your gloomy face.
If you try something new,
you might be able to enjoy things more openly.
Speaking of...
What is it?
If all you wanted was for me
to try to get the role of the prince,
then I wonder who voted for me?
Who knows.
Someone must have unusual preferences.
Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
I'll Let You Do a Dry Run
I'll let you do a dry run.
In order to make our Cinderella play
that we're putting on
for the cultural festival a success,
we used the time after class
and our homeroom time to prepare.
And now, we're just one day away
from the big event.
Cinderella
Tomorrow is the big day!
Anyone who's not busy, please go
support the groups that need help.
Let's all work together
to get this over the finish line!
I'm sorry, President.
If you've got a minute, could you please
help us with the stage backdrops?
Of course.
If there's anyone else free,
could you please come and help too?
I'll come help.
I'm almost done here, so I'll come help too!
I'll—
Oh, sorry!
It's fine.
I guess they won't need my help.
Shirota-kun.
You're free as well, arent you?
Could you please give us a hand?
It's the backdrop with the stairs.
I need you to add a light.
There's already one on the left side,
so you can use that as reference
to add it on the right.
S-Sure.
Hey, did the President just touch that Shirota guy?
Why someone as forgettable as him?
It's because President is like a goddess.
I bet she just spoke to him because
he's so lonely and isolated and pathetic.
The pressure is intense...
But, now that I think about it,
she never used to interact
with me in front of others.
Is there some sort of reason?
Is something wrong?
N-No...
Hey, Shirai!
You made the left and right
lights exactly the same!
Huh?
Oh! I'm sorry! I'll fix it right away!
We don't have time. Just leave it.
Youch.
Now he's done it.
Eternal Virgin Road.
We're back to before I started
working on the backdrop?
Why?
Shirota-kun.
Over here.
C-Coming.
Wait, did she do this to undo my mistake?
Those stairs are for the important
scene where I drop my slipper.
You better make it perfect.
Yeah, go figure.
If you've got it, hurry up.
Right...
President?
Huh? President?
What's up?
Oh, there you are!
We kind of need help with the backdrops...
But what are you doing there?
Oh, I was just checking behind the sets
to make sure everything's good.
I see.
Do you need help with something?
Yeah.
Once you're done there,
do you think you could
help with the backdrops?
How can she remain
so calm in a situation like this?!
Sure, I'm done here. I can help.
If anyone else is free,
could you please come and help too?
I'll come help.
I'm almost done here, so I'll come help too!
Here you go.
Thanks, President!
Be careful.
Shirota-kun.
You're free as well, aren't you?
Could you please give us a hand?
S-Sure...
Um, I'm sorry.
The panties are not fully on...
I know.
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
I already took care of it.
Wait, when?!
When I caught that piece of wood,
I spread my legs and engaged
the gluteus maximus, gluteus medius,
the femoral muscle, and the tensor tympani
muscle to shift it into position.
That's amazing.
Do it quicker from now on
so this won't happen again.
Slowta-kun—no, slowpoke.
That's not even a nickname anymore!
But anyway...
let's continue with our preparations.
R-Right...
Everyone, really good work today!
Let's get a lot of rest tonight and
enjoy the cultural festival tomorrow!
Good work!
Wow, it's already so dark.
I need to get home quick.
Come to the Building A east rooftop entrance.
(President) Come to the Building A east rooftop entrance.
What does she me up here for?
I'm pretty sure the rooftop door is locked...
Why bring me to this dead end?
Did I do something to make her angry?
Oh, you were quick.
I'm impressed.
Why are you so jumpy?
Did you think I'd yell at you?
So you won't?
Wait, what?
Isn't it off limits?
I went to the staff office to get permission.
You are the student council president, I guess.
Wow, there are so many stars.
But why bring me here?
I mean, looking at this night sky by myself
would be kind of dull.
Also, the only reason
that I invited you is
that you were at the top of my LIME history.
I'm sorry if you thought that
there was more behind it.
I'm quite all right with that...
Besides...
Staying at school this late...
When I thought that
this year might be the last time,
I figured it would be a shame.
The last time?
But there's another
cultural festival next year.
We're going to have
entrance exams next year.
Think about the mood
the class will be in.
Nobody is going to pick a large-scale
project that will require us to stay late.
Oh, right.
I like the evenings before events.
The emotional high that
you feel during the process,
before something is about to begin.
On top of that,
I had an easy-to-use closet at my disposal
this year, so it was even more enjoyable.
If I had known how convenient you'd be,
I would have made you my closet
for the cultural festival last year.
I really missed out.
Uh-huh...
Could it be that she invited me so that
I could feel this emotional high as well?
Well, there's still the year after next.
If you mean repeating
a year, please do that alone.
No, that's not it!
I mean the cultural festival at university!
I'm sure the cultural festival will be
even bigger at the university.
so we'll stay even later,
maybe even spend the night to work.
We'd have plenty of time to stargaze, too.
Besides, I also intend to be by your side
to support you at university.
Stay the night?
What kind of work are you thinking of?
Pervert.
Wha?! I-I-I wasn't thinking anything like that!
Why did it get so quiet?
It's so awkward.
I'm starting to feel like
what I said was really embarrassing...
You know...
Yes?!
Back when I read Cinderella for the first time,
I felt repulsed by it.
I mean, even though that girl wants
something, she stays passive.
If you want something,
you ought to be proactive, shouldn't you?
It's not like a fairy godmother
will show up in real life.
But to be honest, along with that repulsion,
I also felt empathy.
Not being able to muster the courage,
your pride getting in the way...
the more important things are,
the harder it is to act...
It makes you want to wait
for something to come to you...
But...
I can say it now.
In fact,
I think now is the only time I can say it.
I-I...
I am...
I'm sorry, President.
I didn't realize.
You want to leave because it's cold!
You should have just said something!
Your hands are so icy already.
No, it's not—
Please wear this on your way home.
It would be terrible if you caught a cold.
Sheesh, you should have noticed
without me saying anything.
Useless!
I'm sorry...
Please Put Them On,
Takamine-san
Haunted House
Hall of the Spider
Big Food
Hall Festival
Fujihigashi Festival
We're going to hold a dress rehearsal prior
to the performance before noon,
so you're all free
to enjoy yourselves until then.
All right.
Weird, where's Ouji? Is he late?
Pretty ballsy for having a lead role.
Crap... I'm so freaking nervous!
I already have cold sweat
running down my spine...
And I only have two lines.
Shirota-kun, do you have a minute?
Uh, sure.
Um, President, where are we going?
I couldn't leave you alone
because you're so obviously nervous.
Go enjoy some of the offerings to relax.
I'll come along with you.
Oh, she's looking out for me?
I have the lead role in this play.
Your role is so minor
that it could be left out entirely,
but I will not allow you to sully
the play even the slightest bit.
That makes more sense...
But...
Is the President holding that guy's hand?!
Who the hell is he?!
With that kind of useless loser?!
This situation is putting me
under a different kind of pressure.
L-Let's go in here, then!
Hall of the Spider
Sure.
This is the Hall of the Spider.
All who enter shall be inflicted
with the mysterious spider's curse.
Should you wish to proceed regardless,
you best steel your resolve first...
We're not really exposed
to the eyes of the public in here.
And unless someone gets really close,
they won't be able to identify us.
There shouldn't be any rumors of
President walking around with a pathetic guy.
It was a snap decision,
but I really did quite well!
Should we get going then?
C-Could it be that President
is afraid of this kind of stuff?!
Now that I think about it,
the thunder scared her, too.
so I guess she's not good with jump scares...
Um, if you're not good with this,
we can turn back.
What? Not good?
Are you suggesting that this
fake kid stuff will scare me?
Just so you know—
Be gone!
You must not enter this place!
This is the Hall of the Spider.
All who enter shall be inflicted
with the mysterious spider's curse.
Should you wish to proceed regardless,
you best steel your resolve first...
Um, President, why don't we just leave?
It's downward social comparison.
Downward what?
By comparing yourself to individuals
you perceive as worse off,
you can gain a boost in self-esteem.
In order to help you shake off your nerves,
I over-exaggerated my shock for you.
R-Really now?
Come on, let's move towards the exit.
R-Right...
Please help meeeeee!
Shirota-kun!
The spiders are in my bodyyyy...
Behind you!
Spider! Spider!
Wait!
A-Are you all right, Shirota-kun?!
What about the spider?! Did you get cursed?!
It's fine, President!
Please calm down!
Remember? This is a haunted house!
It's not real!
Huh?
This is the Hall of the Spider.
All who enter shall be inflicted
with the mysterious spider's curse.
Should you wish to proceed regardless,
you best steel your resolve first...
Downward social comparison.
Since you are slow on the uptake,
I put on an act for you again.
That excuse is so sad!
But she's really here toughing it out
in this haunted house so that I can relax...
Compared to her in the lead role,
my nerves aren't really anything significant.
For her sake, too, I want to
make sure the play goes well.
But still...
President being scared of the haunted house...
is so cute.
What are you grinning about?
Why can't you be proactive
and walk ahead as my escort?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sheesh.
S-S-S-Spider! Spider!
Please calm down.
Ahhh, th-these...
These are her breasts pushing against me!
H-Huge spider!
A huge spider has my leg!
It's fine!
Please wait, President!
It's dangerous to run like that!
Shirota-kun!
M-My body won't move!
Is it the curse?! Am I paralyzed?!
Please calm down!
You just got stuck in the spider web set!
Maybe you crashed into it when you were
running without looking ahead.
Well, since I displayed this much shock,
I'm sure the students from this class
were quite happy as well.
She's still acting tough?!
Please wait. I'll untie you right away.
You're really stuck, huh...
Ahh! It grabbed my leg!
Damn, that was close!
The next guests have caught up to us?!
This is bad. If they were
to see President in this state...
P-President?!
Um, that's pretty avant-garde...
President's pure image will be destroyed.
What do I do?!
What should we do?!
They've put quite some effort into it, huh?
Yeah, the atmosphere is pretty good, too.
Oh foolish intruders unfazed by the curse...
Shall I also turn you into spider people...?
Is it me or did the quality just tank?
What a joke.
Couldn't you think of anything better?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry. You went through
so much for my sake...
I don't how you misinterpreted the situation,
but everything went according to my plan.
Huh?
Didn't you realize that not only
did you relax in the haunted house,
you also got to act in front of other people?
I got rid of your nerves, and by pretending
to get into a sticky situation,
I seamlessly enabled you to do a rehearsal.
I-I see. Thank you very much.
It's impressive that she can
come up with such an excuse.
Waiting Room
There's some sort of commotion...
Did something happen?
Well, it seems Ouji
still hasn't come to school!
What?
Did he call in sick?
No, but we can't reach him
on his phone either...
Without Ouji, we won't
be able to put on the play!
Hey, sorry about that.
I'm late.
Dude, Ouji!
We worried abo—
What?!!
Yeah, well, I had a bit of a run-in...
with a dump truck.
A dump truck?!
It's fine.
Not a proble— arghh.
He's seriously hurt!
Who's on first aid duty?!
President, I'll put some on you right away,
Take him to the nurse's office!
You can make it so
Ouji didn't have an accident.
Stop! I'm fine!
Let go of me!
I can still do it!
I am the Ouji—
Let's find a replacement.
A replacement?!
Why take such a risk?!
I thought she wanted to make
100% sure this play goes well...
We have one hour until the start.
It might be tight, but we
should be ready on time.
Okay, but who's supposed to be the Prince?
We all have our own roles already...
You're right.
Why don't we do this, then?
We pick a role where cutting it
won't affect the story much.
That actor will then step in for the Prince.
That's you, Shirota-kun.
I-I'm supposed to replace Ouji?!