Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Only Look At Me
Only look at me.
The play Cinderella will begin shortly.
A long, long time ago, in a far away land...
A beautiful girl, Cinderella, lived
in a house by the outskirts of the forest.
Ahh, it's Takane-chan!
Stop it, you're so embarrassing.
So cute!
Next, once we fade to black, switch to Set 2.
Actors, please get ready!
Cinderella lived a happy life,
Cinderella
blessed by the generous love
of her kind parents.
But those happy days came to a sudden halt.
Oh no, it's begun...
President had the final word,
and so I was selected to play the Prince.
The only thing I could call practice
was reading the script twice...
Can someone like me
really play the Prince, though?!
No, calm down!
It's still a while until I go out on stage.
And the Prince has a lot of stage time,
but he doesn't have that many lines.
Anyway, these first lines...
Beautiful lady,
would you
honor me by
I'll just focus on not messing these up.
Cinderella, please bring me some tea.
Yes, mother.
This tea is terrible!
Do it again!
I'm sorry!
After her father passed away,
her stepmother began to treat her very cruelly.
Her experience was worse than
the worst treatment maids receive.
Do it agai—
I mean, I can't stand that stepmother!
What's with these guys?
How dare she?!
Hey!
I thought we overdid it,
but they're really eating it up!
I mean, if President is going this far,
they've got to be mesmerized.
Beautiful lady, would you honor me
by allowing me to have this dance?
Cinderella, watch the house
while we go to the ball.
What? You said you'd take me with you.
That was a lie, of course.
Besides, what would you even wear?
Oh, if you were thinking of
your mother's heirloom,
that dress burned nicely in the fireplace.
Perfect for you, don't you think?
N-No! How could you?!
"The ball the Prince organized...
If I could just take part in it,
I would be able to bear all this suffering..."
That is what Cinderella thought.
Alas...
Oh dear Lord,
if I may not even dream for just one night,
when will I finally awaken
from this daily nightmare?
Wipe your tears, Cinderella.
I am the Fairy Godmother.
I have been watching your deeds.
What is this?
I shall grant you your wish.
Cinderella, you must not forget this.
The magic spell will vanish
as soon as the bell strikes midnight.
Takane-chan
please look
this way
Next, get the set for the ball ready!
Ahhh, I have to go out on stage soon!
Hurry with her dress change!
Got it!
It's almost time, huh, Shiraki?
Break a leg!
I feel like my heart's
going to burst out of my chest!
Shirota-kun.
Yes?!
Let's enjoy ourselves.
Oh!
What a beautiful young lady.
You must hail from a distinguished house!
That's right, President said this to me.
This year is the last time we'll have
a large-scale cultural festival in high school.
And that that's why she wants to enjoy it.
May I have your attention, please.
His Highness, the Prince.
Prince, time to go!
I want to support her in that.
And as the first step,
I just have to say my first lines well.
That's all I need to do!
Huh?
Takane-chan
please look
this way
Kou-chan's playing the Prince?!
He said he only had a minor role!
Something's off...
H-Huh?
What were my lines again?
What's wrong, Shiraki?!
Pull yourself together!
Do you want to ruin everything?!
I can't get a single line out,
let alone support President...
I'm basically just dragging her down...
I knew I couldn't handle...
the Prince rol—
What?!
Next, get the set for the ball ready!
Hurry with her dress change!
Got it!
So she brought us back to right
before the ball scene.
I'm sorry, could you buy me
a little bit of time?
Got it!
Shirota-kun, may I have a word?
S-Sure!
What was that complete mess-up just now?!
Are you trying to ruin my play?
I knew she'd be angry!
I-I'm sorry...
Listen. I'll give you a piece of advice.
Okay...
Why are you paying attention
to other people's reactions?
Nobody expects anything from your acting.
Nobody is even paying attention to you.
A paint smear on the backdrop set
will draw more attention than you.
What's the meaning of "advice" again?
In fact, if you have the energy
to pay attention to others instead of me,
you aren't completely out of it.
How insolent.
President, it's time!
Thank you, I'll be right there.
Basically,
nobody ever expects
anything from you whatsoever.
Don't waste time being intimidated.
Don't pay attention to others.
Just keep your eyes on me.
Oh!
What a beautiful young lady.
You must hail from a distinguished house!
Prince, time to go!
As always, her words were full of thorns.
But still,
the kindness that is always wrapped
inside them put me at ease.
And more than anything...
Beautiful lady, would you honor me
by allowing me to have this dance?
I now believe that those words
came so easily then...
With pleasure.
because it wasn't acting.
That's the way I see it now.
Please Put Them On,
Takamine-san
Beautiful lady, would you honor me
by allowing me to have this dance?
With pleasure.
I said it!
I managed to make it through
the first scene, thanks to her pep talk.
Um, so, after this...
After cutting the lights,
there will be a spotlight on President.
She will have her solo.
Then the lights will be cut again,
and we'll be in the dance scene.
Did I get that right?
So I just wait here until the lights come on.
A-A-A butt!
And this cloth around me... it can't be...
I'm inside her skirt?!
Is she telling me to
put panties on her right now?!
But I didn't bring any underwear for her!
Yes, it's true,
I don't wish for many things.
I don't wish for grandiose things.
I just have this scant hope,
In my pocket?
a small handful in my pocket.
A scant hope?!
So please, oh bells...
I mean, having no underwear
on stage is seriously too risky...
Just for tonight, hold your breath.
I need to finishing putting these on
during her solo...
before the stage is lit up again!
Oh my beloved person.
Wait!
Please only look at me.
Please don't move!
Hold me tight and take me
to a world of our own.
But you know?
I am aware.
This dream is already over.
So please don't ever peek
at these hidden feelings.
Now, everyone, let's dance
to our hearts' content!
Let's make this an unforgettable night.
I-I made it!
After that, I followed her lead.
Please wait!
Please, please don't follow me!
And the crazy act of putting panties on her
on stage had blown away my nervousness,
so I was able to continue on without incident.
And then we finally got to the climax.
Th-This is Cinderella, a lowly girl
not any better than a servant...
There is no way that
she's the person of your heart.
Her standing is of no consequence to me.
The person whose foot fits
this slipper is the person of my heart.
Cinderella, would you allow me
to put it on you?
Huh? Did someone take the spare costume?
Oh, yeah, just now—
I bet nobody even suspects this is the second
time you've put something on my body on stage.
H-Hey!
Quiet!
Stop!
That Prince is an impostor!
Huh?!
He is a commoner who tried to take
my place while I was away due to an injury!
Even his face screams "commoner!"
What?!
Kou-chan is way cooler!
He's so unassuming!
They put a real twist in the story.
What is happening?
This wasn't in the script, was it?!
Ouji's become unhinged!
Please play along
and improvise!!
What now?!
T-Two princes?!
What is happening?!
She's so quick!
Cinderella!
You mustn't allow such
an uncouth man touch you!
Uncouth?!
Behold his filthy hands!
In contrast, I have been applying hand cream
and polishing my nails for a week,
all for this one day!
I am fully prepared to touch your lovely feet!
Are you telling me...
That Ouji flipped out because he
wants to touch her foot?!
Cinderella's... beautiful... feet!
Are you really about to destroy the last fun
high school cultural festival that
President has been working for?
For your own selfish wants?!
Oh, please don't fight.
If you truly do love me...
I won't give her up.
Even if you were the real Prince
and I was a commoner.
Someone who is selfish and won't
consider what she wants
won't be able to make her happy.
I will not let you have her!
I will make her happy!
Only Kou-chan wins!!
Wow, Kou-chan is so cool!
Knock it off. You're so embarrassing.
I don't know what's going on, but it's good!
Give it some fitting narration!
Got it!
The real Prince, who appeared out of nowhere,
and the impostor Prince, who's
ready to face off with him!
Who is Cinderella going to choo—
P-Pre—
Let us go.
Y-Yes. Where to?!
Please wait, Pres— Cinderella!
What about the slipper?!
You may have it.
Neither slipper nor standing matter!
Cinderella has found true love!
After that, the play went smoothly.
Ironically, the fresh twist
in the second half was well-received,
and our show was a huge success.
You gotta do that wild entrance
in the afternoon showing too.
Huh? Uh, sure...
But even more than that,
what had impressed
our classmates even more was...
B-By the way, President...
The thing at the end...
Did you really kiss?!
It was just something I did to salvage
that situation, so it wasn't real.
But it's embarrassing, so please
don't talk about it too much.
Right, Shirota-kun?
R-Right...
Fujihigashi Festival
I'm glad the cultural festival went well.
Me too.
I'm glad our play was a big success as well.
That was because of my godly improvisation.
Your acting also gets passing marks,
so it makes for a good memory, doesn't it?
But thinking about it...
What was the meaning of that, really?
I feel like it was a bit much
for salvaging the situation...
Maybe it's something like a reward,
an early payment for being her closet?
She's really not that kind of person, though...
But...
What is it?
It's just... that...
That thing you did during Cinderella...
That thing?
W-When you... and I...
Why do you think I did that?
Try to think about why I did that to you.
C-Could it be?
No, that's not possible... but...
If you don't get it,
do you need me to do it again
and again until you do?
Ow!
And? Did that wake up your brain?
Do you get it now?
If it didn't, I can do it again.
No, it's fine!
Then please give me your answer.
If you don't give me the right answer...
maybe I'll make it so that
the play didn't go well.
Because you couldn't get
a single line out, or something.
I'm joking.
I just want to hear your honest thoughts.
Th-This is just a theory...
Maybe you want me...
to keep being your closet
at university too,
so it was some sort of reward or something?
That was wrong?!
Fujihigashi Festival
We're back here?
Is she angry?
What is the right answer then?!
Why don't you think about it harder?
About what that meant.
Think harder?
What did it mean?
Do you need another jolt?
Um, that's—
Fujihigashi Festival
Looks like time's up.
Par for the course for Dull-ta-kun.
Looks like it's the climax
of the closing event.
As the student council president,
I need to be there.
Um, President, I—
You'll have to continue as my closet
until you figure out the answer.
Quite some time will pass before I figure out
what the right answer was.
Shirota-kun.
Aren't you forgetting something?
At that point,
I was simply hoping the
relationship we had would go on.
Shall we go, then,
Kurota-kun?