Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
I Want You to Enjoy the Very Best
I want you to enjoy the very best.
That's it for today.
Oh, Takamine.
Please collect the assignments and
bring them to the prep room in Building B.
Yes, sir.
Of course.
Got them.
President!
It'll be too heavy for you alone.
I'll help you.
Me too! I'm free!
Thank you.
As always, she's super popular.
I guess I can't say no to your offer...
Is what I'd like to say, but...
Kurota-kun...
Have you
still failed to grasp what you are?
Wh-What does she mean?!
President!
It'll be too heavy for you alone.
I'll help you.
Me too, I'm free!
Thank you.
She undid that?!
More importantly...
What does she mean, "what I am"?
Become my closet.
You are to always carry underwear for me,
follow me wherever I go...
That's what she meant!
Um!
I will help you!
Sheesh.
I took a pair off for your education.
Shouldn't you be grateful?
Y-Yes. I'm sorry.
Basically,
since I'm her closet,
I have to always stand by
in her vicinity to help her change.
And, to make me acknowledge that fact,
she undid accepting the other students' help.
Next time, please don't
give me so much trouble
Let's go.
President, if you like,
I could carry that for you.
Oh, I'll help too.
Wow, people are volunteering to help her again.
Me too.
She's respected,
loved, and praised by everyone...
If I could be reborn as her,
I bet every single day
would be a walk in the park...
Thank you,
but I'm fine.
Anyway, Tanaka-kun,
I heard that you beat a strong
school in a practice match?
Oh, yes!
I think this year's baseball
club is going places!
That's amazing.
I look forward to it.
And Oota-san, you got picked
for the kendo group battle?
Oh, you knew about that?!
I'm so touched!
Science Preparation Room
All right,
let's review, "Birdo-kun."
What is it you're supposed to do when
I undertake anything on my own?
T-Take the initiative and come with you.
Very good.
I'm glad you possess more than a bird brain.
Ah, man, I wish she'd keep up her public
persona even when it's just the two of us...
That was pretty intense before,
handling all those people...
Takamine
Takane
An intense
3 hours
Could you not make it sound like
I was in some orgy porn?
Number One
If I were to star in porn, it'd be one on one!
Her overwhelming
STYLE won't let
anyone try to
match her
And then of course I'd aim to become
number one in the porn industry.
What are you talking about?!
I was just thinking that it must
be tiring, how everybody
comes to talk to you everywhere you go...
That's a sign that I'm a good
student council president.
It's something to be proud of.
Of course I'm not annoyed by that.
Oh. Right.
You knew all the names of the people
who came to talk to you.
Are you telling me you know the names
and faces of every single student here?
Yes.
I memorized them all on the day I was
sworn in as the student council president.
In one day?!
I mean, as the student council president,
everybody here knows my name and face.
She's so beautiful.
Well, not that anybody could ever forget
someone as beautiful and perfect as me.
R-Right...
So, given that everybody here knows me...
I see...
if I, as the president, didn't know who they were...
It's so she won't let anyone dow—
...it would feel like I'd lost.
Wait, that's the reason?!
What do you mean?
What other reason could there be?
Never mind.
I envied her because I thought
she was liked and respected by all...
But she's probably
the president we all know today
because she's been putting in
unimaginably hard work in secret...
So much passion...
I wonder what made her the person she is...
Incidentally, I have also memorized a simple
profile of every single student as well.
W-Wow!
That includes you, of course.
Shirota Koushi, age 17.
Born in Saitama Prefecture, Sakado City.
Personality: weak-willed,
low self-esteem,
very little ambition,
not particularly good at any subject.
If I had to pick one,
it'd be contemporary literature.
But even there, you're just average.
Your social circle is also minuscule and—
Ho-Ho-Hold up!
I get it, I get it already!
That's not so easy...
Did you really memorize every
student's profile in that much detail?!
What are you implying?
Are you suggesting that I've only
done in-depth research on you?
That's not what I...
You need to keep your ego in check.
Personality: excessively focused on yourself.
She added more?!
And one more thing.
A closet perv.
W-Wait, what?
Oh, you're denying it?
When, in reality you're so obsessed with my
body that you peeped on me while I changed?
But now that you're officially in
a position to look, you never do.
Well, that's just...
I figured you probably wouldn't want me to...
I see.
Ow!
Then what would you do
if I said I wouldn't mind?
No, that won't do.
You'd just make another excuse.
I want you to look at me, Shirota-kun...
What if I said that to you?
P-President, please don't mess with me.
I'm not messing with you.
I honestly want to know.
Please tell me how you really feel.
I-Is she being serious?!
If she is...
If I say I want to look...
T-Things like that should only
happen if we're going out!
I'm sorry.
I just didn't expect such an answer.
Well, enough joking around. Shall we go back?
You were joking?!
But, you know, Shirota-kun...
Would it be correct of me to assume...
that you think you and I
could possibly go out?
No, that would be completely unthinkable!
Don't be so quick to shoot it down.
That wasn't such a bad answer...
For me, at least.
Huh?
What do you mean by tha—?!
Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Shirota-kun?
Oh, I'm glad.
You came to.
Huh?
Calm down. This is the nurse's office.
You fell down the stairs and hit your head.
How should I put it...
It looked quite bad, so I used my ability.
Used her
ability
to undo this
How bad is "bad"?
So that undid the fact that you fell,
but you stayed unconscious after.
Nurse's Office
That's why I brought you here.
Oh, that's what happened.
Thank you.
That's right.
So you should rest a little longer.
Oh, I need to correct your profile a bit.
Considering you rejected my offer,
the updated evaluation is:
low esteem, cowardly, fake-gentleman virgin.
Meanness on full blast!
Alternatively,
an absurdly upstanding person.
By the way,
I didn't change after using my ability,
so don't bury your face too deep, okay?
I'll get up! I'm up!
Classes are already over?!
I have an extra lesson in PE...
I wasn't able to get my
long distance time under 30 minutes.
Huh.
Well, the teacher just goes to his club
without staying until the end,
so I guess I'll just take it easy.
Your lack of ambition is almost refreshing.
I mean, even I would like to be number
one in at least one thing, but...
So it's been decided that I'll be
administering the extra lesson today.
P-President?!
Even though I was basically forced
to do this by that teacher,
I'm not going to phone it in.
So I'm asking you all
to take it seriously as well.
I see what she's doing.
Come on, you got this!
Let's pick up the pace a bit!
It's no good...
I'm dead last... so pathetic.
Shirota-kun, stop for a second.
S-Sure.
Your form is way too inefficient.
I'll correct it for you.
Your shoulders are way too stiff.
Relax.
And straighten your back.
Her breasts!
And my sweat is...!
Are you listening?
Since I coached you so nicely,
surely you can finish within 30 minutes, right?
Y-Yes!
I couldn't...
You're the only one who
couldn't make it on time, Shirai.
My name's Shirota.
Come on, man.
You even got coached by the president.
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
Until you manage to do it perfectly,
we're going to keep redoing it.
Ready, go!
From the start?
Start already.
B-But what about your underwear?
You can do that after you finish.
But you'd better complete
the run in 30 minutes.
Y-Yes!
Crap!
I can't...
Come on, everyone.
You got this!
Keep it up!
I'm so pathetic that even
though she's cheering us on,
I'm already thinking about
how I should apologize.
Put on a spurt here!
She's standing up?
If someone saw her from behind...!
Her... uh... It's going to be in full view!
Huh?
Are they noticing?!
I can't allow them to see her in such a state!
I don't want to show them!
What the... Runner's high?
He's in the way!
I can't see the divine panties!
S-So tired...
How long are you going to lie there?
Hurry up and put them on me.
I never expected you to
show up to coach us.
I was watching to make sure a certain someone
didn't collapse and hit his head again.
So, what do you think?
Oh, right.
I'm super exhausted,
but I'm glad I was able to finish on time.
I mean, I thought it would be impossible.
That's not what I meant.
How did it feel to be first?
You didn't just finish within 30 minutes,
you finished in first place.
I did?
Were you too mesmerized by my butt to notice?
So, how does it feel?
To be honest,
it doesn't feel real,
and I never really paid
attention to rankings...
And being first in the group that needed
supplementary lessons
brings me nowhere near her level...
But...
I'm quite happy!
I see.
Well, let's go home, then.
Hurry up and get changed.
Ah, sure.
I missed my chance to
give her back her underwear.
I guess returning it tomorrow might be fine.
I-Inside here...
There's underwear that she
was supposed to put on...
Good evening, Shirota-kun.
Shirota-kun
Did you take my underwear home?
I'm so sorry! I'll return it
tomorrow at school!
I was thinking about going for a run just now,
but it seems that pouch
has my sports underwear.
What?
Unfortunately, that's the only
sports underwear I own.
So you're telling me to bring it?
Oh well, her place isn't that far.
No, wait!
Isn't this a test to see if I follow
my owner's wishes as a closet?!
A closet's duty is to help her change.
But she doesn't need any help at home.
She can put on another pair as well.
This is just...
I might be a closet, but I'm no gofer!
President has sent an image.
This is... She's braless!
You didn't say anything...
President
You didn't say anything... Well, I have no choice,
so I've given up on putting on underwear
before going running.
Well I have no choice,
so I've given up putting on
underwear before going running.
Why?!
Just give up on going for a run!
Or put on normal underwear!
I can run better half-naked than
I can wearing regular underwear.
Why not give up on going for a run
I can run better half-naked
than I can
wearing regular underwear.
President
Really?!
I'm not wearing any panties either, of course.
President
Of course, I'm not wearing any panties either.
Save Image	                                               Share Image
Wait, what am I doing?!
I need to go stop her!
She's outside?!
W-What is she doing?!
She could get taken into protective custody!
Don't worry, I'm not texting while running.
President
(I stopped briefly to take that).
I'm not worried about that!
No, calm down...
She might just be trying to control me
by getting me flustered!
I need to respon—
She's totally getting ready to run!
There's someone in the picture?!
This place...
Is that the park in our neighborhood?!
If she works out at night wearing that...
she could get in trouble!
Oh no!
Wait, there's no need to worry.
She can probably send
just about anybody packing,
and even if she were to get into danger,
she could just undo...
Shirota-kun
That was a joke.
I was just messing with you.
You really thought I'd
go running like that?
I already went home.
You can give my underwear
back tomorrow.
[Cancel]
[Send]
President!
I'm sorry.
Here.
You're late, Slowta-kun.
Slowta?!
Though, I will give you credit for bringing me
my underwear without being ordered to.
It seems you learned how to take action
as a closet based on your owner's wishes.
No...
If something were to happen while
you were out without underwear,
you wouldn't be able to undo it.
That's true.
In other words, you got afraid because your
cuckold fetish was about to awaken
when you imagined me being assaulted—
That's not it!
I-I just came because I was worried.
Oh, really?
Worried about me?
Well, I...
So you were worried about me.
Hmmm.
Did I make her angry?
Thank you.
Huh?
Did you not hear me?
Well, I'm feeling good right now,
so I'll say it again.
Thank you for worrying for me.
I appreciate it, Shirota-kun.
But color me surprised.
I mean, that Shirota-kun said something cool.
Well, I suppose...
as the only person who knows my secret,
you might truly be the only
person in the entire world
who would worry about
a perfect person like myself.
For someone as forgettable as yourself,
that must be an overwhelming honor, no?
She's suddenly dissing me again?!
Oh right...
There are things that only I can do for her
because I'm the only one who knows her secret.
Wait, why am I thinking
I want to go that far for her?
Oh, so...
To sum it up,
Shirota-kun, as you are the only person
in the world who knows my secret...
may I assume I can make you
worry about me a lot?
Please go easy on me if you can...
I'll take that back then.
It's kind of warm.
Sorry!
I had it clutched to me as I ran here!
I see.
Or did you use them for something uncouth?
What?!
No, I didn't use any of them!
Come to think of it, by this point,
I was already unable to take my eyes off of her.