Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Honey, Let Me Wash Your Back.
Honey, let me wash your back.
President was teaching me
how to do my assignment at her house,
but then a huge downpour
led to me staying the night.
A bit later, the electricity went out...
And I found out that she's
actually afraid of lightning.
Sh-She was so cute...
Looks like the electricity is back.
That's good.
I'm going to go prepare dinner.
Oh, really, please don't go out of your way.
Huh? I never said I'd make anything for you.
I... I'm sorry...
Well, I guess I could make enough
for you too, while I'm at it.
Thank you...
Just cooking wouldn't be fun,
so why don't we play a game?
Taking into account that it's
just the two of us under this roof,
let's do some newly-wed roleplay.
While we're in this house,
we roleplay that we're
newlywed: husband and wife.
Do something unbefitting,
and there will be punishment.
So kind of like playing house?
That's a bit embarr—
How about the punishment being
that you have to remain single
for the rest of your life?
That's heavy!
Don't you think the punishment is
a bit heavy for how loose the rules are?
You think so?
Wouldn't it be essentially zero damage for you?
You think my chances of getting married are zero?
I'm going to go ahead.
Follow me once you're ready, honey.
Are we already playing?
Excuse m—
Welcome home.
But, President!
What's with that outfi—
Stop.
What kind of husband
calls his wife "President?"
Here comes the punishment.
Or so I would say,
but I'll be generous the first time.
If you're going to talk to me,
you have to become my husband.
A-All right...
That being said...
Um, since we're married, "President" is out,
"Takamine-san" is also weird...
Ta-Takane-san?
Yes?
Honey?
This game is bad!
No, more importantly!
Um, Takane-san.
You should probably put
something on under the apron...
If you want that,
you know what to do, right?
Please cook the roux in the pot.
Stir it so that it doesn't burn.
S-Sure.
That doesn't help!
The panties do nothing!
Honey...
It's burning.
Huh?
You're right!
Jeez,
you're completely hopeless at preparing meals.
Even though you're always preparing your seed.
What kind of person am I in her head?!
Wow, this looks so delicious!
You really are good at cooking
Pre— I mean, Takane-san.
Okay, I'm going to dig in.
Oh, hold on.
I give you the first bite.
Uh, no, I'm fine!
I can eat it myself!
Oh, but why not? We're married, after all.
The power of the newlywed
President is... devastating!
Are you all right?
Did you get burned?!
No, I'm fine.
I put so much heart into this dish...
I'm sorry...
Are you really sorry?
Yes.
We need something to wipe that off...
How about...
you lick it up?
N-No, that would be...
You can't do that?
I made it for you, so I don't want
a single drop to go to waste.
As my husband, you understand
that sentiment, don't you?
I-I do, but...
You don't need to overthink it.
At this moment, I am your wife
and you're my husband.
If a man honors his wife's wishes...
what is he to do in this situation?
Huh?
This is...
Too bad.
It would have been funny
to see you licking the air.
But why?
As you can see,
I made it so that I didn't feed you.
But...
You need to be more observant.
Just because we're playing this game,
I'm not going to let you lick this
porcelain skin so easily.
That would make me a lewd woman.
I really don't get where she draws the line!
Thank you for the meal.
And? Was it good?
Y-Yes.
Though I was too flustered to enjoy it.
I think it might be time
to prepare the bath.
I'll do the dishes, so you can go in first.
Go in first?
What do you mean by that?
Are there newlywed couples
who don't bathe together?
No, there are not.
A rhetorical question?!
Bathing together is...
I'm fine not taking a bath, then.
Even though 90% of newlyweds bathe together?
Where did you get that statistic?!
I'm joking.
I wouldn't want you to unleash your inner
Mollusca, Class Cephalopoda,
Mollusca, Class Cephalopoda, Superorder
Decapodiformes, Order Octopodiformes
Superorder Decapodiformes,
Order Octopodiformes smell.
Say what?
Where's the body soap...
Is this her shampoo?
How's the hot water from the shower, honey?
W-What are you doing?
You said you wouldn't come in!
Oh?
I did say I was joking,
but I didn't say I wasn't doing it.
You're splitting hairs!
You're taking this game too far!
A boy and a girl, na-naked together...
Gee, you're just as pervy as ever.
W-What do you mean?
You were already getting aroused
over my shampoo alone.
You can take it home if you want.
You can use it at home.
Please stop that hand motion!
Besides, you're wrong about one thing.
I compromised, knowing you're a perv.
A bathing suit?
Exactly.
But the design!
It's basically sexier than being naked!
I'll leave as soon as
I'm done washing my body!
Please wait outside for a minute!
Oh, but that would be a problem.
As your wife, I'm here to wash your back.
Wha?! I-I'm good!
You don't have to commit so hard!
You're so weirdly stubborn.
Then let me rephrase it like this.
I want to practice so that I can
do this perfectly when the time comes.
You're basically like a slightly
fancier mannequin, right?
I figured you'd be an ideal practice dummy.
Y-You have plans to do this then?
Not really. It's just for future reference.
Why am I relieved?
Look, I'm giving you a great chance
to repay me for tonight's food and shelter.
Fine. All right...
But without the body-to-body thing
you mentioned today.
Just do it normally.
Sure, got it.
Can I make it through?!
No, I have to make it through!
I have to use my willpower to contain it.
If my instincts take over
and this thing runs free...
and if she notices that, it's over!
All right. Pardon my touch.
S-Sure.
N-No towel?!
You've got more muscle than I thought.
It really is different from my own back.
Her hand is so soft...
And her voice is echoing and...
I'm in trouble!
Oh, I know!
I heard you can count prime numbers
in this situation.
Here goes. Two, three, five, seven, eleven, thirteen...
Is that what I think it is?!
U-Um, your breasts...
It's just cushioning, so my bare breasts
don't accidentally touch you.
That was totally premeditated!
I'll rinse you off now.
I made it through somehow...
Then, next...
I'll wash your hair.
We agreed that you'd only wash my back!
Oh? I only agreed to do it normally.
I never made any promises about what I'd wash.
Calm mind! Calm mind!
If make it through this, I'll be free!
I wish we had shampoo for men,
but unfortunately my father's is out.
Please excuse me for using mine.
It's true...
It smells just like her...
It's almost like I'm being enveloped by her...
Wait, what am I thinking?!
Calm your mind!
Oh right, have to get behind the ears, too.
Calm you—
President, you really have to stop tha—
I-It's real!
Please wait until we're in bed, honey.
I'm sorry!
What are you in such a rush for?
I haven't rinsed you off ye—
Well, I did what I came here to do.
Please finish rinsing yourself off.
I-I'm saved...
Why was she being so extreme earlier?
Y-Yes?
I'm going to bed too.
Be sure to set your alarm.
S-Sure.
Oh, and...
one more thing.
I'm sure you realize after today...
what my existence means to you.
What she means to me?
What does she—
To you, I am...
A higher being, who holds
the reins in every matter.
Huh?
Could it be that...
she was upset about having
shown me her weak side?
And, in order to erase that,
she went out of her way to
tease me on such an extreme level?!
How proud can a person be?!
Throughout the day,
I witnessed an unexpected side of her,
but also reconfirmed that she will
maintain her "President" persona despite it.
Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Today, we're on patrol
at the town's fireworks festival
Special Yakitori - Okonomiyaki  - Chocolate Bananas - Special Grilled Squid
to make sure the students
aren't doing anything bad.
You're late, Shirota-kun.
Oh, sorry. Wait, aren't I on time?
As a rule, I arrive five minutes early.
As my closet, you should
arrive ten minutes early.
Now, let's go check the places
likely to have a lot of students.
Follow me.
Okay.
I guess she's wearing a yukata,
even though she's on patrol.
No issues so far.
Let's take a short break.
Could you put a pair on me, just in case?
Huh, when did you use your ability?
Oh, I never put any on to begin with today.
What?!
Yukatas tend to show panty lines.
And since I'm wearing an undershirt,
I'm not wearing a bra either.
I see...
But there are so many people around.
I don't think there's a spot
where nobody would see.
Nobody is paying attention
to what other people are doing.
Still, though...
Oh, you leave me no choice.
Oh, Koushi.
My sandal strap broke and I can't walk.
Fix it for me?
Oh, I see.
Pretend I'm fixing her sandals
as I'm putting on her panties.
S-Sure thing.
Let's go to that bench, then.
Sure!
Thank you, Koushi!
O-Of course.
I didn't know she could sound like that...
The fireworks are about to start.
Since we're already here,
let's watch for a bit.
Yeah.
Oh wow, those two are totally
not on the same level.
Dude, that's so rude.
Huh?! Damn, you're right!
I guess we do look like a couple, huh?
But if she heard that...
Not on the same level?
Merely thinking about
comparing us is an affront.
That's what she'd say.
But hypothetically, if we were going out,
what would it be like?
I guess I should thank you.
Though, I suppose it's only natural that
a boyfriend should accompany his girlfriend.
Still, thank you for
patrolling with me today.
...is probably how it would be.
Not an equal relationship.
Hey, after this...
Want to come over?
My parents are gone on a trip...
Oh, right...
If we were dating...
You probably have nothing
to do later, do you?
Do you want to come over?
Just for tonight, you're relieved
of your closet duties.
In fact...
tonight, I want you to take them off.
Shirota-kun?
Ahhh, I'm sorry!
My mind just went there!
Huh?
Whatever.
I didn't see any
problematic behavior in this area...
so I'll redo it and check another area.
Huh?
This is the spot where we met.
How long are you going to space out?
We're moving on.
To where?
I've decided to use this as a starting
point to check the other areas.
I can't be bothered walking back here
from the spot we checked, so I undid it.
I-I see...
There are a lot of adult couples here.
It might not be necessary
to check here further.
Hey, could I have some beer?
One sec.
Hey—
You're so bad.
They're really adults!
Shirota-kun.
Y-Yes?!
Do you have anything to drink?
Let's take a break.
Did she...
see what that couple was doing?!
If so, will she request something to tease me
about being incapable of doing
a mouth-to-mouth transfer?
Or maybe even a serious
mouth-to-mouth transfer?!
No, no, no.
The two choices are obviously
that she didn't see it,
or that she will tease me about
being incapable of doing it!
If tea is all right, I have an unopened one.
But in case it wasn't a tease,
if I didn't play along...
Since she hates losing...
That was a childlike performance.
You spilled most of it.
Shirota-kun?
I'm sorry!
He-Here's the tea!
Never mind. Just put a pair on me.
But the people!
They're all busy watching the fireworks.
Right.
After that, we checked another area,
redid it, and repeated that
with a bunch of other areas.
But every time we did that,
I felt her mood getting worse.
There don't seem to be any issues here.
Yeah.
Actually, it's just the two of us here...
She must be getting frustrated
because I'm too spaced out.
But she's definitely being a bit weird too.
We're supposed be on patrol,
but she's keeps picking places
that are more and more empty.
And it also doesn't seem to make sense that
we keep going back to the starting point.
Shall we rest a bit?
Come to think of it,
she often redoes it after we take a break.
Places with many couples, isolated places...
what does she want to redo after resting?
A confession?!
No, no, no, what's wrong with me?!
If she realizes that I'm letting my
imagination get carried away like this...
Wha, wha, wha?!
President—
Oh, it looks like we coincidentally
got here at the right time.
What do you think?
I, um, very... pretty.
That's such an incoherent statement.
But...
I'm glad.
Whether the words that stumbled out of
my mouth were for the fireworks,
or maybe...
Shall we go home then?
Oh, sure.
At that time, I was still unclear
about why she'd been redoing it.