Toushin
High School
When I went to the cram school
to sign up for lessons...
No!
I have to take action,
or nothing will change!
I'll cross that bridge when I get there!
Ow.
I'm sorry!
I was distracted!
Oh, no, I was looking at my phone, too.
Wait, is that you, Kou-chan?
Huh?
I met a certain girl...
To be more precise, I met her again.
You're Shirota Koushi-kun, right?
I am, but...
I knew it!
It's been so long!
It's me, Ellie!
Wait, Ellie-chan?!
Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
You Two Seem Quite Intimate
You two seem quite intimate.
Toushin
High School
Sorry for the wait.
Toushin
High
School
Did you manage to sign up for the lessons?
Yeah.
It was a surprise running
into you in a place like this.
Last time was grade school,
so I guess that's five years ago?
Maybe?
But you haven't changed at all.
I recognized you immediately.
Oh, but you did get taller.
I used to be taller than you.
Her name is Ellie Evergreen.
We were the same age in grade school,
and until we went to different middle schools,
we used to play together a lot.
You did change though.
I guess you matured, or something.
You're really well-dressed, too.
You think so?!
Well, I suppose I am a bit of an amateur model.
Like in a fashion magazine? That's amazing!
Well, it's really only a small
thing here and there.
That's still amazing!
Hey, Kou-chan, do you have plans after this?
Just to go home. Why?
Then...
Wow!
This brings back memories!
It hasn't changed, huh?
If you wanted to catch up,
why didn't you pick a cooler spot?
Whatchu talkin' bout?!
A place steeped in memories is def
gon help get dem words flowin'!
Why are you talking like that?!
I haven't been to this park in quite a while.
If you go up these stairs here...
Look, Kou-chan!
This feels super low now!
Looks like her spirit's still the same.
Don't just stand around, come check it out!
Oh, right.
Oh yeah, that used to be fun too, huh?
Which?
You know, with that water fountain there.
Oh yeah, the water balloon fights.
Those were fun, huh?
Especially because we could
only do it in the summer.
Why don't we do it now?
With the added rule that the loser has to
go to the convenience store and get ice cream.
It's a bit embarrassing to do at this age...
Hmm, but we don't have any water balloons.
Okay, give me a minute!
Ellie, wait!
I got them!
From the convenience store!
Then why didn't you just buy the ice cream?!
Because then we'd miss out.
Ice cream is twice as good after a good battle.
Her spirit really is just like it used to be.
All right, but I won't hold back!
Yeah, you better not!
The rules are: The person to hit
the other with a balloon first wins.
Being hit by water from a balloon hitting
the ground and bursting doesn't count.
Got it?
All good.
Each person gets three balloons.
Got it.
Then I'll get to making my own balloons.
What's with that ominous look...
Oh, you'll see!
Ellie-chan?!
It's too late to object now, Kou-chan.
That's right.
We never said anything about
regulating the size of the balloons!
So I can make the hugest balloon
without violating the rules!
This battle is already decided!
Yeah, but if you put too much water in...
See!
D-Damn...
I guess that totally backfired...
Let me see if I have a towel.
Oh, it's fine.
I'm not wearing a bra, so it'll dry quickly.
Oh, I see.
What?
I mean, this top shows my shoulders,
so I usually wear a strapless bra.
But because it's in the laundry,
I just came without it.
This is no giggling matter!
You go rest over there for now!
While I go buy a towel!
But we weren't done!
Let's call it a day for today!
I'll also get ice cream while I'm there.
My treat, since you got
the water balloons, okay?
Oh, fine.
Then I'll have a Homerun Popsicle.
Is it me or does Ellie-chan
have her guard way too low?
Now I'm the one getting flustered.
If President had been there...
I saw how you were drooling over her
breasts straining against the thin cloth.
Disgusting.
If you can't even put on a poker face,
you should live with a ski mask
on your head starting tomorrow.
Is probably what she would have said.
But why did I think of her?
Sorry for the wait.
Here's the towel and the ice cream.
Thanks!
But look,
it's basically dried already.
That's summer for ya!
Err, Ellie-san...
I don't think you should
do that in front of others...
It's fine!
I don't do this in front of other people.
But you and I have a friendship
that transcends gender, right?
For ages now.
But we're in high school now.
Speaking of, which school are you aiming for?
I mean, it seems like you're planning ahead
if you're going to cram school this early.
So I was wondering if you're
considering a smartypants university.
Actually, I'm not even sure
I will go on to college.
Huh? Then why?
The other day,
someone kind of floated the idea
of going to the same college together.
But that person is super smart.
I told them that for my academic and
financial capabilities, the bar was too high,
and I probably won't be
able to go to college.
But then...
You disappointed them?
Rather than disappointed,
they looked kind of forlorn.
I thought they were just joking,
but then I thought that maybe
they were counting on me a bit...
The fact that I didn't even realize that,
and the fact that I can't fulfill
their wish made me feel kind of bad.
I don't have any plan whatsoever,
but I couldn't just do nothing...
Is how I'd describe it...
So this person... is she your girlfriend?
No, no, nonono! Th-that's out of the question!
Why are you denying it so hard?
Well, if she's not your girlfriend,
I guess you're in love with her.
Huh?
I mean, it's super obvious!
You wouldn't be agonizing
so much if you didn't love her.
Wow, even our Kou-chan is coming of age!
I do respect her... but love...
You dog, you.
Anyway, she probably invited you to
come along because she also loves you.
No! Never ever!
She only considers me
a useful piece of furniture!
Furniture?
What does that mean?
Well, either way.
Being able to go from agonizing to
springing to action isn't such an easy feat.
I see that side of you
hasn't changed from back then.
I think it's cool.
Don't tease me.
I do mean it, though.
Ah, cold!
Oh, sorry.
It's okay. Where's that towel...
Oh, right, sorry. You're not
supposed to do that to boys.
I don't think girls do that
to each other either?!
I do concede that the neck is off limits.
But I guess a finger or something
would be fine, right?
Not at all!
Licking other people's bodies
is a no-go in general!
If President had seen that just now...
Dirty. Unpleasant. Filthy.
I see you get aroused by anyone if it's a girl.
It seems your indiscriminate lust has
no regard for time or place, Erota-kun.
Is what she'd say.
Why did I think of President again?
What's that about me?
You two seem quite intimate.
Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
Please Put
Them On,
Takamine-san
You two seem quite intimate...
She's so gorgeous!
Is she a friend of yours?
Yeah, well, I'm not sure we're friends...
Licking each others' necks in public.
Quite bold to engage in petting
in broad daylight, Erota-kun.
We weren't licking each other!
What's petting?
You don't know?!
It's foreplay.
Please don't explain it!
A-Anyway, what are you doing here?!
I thought you weren't feeling so well?
What?
Are you insinuating that I wasn't in top form?
No, but...
I'm always well.
Trashta-kun, putting up with you causes
an untold amount of mental stress,
so both my body and mind need to be
in top condition at all times.
She does seem in top form...
By the way...
As I was walking by the park,
I seem to have witnessed some
incredibly uncouth behavior.
Why don't you explain what you were
doing with that loose-looking girl?
Is it prostitution?
Definitely not!
Did she say my curves are nice?
That isn't what she meant by "loose"!
It's not a big thing, really.
It was my idea.
Then things naturally
progressed to playing with these.
Let's play together.
With these...
Contains 3
These 0.01 mm leave everything in the dust
What a bad joke.
He's not someone who can
make such bold moves.
So, out with it. What were you really doing?
We really were planning on doing it.
Y-Yeah, as embarrassing at it sounds.
What?!
Has the heat made you lose your mind?!
Is it that shocking?
Since you're Kou-chan's friend,
and we're here...
How about all three of us get in the fray?
...get in...
What?!
Ellie-chan, I don't think we should.
We wouldn't want to become heated
and get her all soaked.
Soaking wet?!
Y-You need to stop being so full of yourself!
You really think someone like you
could get me soaking wet?!
Wait, you're game?
Awesome!
I'm going to get both of you
soaking wet! Let's do this!
Um, are you sure about this?
You can still get out of it...
Are you seriously going to do it?
Well, I guess. As long as you're okay with it...
That's not a decision you can
leave to someone else!
This isn't the kind of thing you do
with anyone just because you're in the mood!
The basis has to be an emotional
connection with someone you let into your heart!
Did you give up on college
so you could do stuff like this?!
There's lots to do if you want to find work,
like studying and acquiring qualifications!
I-I'm sorry!
The other day,
someone kind of floated the idea
of going to the same college together.
Wait, wait! It's not like that!
Kou-chan didn't want to play,
but I basically forced him!
I saw the water fountain in the park,
and I really wanted to have
a water balloon battle again...
Water Balloons
They're a blast~!
Wait a minute, are you Takane-chan?
Not sure which year it was in grade school,
but we used to be in PE together, right?
Don't you remember me?
It's Ellie.
You're...
The energetic girl who used
to play with Shirota-kun a lot?
Yes, yes!
But why are you whispering?
Anyway, I ran into Kou-chan today,
and I got nostalgic
and forced him into this...
the water balloon battle.
I mean, I was into it, too.
But as you said,
maybe it's not the best look for
high-schoolers to get soaked and fool around.
Somebody might get the wrong idea.
That's true.
Sorry, Takane-chan.
There are people who will reprimand
you without giving you a chance to explain, like so,
so you should refrain
from taking careless actions.
Wait, was I getting scolded
over a hypothetical situation?
Even if it's catching up with an old acquaintance,
you need to maintain decorum.
And now, please excuse me.
Wait, Takane-chan.
We just got together. Can't we talk a bit more?
No, I...
Come on, it's fine.
Hey, Kou-chan, could you go
buy us something to drink?
S-Sure...
I'm sorry, but I have somewhere to—
I'm sorry about before!
I went to all-girl middle and high schools,
so I don't really know if I'm
being too familiar with boys.
I was so happy about running into Kou-chan
that I kind of jumped on him
as if we were still kids...
T-That's nothing to worry about.
No, but it is!
I mean...
I wouldn't like it either, if someone
got all close to the person I love.
What?
But man, you've gotten
super cute, Takane-chan!
I mean you were always cute,
but now you're more... pretty?
Like, you've become beautiful.
You've also got this amazing aura.
Is it that thing where you get pretty
when you're in love?
What are you even talking about?
I don't consider him to be more than a serva—
Sheesh, stop hiding it!
But that part of you is super cute, too!
You not knowing when you're being
too familiar isn't just with boys...
What was that?
Sorry for the wait.
I got some drinks and snacks.
Listen.
I won't try to stop whatever
fantasies are in your head,
but please do not utter
those baseless claims to anyone.
Huh? Ah, okay, okay! I won't tell anyone!
Oh! I'm so sorry.
I forgot I had a shoot coming up!
I've gotta get home!
What about the drinks?
You two have them.
Oh, and Kou-chan!
See you at cram school!
Cram school?
Uh, well...
You're going to a cram school?
The same cram school as her?
Are you sure it's not a facility
for training promiscuous women?
How would I mistake that for a cram school?!
Well, there's still a lot of problems
I need to figure out, like tuition and such.
but it didn't sit right with me
to give up before I tried.
So, for starters, I signed up for the summer
lessons that I can pay for with my own savings.
Hoping that I can maybe
go to the same school as you...
Why didn't you discuss this with me?
I mean...
It was a snap decision,
so there was no good time to mention it...
It's annoying that natural-born
slut found out before me.
It's true that you have no reliable
income to pay for your tuition,
and with your academic abilities,
summer lessons will be a drop on a hot stone.
So you just recklessly
sprung into action without a plan,
just to quell the feeling of unease...
Is what I'd normally say.
But regarding the tuition,
by taking advantage of the university's
financial aid and scholarships,
you should be able to cover the rest
with income from a part-time job.
That leaves the issue
of your academic abilities.
There are no shortcuts in that regard.
So I'll help you
until the entrance exams.
Wha?
I couldn't!
I'm just doing this for my self-satisfaction...
I don't want to be a bother.
I said that I would help you,
so you simply ought to say,
"Thank you very much."
You redid it just for that?!
Here, the underwear.
Besides...
It's not a bother.
I felt like doing something in return because
you are trying to do something for me.
Now...
We're going to be busy.
Don't just stand there.
We're going home.
I'm going to work you so hard,
and then I'm going to work you
further till your legs give out.
So you better prepare yourself.
You mean preparing
for the entrance exam, right?!
Of course.
We only have so much time.
Let's get the assignments for
the summer break out of the way.
Shirota-kun.
You have a really poor grasp of the basics.
I'm sorry.
At this rate, you'll have trouble following
the lessons at cram school, will you not?
T-Temptation...
Hey!
Shirota-kun, focus on your assignments.
Kuro, you stop distracting him please.
I can hardly believe he said
he wants to go with me.
That is quite incredible,
isn't it, Kuro?