Let Me Do It!!
Let me do it!
Toushin High School
On the way home from cram school...
Man, that was rough.
Right? I'm exhausted.
Oh, are you on your way home now?
Such a coincidence. I was just
going home from my walk.
President!
It's Takane-chan!
If you're both so tired,
why don't we go take a break somewhere?
Oh, I have an idea!
There's this family restaurant I often go to.
Hiring
part-time
workers!!!!
Now serving new desserts!
I wonder if President will be all right...
She generally doesn't show
strong emotions towards anyone,
but the other day at the park...
Welcom—
Ellie, you really don't get tired
of this place, huh?
I actually came from my cram school today.
I see.
And what would you like to order?
We'll start with a mountain of fries
and three cups for the drink bar.
Coming right up.
Oh, and my shift will be done in an hour.
Roger that.
You know that waitress?
Yeah, she's from my high school.
Don't tell anyone,
but she makes the portion of fries extra big!
So that's why you picked this place.
It'll be my treat!
So let's all eat together!
Really? Thanks!
I'm sorry, I try not to eat
too many carbohydrates.
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't know!
Makes sense, though!
You have an amazing figure.
So how's cram school?
Oh, right.
They do review sessions and also offer
guidance for my weaker subjects,
so I'm able to keep up so far.
I see.
And it's a relief to have
Ellie-chan in my class.
That keeps me from getting too nervous.
Oh, same for me!
I mean, I never thought we'd be studying
together again once we entered high school.
We used to do homework together a lot
when we were in grade school.
Oh, so you like studying
with girls, huh, Shirota-kun?
You insisted on coming over the other day
because you wanted my help with school work, too.
Despite the fact that my parents
were away that night...
Actually, that time was...
That makes sense!
Figures that you're just as smart
as you used to be, Takane-chan!
If only you had been there back then...
Big Strawberry
The only memories I have are of us
abandoning our homework and playing.
I wonder.
Even if I had been there,
I might not have been a match
for Shirota-kun's fickle nature.
The other time, too...
He couldn't focus on studying anymore,
so he strong-armed me into cosplaying
as a cat to clear his head.
Wha?! No, that was your—
That sounds so fun!
Was it Halloween?
Halloween?!
Oh yeah, let's all hold a group
study session together!
And maybe a sleepover afterwards.
Just the group study session, maybe.
Oh, come on.
We used to do sleepovers
all the time before!
Ellie-san.
That is an extremely dangerous suggestion.
Because...
Not only did he stay the night saying
the heavy rain prevented him from going home,
but he also pushed
my unclad body to the ground.
T-That was you! The lightni—
What's that about lightning?
Unclad? What does that mean?
Phew, she didn't get it.
Um, President, is everything all right?
It seems you're on edge or something...
I think it's quite natural
for me to be on alert.
She only knows
the pure you from the past.
I am revealing to her that you've become
a degenerate controlled by your desires.
Hold on, like half of that was made up!
Oh, is it, though?
It seems we have a discrepancy
in what we remember.
Even then, it can't hurt to listen to my side.
After all, I'm the one who understands
the current you better than her.
Still...
All right, see you...
Ellie-san.
Please be sufficiently wary
of Shirota-kun's behavior.
You're still on that?!
Oh, Takane-chan!
Could we maybe talk?
I don't mind...
Kou-chan, I'll see you tomorrow at cram school!
Yeah, sure.
I wonder what's going on.
Can I really leave those two alone?
What did you want to talk about?
I'm sorry, Takane-chan.
I didn't realize.
What do you mean?
You came to our cram school
because you're worried
that I like Kou-chan and that I'm
making moves on him, right?
W-What are you talking abou—
And then I did it again...
Having fun recounting the good times
I had with Kou-chan in the past...
I'm really sorry!
I made you feel jealous.
H-Hold on!
You're stacking theory on delusion and—
But don't worry!
Kou-chan and I are
totally not like that at all.
I mean, I'm with someone!
Oh... really?
Yes.
If anything, I'd be more
into you than Kou-chan...
Just kidding.
Wha?
Ellie, sorry for the wait.
Oh, no worries.
Well, I'm going home then.
You take care on the way home, Takane-chan!
S-Sure...
What's this?
Were you waiting for me?
You look like the bronze statue
in front of Shibuya Station.
Did you just compare me to Hachikou?!
So what did you talk about?
We had a lecture about
how you're lust incarnate.
You're joking, right?!
I'm joking.
We only talked about trivial matters.
I see...
Well, if I had to say one thing,
it's that I realized I've been
unjustly suspicious of her.
Ellie, that girl is your type, isn't she?
You realized?!
It's fine, though! We're just friends!
This reminds me...
The other day, Ellie-san foisted
these leftover ones onto me.
Water Balloons
Oh, really?
How about we have some fun?
Huh?
The one who lands more hits
with the balloons wins.
The victor gets to make
one demand of the loser.
What do you say?
You really want to do this?
What now?
You're saying you can do it
with Ellie-san, but not with me?
N-No! That's not what I meant...
After some back and forth, it begins
I doubt I stand a chance against her,
even if I play to win.
Even then, I can't risk dousing her in water,
so I need to be careful not to hit her!
Not bad, Shirota-kun.
You got the first hit on me.
Um, I don't think that one was really...
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
My bra is visible now...
Quite skillful.
Was that on purpose?
Wha?! I'm sorry!
Wait...
This situation seems familiar.
Oh yeah, it's like when Ellie and I played.
But that time, it wasn't that
her bra became visible.
Say. Care to explain why
you seem so distracted?
Don't tell me you and she experienced
something more than her bra becoming visible?
Wait, was she watching Ellie
and me from the beginning that day?!
N-N-Not really?!
That's not...
I meant to toy with you more
by feigning a close fight,
but I accidentally ended you in an instant.
Now, what will I order the loser to do...?
Please go easy on me.
Let me think...
Right, then how about this.
I worked up a sweat,
so I'll have you lick it up.
S-Say what?!
What is that even?!
This also kind of reminds me
of that other situation...
Could it be that she's deliberately
recreating the events of that day?
Um, President,
are you still mad about me taking my plans
for the future lightly and playing around?
Is there any reason for me to be mad?
Right now, you're earnestly engaging
with shaping your own future.
Then it doesn't have to be
such an abnormal order.
We're in a public park, too.
Besides, me licking it would make it dirty.
It's fine.
We're the only ones here.
And it wouldn't be dirty.
I'll disinfect it when I get home.
Then wouldn't it be better
if I didn't do it at all?!
So what?
Having your neck licked by a girl is fine,
but you can't do the licking yourself?
So she is holding a grudge?!
That's not really it.
Then hurry up and follow the order.
So... the sweat on your neck?
What?
Who said anything about my neck?
Take a good look.
There's no sweat anywhere on my neck.
But under my clothes...
my armpits...
my chest...
my stomach, and my inner thighs.
If you were to lick,
those would probably be the areas.
I'll be generous and allow you to pick a spot.
All of those are impossible!
Sheesh, I know in reality
you want to lick all of it.
Still pretending not to be a perv.
You know I could force you
to do my entire body, right?
I-Is she really planning on making me do this?
Once she makes up her mind,
there's no force that can change it.
That means I have to pick
a relatively safe spot
before she gets even more outrageous ideas!
Well, please go ahead.
O-Okay...
I thought that the stomach was the most
normal place given the choices...
But when I think about it,
it's not normal at all!
With Ellie-chan, I was on the receiving end...
but this time, I have to actively do
it to President's stomach...
When you stare that intently,
it almost makes me sweat more.
I'm sorry!
Her skin... it's almost translucent...
it smells so good...
and now the moisture
trailing down this skin is...
Come on, hurry.
Good work, Licky-ta-kun.
You weren't half bad.
Oh, and just so you know,
you best not waste time deeply
pondering, "What was this for?".
I haven't been paying
too much attention to you lately,
so that's why I spent time with you.
That's the only reason.
With that said, if today's
experience was too intense
and ends up overwriting your memories
of being in this park with her, I'm sorry.
At that time, I felt like I heard something
that sounded like her core motivation...
Shirota-kun?
Shirota-kun?!
But the fever got to that memory,
and it faded along with my swirling vision.
Hold on!
I'll undo it right away!
Please
Put Them On,
Takamine-san
Please
Put Them On,
Takamine-san
It's the last day of summer break.
We've come to a leisure
facility in our prefecture.
That's quite a nice view.
It's my first time here too,
but it's really nice.
Toushin
High School
Earlier that week...
After finishing the summer classes
at cram school,
I received a message from the president.
This seems ideal for unwinding.
Let's go.
Okay.
President said she'd help me study
after the summer classes were over,
and that she doesn't really
want anything in return.
But I still want to repay her somehow!
I've studied up on this place, too,
so I'm going to be a good host
and have her enjoy herself!
Where do you want to go first?
If you have any preferences,
I don't mind hearing them.
Oh, then why don't we get some
drinks before we set out?
There's a cafe that offers
takeout right there.
Let's do that.
Oh, that reminds me of a coincidence.
I received two drink coupons
from an acquaintance.
Be grateful.
I'll treat you to a cu—
I got them!
Black is fine, right?
What about the money?
Oh, it's my treat.
I mean, you invited me out today!
I was feeling like a vanilla latte today.
As a closet,
you're supposed to sense what your
owner wants the most and bring that.
Here, you may have these coupons.
R-Right.
What are you standing around for?
Hurry and put them on me.
Oh, right!
She went behind the building by herself?
That basically never happens...
What should we do next?
Apparently there's a Nordic
general goods store up ahead.
Could we go there?
Sure, that's fine.
Looks like this is it.
That's pretty cute.
It's got a warmth to it.
You think so?
Yes!
Excuse me, I'm going to the bathroom.
Sure.
Was there anything that caught your eye?
I thought the carved wood coasters looked nice.
And you were intrigued by that
stuffed animal, right?
Not really.
Oh...
I did say it was cute, but I don't need it.
Gazing at a mirror is much more soothing for
my soul than staring at a stuffed animal.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I actually got you this as a present
for inviting me today...
Um, President?
I'd rather turn it around and gift you
something before accepting any alms from you.
Carved wood coaster, right?
But why?!
I only had good intentions...
So, what are we doing next?
Oh, then right here.
It seems you can get on a boat.
I've never been on one,
but what do you think?
Well, if you want to try it.
This feels nice.
I don't know if it's because we're floating.
You're right.
Being on a boat feels nicer than I expected.
Oh?
So it's your first time on a boat, too?
You've got so many experiences,
I thought you'd done this already as well.
E-Even I can have first times...
I-Is that wrong?
N-No.
Anyway, I'll take over rowing for you.
Seeing you totally exhausted
isn't pleasant.
No, I'm still fine!
Hey, I said I'd take over!
I'm really fine!
Jump!
What?!
P-President?!
Oh no.
I accidentally slipped.
Yeah, no, that was on purpose.
I don't like using my ability
for things like this,
but I also can't stay in these wet clothes...
She undid it to the point
before we got on the boat?
But where is she?
Sheesh.
Um, President... what are you...
Don't "what are you" me.
Stop looking so confused already.
So, where do you want to go next?
If you dawdle too long,
the day is going to end.
That's not what I meant.
Why did you put them on yourself?
Th-This is because you were
so dense, I couldn't wait anymore.
You better repent for causing me this trouble!
I'm sorry!
I was supposed to be a good host for her today.
I'm just making her more and more displeased.
I wonder what I did wrong.
I'm sorry.
It seems whatever I'm doing is unnecessary.
No, that's not it.
I don't know why,
but you're putting up a big front today.
At this rate, the only thing you'll
gain from today is the exhaustion.
I've been trying
to show you my appreciation.
As a reward...
for working hard on summer classes...
Wha?
Could it be...
That the reason
she was being weird all day is...
that she was looking out for me?
What?
Why do you look so utterly shocked?
I-I specifically wanted to reward you.
If anything, not accepting that
with gratitude is wrong.
Thank you so much!
But I'm fine!
You're already treating me well enough.
Not only are you helping me
study for the entrance exams,
but more importantly, I'm more
optimistic now thanks to you.
Besides...
Last night, I put together a plan for today,
trying to come up with things
that you would enjoy.
That's already enough for me to have fun.
Huh, look at you with your smug lines.
W-Was that smug?
Besides, if you think someone
like you could bring me joy,
I must have sunken quite low in your eyes.
W-Wha?! No, that's not what I...
You're really...
so cocky.
Well, then.
Why don't I take you up on your offer
and hear what you've planned next.
Huh?
You were going to make sure
I enjoyed myself, right?
When you put me on the spot like that,
I'm not so sure anymore...