[EP. 04] Before our Lips Touch
So hot…
Why is it so hot in fall?
Oh?
That’s Wook!
Hey!
You scared me!
Let me have a sip.
Kyaaaa! Your coffee is just the best!
Hey,
Are you with me?
What? Yeah…
Why is the weather like this in fall?
I know…
I want my break back.
Me, too…
I want to skip class and go hang out
somewhere nearby.
You, too? Should we go?
This weather is forcing us to go have fun.
So, you studied hard when it was cold?
You’re not one to judge, Yeo Reum.
At least I don’t blame the weather.
I’m just saying…
Argh, I really don’t want to go to class…
Gosh!
I’m late for class!
See you later!
What?
Okay…
One-sided love
emotion that writes the same behavior differently
What are you doing?
Ah… Nothing…
Let me have a sip.
It’s mine!
A Day Before Us