[EP. 05] Before I Noticed You
Why soup?
You kept saying how hot it was…
I don’t know..
So hot..
Did you drink last night?
Speak for yourself.
Geez…What are you doing!?
Oh,
Hello, Ha Eun
Hey, Wook
You’re here to eat alone?
Where’s Yeo Reum?
Yeo Reum?
She’s coming after her team project meeting.
He would just not say hi, huh?
Definitely not my type.
Hey, say something. Ha Eun is here.
Ha Eun, have you seen him talk?
Not really…
He really likes cute things.
Whenever he sees cats, he just…
Argh
What? Cats?
Oh… It’s nothing…
Make an order…
But you, seriously…
Is Yeo Reum coming late?
No, she said she’d be here soon.
Isn’t it hot today?
I should order something cool.
Ah?
What are you doing? You said you were hot.
I’m cold now.
What’s up with him…
Consideration; the first step to noticing others
Hi hi, sorry I’m late.
You must be hungry. Order something.
I’m hot after running here.
I should get something cold.
A Day Before Us