Goto Ryuji isn't fighting.
But thanks to that, I can witness
a battle between S-rank hunters.
Now,
let's begin.
You want to compare strengths?
That makes it simple.
Alright. Let's see who's stronger.
He's fast, so I shouldn't
get into close combat with him.
My expertise lies in long-range combat.
Hoshino, this is too dangerous.
Take him down quickly.
Master, this arena is reinforced
with top-tier magic gems, right?
Yes.
But it seems we need to reassess
the reinforcement standards.
They're the top-tier hunters
even among S-ranks.
Merely restraining their arms
won't suffice.
You must be prepared
to break them if necessary.
Yikes.
Is his name Atsushi Kumamoto?
Seems he's not the combative type.
Darn it. I'm bad at handling
these situations.
My resolve wasn't enough after all.
Perhaps he's using us to test them,
so as to see if they have
the resolve to fight the ants.
Since you chose me to test them,
I'll gladly have them give you an answer.
I can't handle this.
They're all monsters.
An A-rank like me stands no chance.
That's not true.
You're plenty strong too, Master.
Looks like I've won this match.
Got smashed into the ground.
This is the first time.
Does this count as my win?
Tch.
How long will you keep running...
Do you think I'm weaker than Hunter Cha?
I'm being underestimated.
Can't read her movements.
The Dancer Cha Hae-in.
After seeing her dance-like footwork,
it's clear her title is well-deserved.
I need to help Hunter Baek.
What kind of move was that?
Oh no. I acted reflexively.
- Ah.
- He's about to lose his temper.
Once he becomes like that,
no one knows what he might do.
Should we stop him?
If there's a risk of injury.
So fast.
This doesn't look good.
You could say I'm meddling,
but this has gone
beyond friendly sparring.
Who do you think you are?
No way. He instantly subdued
the enraged Kumamoto.
Is he really a Mage?
Yes, that's correct.
I'll have to verify it myself.
Hunter Cha. Shall we admit defeat?
- Hunter Baek appears to be eliminated too.
- Okay.
Even going all out, I still couldn't win.
Hunter Sung.
Our guild master Goto asked
if he may request a match.
He exudes combat spirit.
Is he trying to gauge my strength?
A perfect chance to test
how much I've improved
since conquering the Demon's Castle.
He actually smiled in my presence.
Mr. Goto.
Hunter Sung agreed.
- But with one condition.
- Condition?
He stated he'd consent
only if you go all out.
Interesting.
The 4th Jeju Island Raid Mission
is imminent.
Our nation will collaborate with Japan
to ensure complete preparations.
Aren't you working today?
It's my day off. I told you yesterday.
Did you?
The hunters are working hard.
We should do our jobs properly too.
Hello.
Well,
I'd like to ask about sentry team
of the Jeju Island Raid Mission.
What's going on?
The legendary 10th S-rank hunter.
He's quite fiery,
challenging Goto to a duel.
I saw his combat skills
in A-rank dungeons.
But can he handle an S-rank hunter?
You're surrounded by hunters today.
Do you feel alright?
I can't go to the battlefield
holding my nose.
We're not going to stop them?
For a close combat
between a Fighter and a Mage,
normally, we should have intervened.
But my thoughts align with yours,
Hunter Cha.
Don't you have expectations of him?
If it's truly as I predicted
that Hunter Sung is the Awakened
who can keep evolving...
Then let's start...
Hey, I haven't finished speaking yet.
With that kind of speed and movement,
you claim you are a Mage?
Don't make me laugh.
I'll expose your true nature.
True, he's completely different
from other S-rank hunters.
But, I can still dodge.
He smiled again.
His attacks are too fast to see.
He's dodging brilliantly.
Just avoiding those attacks
is already remarkable.
He's not just dodging.
He's testing his opponent's strength.
The more he dodges, the angrier I get.
I've changed my mind.
I'll eliminate you with full power.
Hunter Sung!
I almost lost one of my eyes there.
He didn't grab my wrist, but my hand.
Are you mocking me?
I don't understand you.
But if I grabbed your wrist,
the game would end.
You don't want it
to end like this either, do you?
Hey, Mr. Goto is serious.
If they keep fighting,
neither will come out unscathed.
Ice...?
Hunter Sung.
Mr. Goto.
Let's stop here.
No one can take responsibility
if something goes wrong.
Please tell him the duel is over.
Y...yes.
- Did I interfere too much?
- No.
Only getting a scratch
from fighting Goto, that's impressive.
I got too carried away.
However,
now I've known about everyone's strengths
and infiltrated Shadow Soldiers
into their shadows.
I'll send you the list
of raid mission participants later.
Please also send it
to our vice guild master.
I will.
Chairman Go.
What is it, Hunter Sung?
Regarding the Jeju Island raid mission...
Ryuji.
There's an exceptionally
skilled hunter here.
Can't be stronger than
the guild master of Draw Sword Guild.
I'm not sure.
Which hunter are you referring to?
Sung Jinwoo.
He's a Reawakened,
recently promoted S-rank hunter.
That's strange.
This person isn't on
the raid mission's hunter list.
What?
Hunter Sung is not
joining the Jeju Island raid mission?
He must have his reasons.
But...
Byung-gu isn't listed either...
We now have 15 S-rank hunters.
This time we must...
Secure victory.
- I'm home.
- Jinwoo, you're late.
Welcome back, Jinwoo.
Dinner is ready.
I'm back.
My mother has awakened
after four years of sleep.
She needs me now.
So...
I can't go to Jeju Island.
Food supplies are exhausted.
We have started eating each other.
This land no longer
has food to nourish us.
We can't continue like this.
We must leave this island.
We must have a stronger child
to lead us.
They need my powerful child.
Grow stronger, my child.
Ant-type monsters are evolving
at an alarming speed.
During the 3rd Jeju raid mission,
ants were still crawling on the ground.
This is the latest confirmed situation.
Their forms now resemble those of humans
with massive wings on their backs.
The Hunter's Association announced
new strategies against ant-type monsters.
There it is, darn monster.
I'll be your opponent as an S-rank hunter.
It's too dangerous. Don't go.
Why must I join the sentry team?
But Miss Han, you're an E-rank hunter.
- Ouch...
- You have the nerve.
I'm sorry!
Considering the possibility
of ants landing on the mainland,
the Association requests
all hunters to join the sentry team.
Finally, it's tomorrow.
The Jeju Island raid mission
is about to begin.
This is the First Fleet,
which arrived at the target location,
coastal waters of the Jeju Island.
Second Fleet
arrived at the target location.
Third Fleet is about
to enter the alert zone.
Fourth Fleet is advancing.
Estimated to arrive
at the target location in 5 minutes.
Master.
Is our strength enough against the ants?
We won't know unless we try.
Our sentry team is here
precisely for such contingencies.
We must eliminate the ants.
Don't let them reach the mainland.
Cool, Master.
I, Jung Yoontae,
pledge to follow you for life.
Then I leave this place to you.
We won't get to step in anyway.
We'll just be idling here all day.
There's always a contingency.
It's because you are here
that I can depart to the front line
with peace of mind.
- Be careful on your way.
- Hmm.
Huh? Why was Minsung assigned there?
It could be troublesome.
Transfer him to the rear.
Reports from all units.
All preparations on mainland coast
and waters surrounding Jeju Island
are complete.
The decoy unit has also
landed on the island.
Hmm.
Many hunters have
responded to this operation.
Furthermore,
his decision to join
has given us a boost of confidence.
Byung-gu!
Never thought you'd come.
Without a healer like me here,
you'd get instantly killed, Yoonho.
You'll charge straight at magic beasts
the moment you see them, right?
If I'm slow, you'll be the one dying.
Is this the central urban area
on the island?
This is Alpha, all units respond.
Bravo, in position.
Charlie, in position.
Delta, ready to go.
Live broadcast...
Yes.
However, to prevent accidents,
the footage will be delayed by 10 minutes.
As a photographer
from the Hunter Report Team,
I will broadcast the details
of this battle to the public.
Okay. Hunters demonstrate their
true abilities when protecting others.
This will be an intense battle.
Are you up for this?
Rest assured.
Despite appearances, I'm an A-rank hunter.
I'm accustomed to filming
in dangerous zones.
That's good.
This might be ordinary folk's last chance
to witness an S-rank raid mission.
No, we must make sure it's the final one.
We must succeed this time.
If this operation fails,
our nation will likely
be erased from the map.
This country needs heroes...
The assault team is ready to deploy.
Very well, I declare
the 4th Jeju Island raid mission
officially commences.
All units, deploy!
Roger.
The decoy unit is moving out.
The magic power energy is terrifying.
They're making their move too.
Hey, they're heading this way.
Open the hatch.
I'll handle them.
Incredible...
There are many of them.
Seems we'll need drastic measures.
I've finally reached this place.
Standing on this land once again...
No wonder he's the Ultimate Hunter.
Very reliable.
Alright everyone, let's descend.
Japan's hunters can stall those ants
for at most one hour.
Meaning we must eliminate
the queen within that timeframe.
Is everyone ready?
We can definitely do this.
Let's move.
We're commencing our operation.
Activate interference wave.
Interference wave activated.
Now the ants won't receive
the queen's distress signals.
Yikes!
Kumamoto, fear will get you killed.
Could we have eliminated all these ants
before they can kill the queen?
Possibly. Where is Kenzo?
He's over there playing.
Just like a child.
Did you see those flames?
Must be from that Choi guy.
I wonder who would win if I fought him.
Could be alternating temperatures.
Exits have been sealed.
Let's move quickly
while they're all lured out.
But there are so many tunnels.
How do we find the tunnel
leading to the queen?
What are you doing? It's too dangerous.
We don't have time to check each one.
Just find the deepest tunnel.
Looks like that's the one.
Daily quest is complete.
The streets are empty today.
All S-rank Hunters
on this raid mission are top-tier ones.
They could easily complete the operation.
Even without someone like me.
Is the queen really here?
Maybe it abandoned them and fled.
This is an island,
so it can't go anywhere.
Everyone, check this out.
An egg chamber...
The queen's chamber must be nearby.
Look.
That egg...
Is that also an ant egg?
It's enormous...
Our mission is to kill the queen.
Don't bother with other things.
But can't blame him for reacting that way.
Ant evolution remains unpredictable.
If there's an ant from that giant egg...
Darn.
Annoying pest made me hurt my shoulder.
Want me to heal you?
But it's not free.
Shimizu.
Quit fooling around
and heal me right away.
There's something I want.
Instead of money...
Here we go again...
Fine.
What exactly do you want...