Huh?
There's something there.
Watch out!
I know.
This one...
Kenzo!
Got you.
Each one has S-rank strength.
But,
no matter how strong,
they are still magic beasts.
Their movements are monotonous.
Facing hunters with various tactics,
they are no match at all.
The ants' exoskeletons are really tough.
Right.
Luckily, there aren't many of them.
No need to worry even if there are.
I will support you from the rear.
Rest assured.
Never thought someone
afraid of fighting would say that.
No more sarcasm, Yoonho.
Is this your first mission?
Don't forget,
these magic beasts can still live
for a while with their heads blown off.
You should at least cripple them.
Oh. Okay.
The enemies get stronger as we go deeper,
but we still haven't seen
any ants walking on two legs.
Yeah, I think those are the ones
arranged to be the queen ant's guards.
In other words,
we still have a long way to go.
Are we sure this is the right direction?
It is. Probably.
Hey.
The direction is right.
There's a strong smell of powerful
magic beasts coming from deep in the cave.
Oh my, at this distance,
President Baek's ability
should allow him to see it, right?
Geez.
Is that it?
The queen ant
is in the deepest place ahead.
There are many guards protecting her.
The decoy unit outside has its limits.
Also, there are many S-rank guards ahead.
The strength of the queen ant is unknown.
It will probably be a tough fight.
But with our lineup,
we will definitely win.
Let's go.
- Yes!
Is it around here?
I wanted to check on Charlie
since we lost contact.
Where on earth did they go?
They did kill ants here.
Hm?
These are Fujishima's glasses...
Are they...
What's wrong?
What's this?
What is this smell that hits me?
I've never smelled
anything like this before.
Did you reach Charlie?
Not yet.
Is there a problem?
We don't have time
to worry about others now.
This time you have to be serious.
No other choice, huh?
What a grand welcome.
Then we must also show proper courtesy.
Let's proceed as planned.
I'm counting on you,
the ultimate weapon of mankind.
I understand.
Your opponent is here.
I usually don't use such strong power.
But it seems today I have to
use all my trump cards.
That's right. No need to hold back.
Even if I must turn into an ugly form,
I'll kill every last one of these insects.
That is
President Baek's magic beast form.
The battle has started.
Viewership has surpassed 80 percent.
Go forward a bit more,
and get a clearer shot.
380 percent of the viewership?
I must meet their expectations.
This is the BOSS room
of an S-rank dungeon.
Are you out of your mind?
No, of course not.
Please stay behind me.
The battle will become even more intense.
Look, everyone.
The S-rank hunters have
finally reached the queen ant.
Now is the time to fulfill
our long-cherished wish.
A fierce battle unfolds before your eyes.
These S-rank hunters
who usually don't fight together
are showcasing perfect teamwork
in this joint offensive.
Hunter Cha's sharp strike
pierced through the ant.
It's down.
The last guard ant is killed.
Now is the time, attack!
Take this.
The queen ant without guards
is just a living target.
As long as I'm here,
no matter how many times,
I will make you all stand up again.
I won't let you get close to the healer.
Please subdue it like this.
Does it still have such strong power?
Is it a dying scream?
No, it's not quite the same.
- Don't run away.
- You can't escape.
- Hunter Cha!
- Miss Cha!
I'm going up.
Another hit.
It's done!
Master.
Did we finally succeed?
It's over... right?
Yes.
With the queen ant dead, the remaining
ants will naturally go extinct in a year.
Then this place will become
a habitable area for humans again.
But its final scream...
What are you talking about?
We killed that queen ant!
We got revenge for Eunseok!
Yeah.
We have a problem.
The ants are heading towards the nest.
What? The interference wave has no effect.
What's happened?
Collect information and report back to me.
The flame prison has been broken.
What's going on?
This is much faster than expected.
The queen ant's scream.
Is it...
Calling for its companions?
But even if it is,
the ants outside can't
break Master's techniques.
Then what exactly is...
Something is approaching.
Black ant.
A chilling sense of oppression.
And this smell...
What is this?
That is not an ordinary magic beast.
There's no time.
If we don't kill it...
It just walked past.
Miss Cha...
Don't underestimate me!
Take this.
It took it?
Be amazed.
We have a reliable companion.
The skill to protect oneself, camouflage.
After using this skill,
I become invisible.
Although I'm immobile during use,
this is enough for a healer.
As long as I'm here,
our team will never lose.
I did use camouflage.
Does it mean...
Byung-gu!
Yoonho...
Run away.
Run away!
Yoonho.
You wretch...
You all are too weak.
Our queen ant is dead.
Just killing soldiers is not fair.
Where is your king?
King.
There is a strong one outside.
Outside...
Is it referring to Goto?
No, there's no time to think now.
We need to leave here quickly.
Darn. Have the other ants returned too?
Something's not right.
Not just Charlie,
even Delta has become unreachable.
It might be poor reception.
But they should be
within the communication range.
Bravo, please respond.
This is Bravo.
Can you contact Charlie and Delta?
No, we've lost contact
with them since earlier.
Do you want us to go over
and check on them?
We are on our way now.
After you finish,
wait for me at the rendezvous point.
I understand.
How could it be...
It's me.
I didn't receive your scheduled contact.
There are casualties here.
Oh?
That's quite unexpected.
Didn't you order them
only to kill mutated magic beasts
to avoid any risks?
They are simply too weak.
That is something you would say.
Alright.
With your abilities, missing a few people
shouldn't be an issue, right?
By the way, is the team over there
with the queen ant?
Yes.
But just a moment ago,
it was confirmed that
the interference waves have failed.
All the ants outside
have returned to the nest.
Hmm...
What do you think
their chances of survival are?
Given their strength,
the chances are zero.
Very well.
Despite Japan's best efforts in support,
the allied forces were annihilated,
so we had no choice
but to temporarily retreat.
We will inherit their will
and continue to advance towards
Jeju Island
with the second assault team at sea,
gradually weakening
the neighboring country's power
to make our country the one
to conquer the S-rank gates.
It's about time.
Everyone, retreat.
Meet up with the second
assault team at sea.
Forget it.
Chairman Matsumoto has given the order.
We are retreating.
We'll come back later
to retrieve the bodies.
Ishida!
Leave quickly.
Join Bravo and meet up
with the second team.
Prepare for the next offensive.
But...
You staying here will only get in the way.
- Go.
- Understood.
It has an extremely piercing aura.
Are you the king?
Interesting.
An ant can speak.
King...
That's right.
I am the king.
What is this magic power?
This feeling...
I have had it before.
That is...
Choi Jong-in. Increase the firepower.
Stop pushing me.
This is my limit.
We all suffered fatal injuries.
We have no more strength to fight.
Even Choi Jong-in, as the lifesaver...
Is this the end?
What is happening?
These black soldiers are...
Exchange.