What is going on?
These black soldiers...
What exactly are they?
C-Could it be...
Why? Why is he here?
Mr. Song.
This means the broadcast
has been interrupted, right?
What exactly happened?
Can't get through.
There seems to be chaos there.
Our top priority is to confirm
the safety of the Hunters.
Gathering information comes after.
Yes.
Director!
Our phone lines are about to be overloaded
due to inquiries from viewers!
And they're asking us
to broadcast the live footage!
I would if I could!
Forget about live footage,
we can't even contact them now!
And what if all the S-Rank Hunters
were wiped out?
Hey, answer me!
What's going on over there?
Darn!
The camera malfunctioned.
At this critical moment...
Iron!
Do it.
I'm completely confused.
What are these things?
And why is Hunter Sung here?
Hunter Sung.
When did you come here?
And how did you get here?
I'll explain later.
Let me heal your injuries first.
Please drink this.
Oh, right.
This can't be transferred.
Oral medication?
Is it subspace magic?
Master Ma.
Please open your mouth.
This is...
The wounds...
...have all recovered.
She hasn't recovered yet.
Why isn't it working on her?
BECAUSE THE HIT POINTS OF THE TARGET
ARE TOO LOW, POTION DOES NOT WORK.
Is this the same as last time?
It's not good.
Her aura is getting weaker.
I can't heal such a serious injury.
Let's get out of here quickly.
I'll clear the way.
- Okay.
- Wait!
They come wave after wave...
Their numbers are too many.
Master!
How is the assault team doing?
We can't grasp it yet.
There must be temporary signal
interference on the whole island.
We've tried to contact Japan's team,
but we can't reach them either.
The same goes for private media.
The image was cut off
after the black ant appeared.
Restore communication quickly.
Order the medical
and recovery teams to stand by.
Roger!
I have never...
...hated my body and heart so much.
Even if I can't help,
I want to fight alongside them.
Master...
Please...
Please be safe.
Geez, what is going on?
I thought the image was cut off,
but even the TV broke.
I can't believe it.
Hitting it won't fix it.
I'll go back to my room for a bit.
Maybe I can find some information
on my phone.
What an impatient child.
What's going on? Explain it.
Mr. Goto's survival signal is off.
From the communication before the outage
and the strong enemy reaction
at that moment, I believe he died in battle.
What about the others?
We are currently checking them now.
You better hurry up.
If we keep losing Hunters,
it'll affect the plan.
Yes.
Goto get killed?
How useless!
What is happening on that island?
Igris and Iron can manage
to fend off them.
But the infantry are at
a slight disadvantage.
I do want to enhance combat power,
but there are too many people here.
No.
Everyone.
At this rate, we'll be in danger.
I will carve out a path.
So I ask you...
...to follow behind him.
Others clad in black will
hold off the ants for us.
If some ants slip through and attack you,
please deal with them by yourselves.
Got it. You can leave that to us.
Yeah.
And also, please do not
disclose what you see next.
Could it be...
That ant has returned.
Does it mean...
...it has killed Goto?!
There is no king outside.
Is the one called the king here?
The shadow attached to Goto lost contact
because of that one?
Ah...
Hey!
Are you the king of humans?
Oh?
You can talk even though
you're just an insect.
Human...
Such a strong presence.
As expected,
an insect is just an insect.
Even if it's Hunter Sung...
To face it alone...
Director, the image is restored!
What...
This is...
Start the broadcast, quickly!
Eh?!
If we start now, it will completely
turn into a live broadcast!
If something happens,
we won't have time to respond!
We've already cut off once!
It can't get any worse!
Do it!
Y-Yes!
Our— No...
The fate of this battle...
...depends on this person.
Mr. Song!
Is that...
This is...
No way...
Why...
Big brother?!
He said he was going out for a bit...
Eh?!
He joined it again?
I knew you'd join them, Hunter Sung!
But how did he get to the island?
That is not important right now.
Let's believe in him.
Why would a Mage
get so close to the enemy?!
He has underestimated that ant!
He took a punch to the face!
So weak.
You are not—
Master Baek...
Master Choi...
Is he really a mage-type Hunter?
I am not too sure either.
I didn't know he was so strong.
He is very tough.
Is it because of his shell?
What an intense battle!
As an A-Rank Hunter, just standing
would use up all my strength.
The impact of their magical power
is almost making me lose consciousness.
I'm being pushed back...?
Why...
Who is...
...this human?!
This is...
This is a deadly poison
I refined from the toxins
inside the surrounding marine life
by using my magic power.
You can't move anymore.
You're finished now.
Human...
...die!
Seven out of ten are dead.
Are you kidding me?
No, it's the truth.
Contact has been made
with the remaining Hunters.
So we have confirmed it.
More than half died?!
How can you be so useless?!
And now strong reactions
reappeared near the crater.
That should be the one
that killed Mr. Goto.
As it fought with Goto,
how is it still alive?!
And you said it went to the nest?! Why?!
I'm not sure.
Maybe it has some purpose.
Or maybe it returned injured...
The condition of
the Hunters there is unknown.
But if they're still alive,
they'll run into it.
Even Goto couldn't kill it.
They will never be a match,
as they are exhausted.
That ant should also be worn out
from continuous battles.
As long as we can kill it,
the rest are just minions.
There is still a chance.
Immediately retrieve
the three remaining Hunters!
Unite with the second assault team
at sea and attack again!
That's the order.
A helicopter will pick you up right away.
Got it.
We are going to implement Plan No. 9.
Let's go.
No...
That thing is a monster...
We can't defeat it...
Get yourself together!
Have some guts, will you?!
We can't possibly defeat that one!
We have to escape!
We will be killed if we don't escape!
You are a disgrace.
We have no choice but to do it.
Wasn't he poisoned?
Was he alright?
I wouldn't be surprised
by anything anymore.
So you had a secret weapon, huh?
No wonder you seemed so confident.
BUFF: HEALTH AND LONGEVITY
DETOXING IS COMPLETE
However, I don't know if it's because
my perception has improved.
I can sense its emotions...
...and its anxiety.
Actually, it's the same for me.
Every second counts now.
I have to finish this soon!
Poison is ineffective against him.
Competing in strength is meaningless.
Then...
ITEM: DEMON MONARCH'S DAGGER
His speed is not inferior to mine.
And he's getting even faster.
Why is this happening?
Upgrade...
Mutilation?
W-What's going on?!
This is bad...
Healing ability?
What's going on...?
What was that just now?!
Who exactly is that human...?
That human...!
Go.
Why...
I should be above everyone else...
I should be consuming everything
and growing, aiming for the pinnacle...
I should be the king...
But now...
Run...
I have to run away quickly...
To survive, I have to run away now!
Get as far away as possible!
Quickly...
Get far away quickly!
ACTIVE SKILL: MUTILATION
Those ants...
...ran away.
Did we win?
Hunter Sung!
Her aura...
We have to be quick.
Let's leave here.
The evacuation helicopter is parked
outside. As long as we get on it...
No.
She can't hold on until then.
Then what should we do?!
Isn't that ineffective on her?
This one hasn't been tried yet.
The Elixir of Life that cured
my mother's Eternal Slumber...
This one...
This is the last resort.
Not covered by the drug?
Is it not working?
It'll be too late to evacuate now.
The potion has no effect.
Shadow Exchange also
needs time to be usable again.
Is there...
Is there no other way?
SOLO LEVELING
EPISODE 24: ARE YOU THE KING OF HUMANS
EPISODE 25: ON TO THE NEXT TARGET
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org