Could you stop the camera?
Excuse me?
Do it right now, or I'll break it.
U-Understood!
Hunter Sung. What do you
intend to do to Byung-gu?
I asked you a question!
We're running out of time.
Please stop talking.
Arise.
The chairman has called for the
execution of plan 9. Are you ready?
Are you insane?!
You wanna send us back to the island
while that monster is still there?!
You'd be singing a different tune
if you'd seen it yourself!
Goto died... like it was nothing.
The new variant is dead.
One of their hunters took it down.
It's... dead?
Do you still insist on staying behind?
A skill that lets you use
the powers of the dead?!
It wasn't just summoning magic?
Byung-gu...
I heard a voice.
It was Hunter Min, asking
me to use his power.
I think I can tell what
he was like in life.
To immediately go and heal Hunter
Cha without even being given the order...
He must've been a
kind, caring person.
I can see why he wouldn't
want this getting out on TV.
The ability to grow stronger and stronger
as he engages in more difficult battles...
What a monstrous ability.
But with Min...
Hunter Sung.
If you intend to continue
battling as a hunter,
I'm sure Byung-gu's power
will be of great use to you.
But... He always hated fighting.
I would rather he not have
to return to the battlefield.
This takes me back
to the red gate incident.
You grabbed my
shoulder then, too.
But this time, instead of giving an
order, you're making an earnest plea.
Don't worry. I was
thinking the same thing.
Release extraction.
Thank you so much.
How are they alive?
After a rendezvous with Hunter Sung,
he proceeded to defeat the new variant.
I can see that, you fool!
How is he on the island?!
I thought he wasn't
participating in the raid!
There's no way to tell.
From the magic power readings, all we
can say is he appeared out of nowhere.
This is a nightmare. And after we
lost seven of our ten S-Rank hunters!
Chairman, should we
proceed with plan 9?
Any further casualties will undercut
our ability to respond to domestic gates,
to say nothing about the
global balance of power.
What's your call?
We're pulling out.
Withdraw immediately.
Understood.
Why have the ants started
coming at us so suddenly?!
How should we know?! I
thought the queen was dead!
That's probably why!
With their leader gone,
they're running amok!
We can't let them
reach the mainland!
They ain't gettin' past us!
Time to show these bugs
what the Knights Guild can do!
You got it, Master!
Hurry, everyone!
Well, this is a real shitshow.
It seems like the ants trying to
flee the island are spreading out
and heading toward the mainland.
We have to hurry before
they cut off our route back!
We should take
off at once. Let's go.
What about Hunter Sung?
He's staying behind to take care
of the remaining ants and eggs.
I hate to admit it, but in our
condition, we'd only slow him down.
And though she's no
longer in mortal danger,
it'd be better to have the medic team
examine Hunter Cha as soon as possible.
Getting experience from smashing
unhatched eggs is a nice surprise.
I almost feel bad for not
using this thing more often.
The Demon Monarch's Sword
sure does live up to its name.
That said... I'll leave
the rest to you guys.
I've finally hit level 100.
He's still emitting a ton
of aura, even after dying.
Arise.
What is this darkness?
I can't sense anything.
Did something happen
during the extraction?
I'm back.
For a second there,
I thought it had failed.
Well, on to the other ants...
My king.
Did you just talk?
Yes.
None of the other shadows
could talk... So why can he?
My king, I ask that
you grant me a name.
"General" rank?
Never seen that before.
Is the new rank why he can talk?
And I've gotta wonder...
I was the one who killed you.
Are you still willing to obey me?
I did not die.
By your hand, I was reborn.
I am filled with joy.
I swear to serve
you for eternity.
Please grant me a name.
Beru.
Your name is Beru.
I am honored.
Now, back to business.
Arise.
They got past
the hunters at sea!
We're the last line of defense!
We cannot let them reach the cities!
Oh, no, no, no!
How the hell do we
fight these things?!
Tanks, get in front!
We hold the line,
or we die trying!
That's a lot of ants.
Four thousand without a leader. They
appear to be fleeing in all directions.
There were still that many?!
Can you thin out
the numbers for me?
If that is your wish,
my king, then certainly.
You need only say the word.
Go.
Good! Keep it up.
These things are dangerous, so be
careful and take one down at a time!
Work together, and make sure—
Mr. Song!
Are you okay, Mr. Song?!
What just happened?!
What was that light?
I don't know. But
I think it saved us.
Jinwoo...
There's just too damn many!
Can't you do something?
Not without wrecking
the helicopter, no!
I hate this.
There's not a lot
we can do in midair.
In the end, he
saved us once again.
They should be able
to make it back now.
Afterward, the majority of the ants
that had dispersed from the island
were held off by the
many hunters in the field,
minimizing the
damage to the mainland.
Our country's S-Rank
hunters returned safely.
Hunter Cha, who remained
unconscious, was transported to a hospital.
It was a battle with
many casualties,
but the emergent threat from the
island was successfully dealt with.
And so, the fourth Jeju
Island raid ended in our victory.
Looks like we've got more
visitors from far abroad.
It's been two days of this now.
They'll be within
firing range shortly.
Notify the mage-type
hunters on standby.
Prepare to intercept.
No, belay that order.
Our country's hero seems
to want a bit of exercise.
Here they come.
Can't just sit around
all day, after all.
Let's send every last one
of them to a watery grave.
If I'd gotten a crack at the
black ant instead of these peons,
I might've actually
had some fun.
What a shame.
It's now been several
days since the raid ended.
A memorial has been
erected to honor the victims,
and a large crowd has
come to pay their respects.
Here we have the S-Rank hunter,
Sung Jinwoo, approaching the table.
He contributed a
great deal to this raid,
with some saying that it would not have
been a success without his participation.
Some are calling him a hero...
But at the same time, many
are questioning whether or not
there would have been fewer casualties
had he participated from the start,
to sum up some of
the more critical voices.
Please hold your head high.
No matter what the public thinks, you're
the one who put an end to this tragedy.
As chairman of the Hunter's
Association, I'd like to first thank you
for your service during
the fourth Jeju Island raid.
No... If I had got there sooner,
maybe Hunter Min could have survived.
But thanks to you, the other five S-Ranks and
many of our countrymen's lives were saved.
That is a major accomplishment.
I promise that you will be rewarded
however you wish in due time.
I understand.
Now, I was wondering what
your plans are for the future.
The future, sir?
Right.
This raid resulted in your power being
demonstrated on an international level.
I doubt the public
will leave you alone.
There will be many who will
try to approach you, as well.
The Association
can't ignore that.
Which is why I feel the need
to ask you, Hunter Sung...
What do you intend to do with
your great power, and where?
I'm thinking about
starting my own guild.
How the hell didya end
up stuck on cleanup duty
instead of attendin' the
memorial service, Master?!
Hey, dumbass. Makin' sure the
enemies're dead, killin' stragglers,
and collectin' resources
is all important stuff.
Bein' entrusted with the last
bits of a job is a sign they trust me.
But...
And besides...
A real man does the job he's given,
nice and steady, without no bitchin'.
You're so awesome, Master!
Who the hell're you?!
This place is off-limits!
What are you doing—
What was that?!
I dunno who you are,
but yer not supposed—
What did you do?
All the noise they were
making was bothering me.
I just had them
take a little nap.
So, were you able to make sure?
Yeah. It was
definitely his power.
So very strange. Someone
like that, helping humans...
He's always been an odd one.
If you're that curious,
go and see him.
If the opportunity
presents itself.
I think we're done here.
Let's head back.
Isn't one of them here?
We can leave this area to him.
In other words, you
don't want to get involved.
The hunt will commence as
planned. That hasn't changed.
I guess it's not worth
the extra trouble.
Quite the stench, though. I can only imagine
the fuss she'd make if she were here.
I'm not getting anywhere.
So, about the guild...
Oh, Chairman Go
just gave his approval.
Seriously?! Then I'll get
right on finding us an office!
Hey!
Wait—
Jinwoo! Make sure
you hire me, okay?!
I promise I'll be useful!
Come on, we're discussing
some very important—
I'm hanging up.
Like what, exactly?
Those two...
Man, I am seriously
not getting anywhere.
Hello?
Hunter Sung. This is Go.
Did something
happen with the guild?
No, I'm calling
about something else.
Further down this highway?
Correct. A B-Rank
gate has appeared.
That explains it.
Hunters are being arranged for,
but it's going to take some
time before they can get there.
Well, if you don't mind...
One vehicle at a time, please!
How much longer before
the hunters get here?
You mean the traffic's so
bad the hunters can't make it?!
What are we supposed to do?
Hey, don't hang up!
I'm here to close the gate.
Oh, right!
Manager Woo informed me.
But it's going to be a while before
the other hunters are able to make it—
I'll be fine solo.
But...
There he goes.
I mean, I know it's only
a B-Rank gate, but...
Don't tell me...
Well, this is
obviously a red gate.
How does this keep
happening to me?
The exit's closed, and I have no
idea how far this forest extends...
Now I'm thinking I should've
told Mom I was gonna be late.
Then again, if this is all that's in
here, it shouldn't take that long.
Let's make this quick.
He came to the
memorial ceremony.
This raid proved that I
still have a lot to learn.
I wasn't able to do
anything. I had to be saved.
But not him.
I want to catch up to him.
I want to stand at his side.
And to do that...
I need to get stronger.
Hunters are born to hunt.
Dungeons are worlds where
survival is all that matters,
and a hunter has to be prepared
to become prey at any time.
That's because there's no telling
when the roles might be reversed.
You're always one
step away from death.
But hunters are
still willing to fight,
no matter how many
enemies they face,
or how much stronger
those enemies might be.
They've all got different
reasons for fighting.
To protect their family.
To uphold their ideals.
To prove who they are.
To defy fate.
So hunters continue to hunt.
And none of them are ready to stop.
On to the next target.