Arise.
Very good.
(Solo Leveling Season 2
-Arise from the Shadow-)
How long has it been?
About three hours or so.
It's been about three days inside.
The environment inside is harsh.
Alas.
I guess
Sung Jinwoo must have died.
I made a wasted trip.
No,
wait.
Sung Jinwoo isn't from
the White Tiger Guild.
Then why did he go through the gate
with your assault team?
He is my friend.
He was interested in a Level-C quest.
That's why I brought him along.
Alright.
I see.
Did you think I would say that?
What are you up to?
I know you love new things.
Hwang Dongsoo.
Let go.
Are you ordering me?
As a guild master from a small country?
What did you say?
This is bad.
If we don't stop them,
a fight between S-Rank hunters
will happen.
So, you want a fight?
It's because it's too cold.
No.
As long as I have gear,
I won't lose at all.
No wonder I didn't see any Ice Bears.
Did the E-Rank hunters
kill them all?
Impossible.
They couldn't possibly do it.
I got it.
It's the White Demon.
The White Demon is here.
Darn it.
Pretty impressive.
If you hadn't held back your strength,
my arm might have been broken already.
I don't know what you are suspecting.
But about two months ago,
I tested Mr. Sung's magic power again.
He is indeed an E-Rank hunter.
That's the investigation result.
And magic beasts killed Hwang Dongsuk.
That's your word on that.
What an obvious lie.
I guess Mr. Yoo actually murdered him.
Why did you go after Sung Jinwoo?
Well, of course,
it was just an excuse.
An excuse to kill.
He is a lucky guy.
Mr. Hwang.
I know Mr. Sung's strength well.
He will definitely come out alive.
I lost all my money for weapons.
No, I mean it.
It's a big gap.
Weak people,
how are you still alive?
You even have warm clothes, blankets,
tents, and food.
I get it.
So that's what it was.
You bad guys.
Mr. Kim?
The assault team has been annihilated
because we lack food and gear.
That is…
Who hid these things?
Who hogged all the gear
and got other teammates killed?
I figure it out now.
Heejin.
You knew it, didn't you?
That's why you joined this team.
Confess, or you'll be accomplices.
I'll count to three. Confess honestly.
One.
-Two.
-The culprit is that guy.
Sung Jinwoo.
Three.
You got your teammates killed.
Sung.
Captain.
You even brought us trouble.
Show up.
You can't hide your strong presence.
They are Ice Demons.
We're outnumbered.
Is he the boss?
Among the trash,
there is someone useful.
What did you say?
Are you saying we're all trash?
Oh, that's really surprising.
Kid, can you understand our language?
Huh?
Why can I understand it?
Can you understand their language?
Is this because of the system?
If so, that would be perfect.
This guy told me
there's an expert among humans.
He wanted to compete with you.
And then?
Interesting.
It seems I can't beat him quickly.
It's getting more interesting.
That being said,
you're clearly not human.
Why are you mingling among humans?
What?
You don't even know who you are.
We keep hearing a voice.
It tells us to kill humans.
But when facing you, I can't hear it.
Hear a voice?
Is it something similar
to system commands?
He can't hear anything when facing me.
Is it because I've become a player?
There is no need for us to fight.
Let's have the best of both worlds.
Hand over the humans behind you,
and we will spare your life.
What do you think?
How do you find this proposal?
Who are you?
Why do you fight humans?
We are…
Hand over the humans behind you,
and we will spare your life.
What just happened?
What do you think?
How do you find this proposal?
You're going to accept it, right?
I refuse.
Are you planning to be our enemy?
For the record, you're outnumbered.
I beg your pardon?
What is this?
They're monsters.
Monsters have appeared.
Black soldiers and black Ice Bears.
What?
Mr. Sung, did you summon them?
It's no use making a death struggle.
A death struggle?
Is it really so?
Get away.
It's not a battle we can be in.
He truly has the capacity to boast.
Soldiers can't be killed,
but they need MP.
I'm running out of the MP.
Anyway, their boss
looks stronger than me.
I can't even defeat him with Igris.
Regular soldiers can't end this fight.
I need stronger combat power.
My name is Baruka.
What's your name?
Sung Jinwoo.
I love this exciting battle.
The last voice I heard…
Sung Jinwoo.
Luckily, the soldiers bought me time.
Next up is…
Is this all your soldiers can do?
Sung Jinwoo.
Just die!
Even a human has betrayed you.
Utterly boring.
What a cheap trick.
Sung Jinwoo.
Just die!
Kim Chul.
I knew it.
Utterly boring.
Sung Jinwoo.
You guy.
From the very beginning,
did you anticipate that I would come?
Darn it.
Arise.
What a cheap trick.
Iron.
From today on,
you will be called Iron.
Quite interesting.
I'll start by getting rid of you.
You are moving way too slowly.
Heejin.
This is
how hunters fight?
If that's the case,
how could I possibly become a hunter?
I have never seen this before.
We're not dreaming, right?
This guy can't fight me.
You and that knight,
come at me together.
Is that so?
First of all,
take you down.
He actually avoided the vital areas.
You are underestimating me too much.
You are indeed very strong.
However,
your men are not.
But
if you die, those guys won't be an issue.
You idiot, you threw away your weapon.
Iron.
Pretty good.
I'm going to kill all of you.
The outcome has been decided.
Are you kidding me?
It's not over yet.
I told you.
The outcome has already been decided.
Have I finally defeated him?
Hey.
Stop.
Don't go too far.
I'm worried about your future.
It's over, isn't it?
Yes.
Let's go.
To the outside of the gate.
Great.
We can go home now.
We can finally get out.
What a day.
We can go back now.
Before that,
it's been almost a week inside.
We will stay here on standby.
Mr. Baek, you go back.
My members are trapped inside.
I can't just go back.
I'll wait here until dawn.
There's a shadow.
Someone is coming out.
Mr. Kim.
I knew you could do it.
Mr. Baek.
Miss Park.
Mr. Go.
It's good that you're alright.
How are the other hunters?
Mr. Sung.
I knew it.
The gate has disappeared.
What about the other hunters?
Where is Mr. Kim?
So,
only low-rank hunters survived?
What exactly happened inside?
Go back.
I'll take you home.
Okay.
Please wait.
May I have a word with you?
I'm already tired.
Whatever it is, ask the guild.
This is not a request.
It's an order, even a threat.
In this incident,
six members of our guild went missing.
I'm in charge and must ask you something.
That makes sense.
But I saved two members of yours.
As the person in charge,
shouldn't you thank me first?
Please forgive my rudeness.
You are right.
I am truly sorry.
Miss Park.
Yes?
What's wrong with that guy?
Why did he seem so mad?
I don't know either.
After defeating the boss,
he got in a bad mood.
I think he must feel quite exhausted.
He is not a bad person.
Mr. Ahn.
Make sure to bring him to our guild.
Yes.
Indeed, I did not misjudge.
Thank you.
Please be careful on your way back.
Hmm.
Well, Jinwoo.
Jinwoo?
Thank you for today.
See you tomo…
No.
See you later.
Yeah.
Not even a day has passed outside yet.
Only this stuff looks good.
Because there's a big gap
between him and me?
Three attempts failed.
NUMBER OF EXTRACTION POSSIBLE: 0/3
YOU HAVE NO ATTEMPTS REMAINING
I worked all day for nothing.
No…
Well…
It's the third time already.
Brother.
I'm going to eat your breakfast.
I'm coming out.
Good morning.
You came over in this costume?
Yes.
Alright, let's head out.
Whatever.
We'll pick someone up on the way.
Eh?
Good morning, Captain.
Ah… Yeah.
Good morning.
Sorry for the trouble.
Jinwoo.
Jinwoo?
Did you get some sleep afterward?
I couldn't sleep at all.
Right, it was morning
by the time you got home.
-Yeah.
-Got home?
Didn't sleep at all?
How about you, Jinwoo?
You two spent the night together?
-You take a nap. I'll wake you when we arrive.
-Um…
-Thank you.
-Boss?
Hmm?
Miss Han
is underage.
So?
Nothing…
Let's set off and get it done soon.
Yes, Jinwoo.
Yes.
(Solo Leveling)
(Episode 14: I Suppose You aren't Aware)
(Episode 15: Still a Long Way to Go)