(Solo Leveling Season 2
-Arise from the Shadow-)
What are you doing there?
I'll ask one more time.
How careless…
What was I thinking?
I got lost and ended up here.
Got lost?
Are you from the mining team?
This is the BOSS room.
Please step back.
Cha Hae-In.
She truly lives up to her reputation.
I didn't notice her at all
until she spoke.
Did I see it wrong?
Wasn't he just holding a weapon?
I am sorry.
Please hurry out.
If you agitate the boss,
the mining team may get annihilated.
I understand.
Umm, hold on.
Yes.
He isn't smelly.
What are you doing?
Are you really a hunter?
Uh, yes…
E-rank…
Sung Jinwoo.
It's nothing.
This dungeon is very large.
Be careful on your way back.
Okay.
Is it because his rank is too low?
He's not smelly at all.
On the contrary,
he smells rather pleasant.
I heard you met Hunter Cha
when you were lost.
You are so lucky.
We can only admire her from a distance.
She patrols to protect us from the boss,
sacrificing her own rest time.
She is a very reliable young woman.
That's why she came to the BOSS room.
Hunter Cha feels uncomfortable
with the scent of other hunters.
The scent of hunters?
I heard it's due to
her unique constitution.
She always covers her nose
with a handkerchief.
Right.
But her reaction to me…
I don't have
the distinct scent of a hunter.
In the red gate, that guy
said something similar.
Is it because I am a player?
The only one favored by the system.
What exactly is the so-called player?
Thank you for your work.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, we finished work early.
Never thought we'd finish earlier
than the recovery team.
You have talent for this.
I thought you secretly used the excavator.
You flatter me.
I've been in this line of work
for a long time.
But I've never come across
a talent like you, Sung.
Sung.
Are you interested in working for me?
You'll be rewarded fairly.
Well…
I'm glad to hear you say so.
But this is a one-time thing for me…
I see.
That's a pity.
But could you help for one more day?
One more day?
Yes.
Tomorrow, there are back-to-back
A-rank and C-rank raid missions.
The evaluation will be conducted
the day after tomorrow.
Today, I've gotten a grip
on the raid process.
Wait.
Tomorrow?
Hunters Guild also have
raid missions tomorrow?
A-rank and C-rank missions simultaneously?
Yes.
But the 2nd assault team
will be coming tomorrow.
The 2nd assault team…
That is our strength.
We can raid A-rank gates
with two groups of people.
No one else in the country can do it.
Then, where should I report tomorrow?
So you are willing to help?
I will talk to the boss about
doubling your salary tomorrow.
Eh… you don't have to…
Come on, that's the least I could do.
Could you help inquire about
Sung Jinwoo in the mining team?
Do you mean Hunter Sung?
Do you know him?
Mr. Choi said the same to me yesterday.
Mr. Choi?
Yes.
But all the information
about him has been sealed.
Eh?
He's not a top-tier hunter,
yet his information was blocked
by the association. That's new to me too.
I see.
His behavior in the dungeon.
Mr. Choi ordered an investigation.
The association blocked the information.
There must be something behind it.
I've met so many hunters.
But this is my first time
meeting someone with a nice scent.
Oh, he's here.
Sung.
Good morning.
Sung, have you been eating well?
Hi, Sung.
Jinwoo, please don't get hurt today.
I haven't felt this way in a long time..
Let's eat together today.
Yeah, you came after all.
Okay.
Alright, let's start with C-rank dungeon.
The assault team is about to come out.
Everyone needs to get ready.
He's again doing a great job.
Mm-hmm.
With Sung, the progress is much faster.
Thanks to you, we can rest and
go into the A-rank dungeon after lunch.
The recovery team is also amazed.
Do you really not want to work with us?
I'll give you five times the salary.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Captain Son Kihoon.
Can I borrow someone
from your mining team?
The person in charge of
carrying luggage couldn't come.
From us?
The recovery team should
be better at moving stuff.
They said they are also short-staffed.
Hmm…
If you go in with the assault team,
you will receive the risk allowance.
Portering in an A-rank dungeon
is not fit for low-rank hunters.
Offering more money wouldn't change that.
No one wants to go?
I'll go.
Uh… Sung!
This is too reckless.
There are high-rank magic beasts inside.
That money isn't worth
risking your life for.
It's alright.
Actually, I'm quite bold.
It's not about being bold.
He just joined the team yesterday,
so he doesn't understand anything.
His rank?
E-rank.
So please find someone else.
No, he'll do it.
Eh…
I am the leader
of this attack team, Son Kihoon.
I am Sung Jinwoo.
It's even bigger than that of yesterday.
But the magic power is not
as strong as that of the gate yesterday.
Be assured.
If it's too dangerous,
they wouldn't send us, the second team.
Six A-rank and three B-rank hunters.
Although there are no S-rank hunters,
they wouldn't be a second team
in other guilds.
Let's set off.
Hunters Guild
has two assault teams of this level.
The magic power inside
is less than that of yesterday.
But for some reason,
I have a sort of ominous premonition
similar to confronting the red gate.
I must be overthinking.
Don't be nervous.
Kihoon…
Ah.
All the hunters here
led by the captain are very strong.
If you stick with us,
you won't be attacked by magic beasts.
Thank you.
After this raid mission is completed,
I will be officially
appointed as the captain.
Although I'm not as good as
Captain and Vice-captain,
I'm nonetheless an A-rank hunter.
I can do it.
They got ready without any instructions.
It's coming.
It's Dungeon Jackals.
Get down.
Why are Dungeon Jackals
in an A-rank dungeon?
Are they rare magic beasts?
Because they are C-rank magic beasts.
It wouldn't be surprising
if they all died in the dungeon.
Collar?
Please look here.
It seems they were being raised.
They were spared and used as hunting dogs?
It seems my premonition was correct.
High Orcs.
How could it be?
Their power is astonishing.
He-ah!
The taunting skill is ineffective.
They've targeted the back-line!
Watch out!
We won't be taken down that easily.
That strike was ineffective.
Their magic resistance is too strong.
It's too strong.
I can only hold it back for a few seconds.
I'll summon help now.
Those who obey my command,
take the enemy's head.
This is my trump card
that consumes a lot of MP.
How about it?
Healer!
We need you here.
Wait, I'll be right there.
We are outnumbered!
If we're surrounded, we will be done for.
Move in groups of three.
Or we'll be dispersed.
There are so many High Orcs
that can rival A-rank hunters alone.
B-rank members cannot
handle these magic beasts.
Please, let everyone survive.
Next one.
Don't move.
I'll heal you right away.
What just happened?
What happened?
These High Orcs suddenly…
Now!
Attack back!
As an outsider, I really don't
want to stand out here.
But I cannot watch people die.
I must weaken them without being noticed.
Don't play any tricks.
Is anyone seriously injured?
It seems okay.
Everyone's alive. It's a miracle.
Hey.
Something weird happened
during the battle.
I also felt that they
suddenly slowed down.
Gina, was it you who did it?
I couldn't do that.
I only know attack magic and
a little bit of telekinesis magic.
And the other members
mainly focus on firepower, right?
Without assassin-type hunters,
that shouldn't be possible.
But, no matter what,
we just won.
Right.
We're really lucky.
That porter
underestimated our assault team.
With a magic caster on the team,
how could he think that
his stealth skill wouldn't be detected?
However,
it's true that we survived because of him.
It seems he has his reasons.
I'll let him off this time.
Captain Son,
do we keep going in?
This place is too dangerous for us.
We need at least two more healers
and three more mages.
I understand how you feel to encounter this
on your first time as the captain.
But,
I also think we should retreat first.
I can understand
he doesn't want to give up.
Everyone wants to conquer the dungeon.
But,
if he is a wise leader…
Then,
let's retreat for now.
I was afraid you would
wanted us to keep going.
I'm not that foolish.
This is…
A barrier.
And a high-level one.
It wasn't here when we entered.
Is there a way to lift it?
Given some time, I can do it.
There's an entity capable of
using such high-level magic in this dungeon.
Fortunately, we chose to turn back.
We can't conquer this place by ourselves.
What's this magic power?
No way.
The dungeon boss?
We need to lift it, help me.
Understood.
Okay.
Even a B-rank hunter can feel
such a powerful magical fluctuation.
Why wasn't it detected outside the gate?
Curse magic, is it a trap?
Semi, cast divine magic.
What's wrong? What are you doing?
Captain Son.
There are roughly fifty of them.
-Kihoon.
-Don't move.
We'll die pointlessly
if we fight them here.
Helelakkohina.
Vitualanaka.
Humans.
My name is Kargalgan.
I wish to see you humans.
Kargalgan.
Did you block the entrance?
Yes.
I am the great sorcerer
of the glorious orc tribe.
Is there a stronger being
than you in the cave?
Who do you think can surpass me?
Choose.
Either die at the hands of my soldiers,
or come to see me.
We will come to see you.
Hunter Sung.
Yes.
As soon as we see the boss,
we will attack immediately.
No matter what, it should be distracted
and cannot maintain the barrier.
You take the opportunity to escape
and find the main assault team.
Are you trying to get killed?
Our mission is not to
return alive from the dungeon,
but to close the gate.
I also have a favor to ask of you.
This is my short will.
Please pass it on to my family.
We must complete our mission.
But you are different.
Please make sure you leave here alive.
This desperate situation
is just like ours in the double dungeon.
Those people back then…
But these people…
I'll take it for now.
But I hope things don't turn out that way.
He isn't here.
Did he resign from the mining team?
Hunter Cha.
Why did you come?
Isn't today your day off?
May I ask
if Hunter Sung Jinwoo was here?
Ah, Sung.
He just went in as a porter.
Eh?
You mean he's inside the gate now?
Humans.
Welcome.
(Solo Leveling)
(Episode 17: This is What We're Trained to Do)
(Episode 18: Don't Look Down on My Guys)