Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
A coup at the Land of Green...?
Yes, it seems there's no mistake.
The retainers conspired with
some men
and began a rebellion...
What happened to Naruto
and the others?
Speculating from their gathering point,
they are around here.
So they've already
crossed the border...
The large countries have agreed
to make this
a demilitarized zone.
Considering Naruto and
the other's mission,
they should be in a safe area...
Are you sure?
What do you mean...?
Don't you think the timing
of this request
strangely overlaps with the coup?
Then you're saying that Naruto's mission
is also related to this case?
There is a possibility...
But there's no time to deal
with Naruto at the moment.
We have to take back
the Land of Green
from the rebels as soon as possible.
If we leave it like this,
the flames of the war will eventually
reach other countries...
True...
Shizune, gather the free villagers
and have them head to
the Land of Green immediately!
Yes, ma'am!
You've done it now!
What a persistent brat...!
You shouldn't be able
to stand anymore...
Naruto!
This is... nothing.
What a surprise...
you got some guts.
Then, take this too!
Ninja Art Magnet!
Electromagnetic Illusion.
Naruto!
It's useless!
Your voice wouldn't reach him!
The human brain functions by
a faint electric current
running through it...
If you receive
my magnetic force powder,
it's going to alter your electric
current and stop your thinking...
That chain also has
a strong magnetic force.
Now, get buried!
Naruto!
Are you okay?
Thank goodness...
Hinata... run!
I can't leave you behind...
He is...
He's someone that
you can't deal with...
Naruto... I promise I'll save you!
Hinata!
I'll have you tell me
where that girl is!
Byakugan!
Take this!
Electromagnetic Illusion!
Protective 8 Trigrams 64 Palms!
What?!
I see, so that is the Byakugan
of the Village Hidden in Leaves...
How interesting!
What wonderful Taijutsu, but...
I'll crush it
with my power!
I did it...?!
Yeah right...
That level of Taijutsu will not work!
It's useless!
This is bad...!
You're not much of a challenge.
I'm disappointed!
Now tell me!
Where did you hide that girl?
If you answer me, I'll let you live...
That boy too!
If you rescue him right now,
he wouldn't die.
Run... Hinata...
Now say it!
You don't want to save
that boy?
Or do you think you could win
against me?
If I say it...
Naruto would never forgive me.
Then I'll force you to talk!
I'll change the area behind you
into a powerful magnet.
I can change the position of the magnet
according to your movement.
So it's a waste to run away!
That brat...
She evaded the attack by throwing
a paper bomb at that very instant.
She's pretty quick witted.
But...
I won't let you go!
Hinata...
Naruto... I promise that
I'll return to rescue you...!
But, there is a huge difference
in power between him and me...
I could never win against him!
He's already caught up to me...
What should I do?
This is...iron sand... ?
I see...his Jutsu can
change his body
and the things he touches
into magnet.
The reason why he didn't attack
back there
was to brush off the iron sand
from his body...
If he doesn't,
he would sink in his iron sand.
His attack pattern consists of
alternating between
Ninja Art Magnet
and Iron Sand Genjutsu...
He does this to turn
his magnet powers on and off
so his body won't
completely turn into a magnet.
Then, there is one way
to beat him!
Now... play time is almost over!
Now, it's time you give up!
I would never give up!
Because that is my Ninja Way!
What a waste...
How dare you do that to Naruto!
I will definitely not forgive you!
Once you say where
that girl is,
why don't you live with
that brat in hell!
Hey, don't be shy
and come closer!
Right now!
I'll risk everything
in this single attack!
An attack that didn't work before,
will never work!
Is... that right?
What?!
We're both going to hell!
Let go, you!
You brat! How dare you play
around with me!
I changed my mind.
I'll finish you off now!
What is this?!
Just now...
I struck a Chakra Point
that would make your Chakra flow
go out of control.
Now your body will just turn
into a strong magnet...
What? That's why you brought me
to this sandy area?!
S Stop!
I did it... Naruto...
Damn...! I can't move!
The Human Boulder!
Naruto!
Choji...!
Are you okay, Naruto...?
Thanks... Yurinojou.
So what happened?
The second Janin attacked me
and I got beaten up.
What happened to Hinata
and the princess?
Oh yeah...!
I can't stay here!
What...?
What's going on...? Naruto?
Hinata is in danger!
- Oh! Naruto!
- Naruto!
Hinata!
Are you okay... Hinata?
Hang in there, Hinata!
N -Naruto... Choji...
Yurinojou...
You guys...
you guys came to rescue me...
Of course...
We're friends, right?!
Yes!
By the way, that magnet guy...
Where did he go?
He probably sunk into the sand...
What?! You did it, Hinata?
Yeah... I did my best...
Hinata, you're great...
The guy that I couldn't handle...
You're complimenting me?
Naruto...
Here...
This is... my forehead band?
The mission is not over yet.
Naruto, please protect the princess...
Princess Haruna.
Hinata...
I'll promise you!
I swear on this forehead band
I will definitely protect the Princess!
And...
I can't be losing against you!
Naruto...
Look after Hinata, Choji... Yurinojou!
Right!
Leave it to us... Naruto!
Well, I'll be darned.
I can't believe that Ruiga
and Jiga were both defeated.
Well, that saves some
trouble though...
Nobody has ever escaped
from my Jutsu.
Today will be a good day.
Haruna! Where are you?!
There she is!
Haruna! Get a hold of yourself!
Are you okay?
I'm glad...
I It's me, Princess Haruna!
N -Naruto...
I came to rescue you,
but what is this treatment?
Sorry...
Why did you escape by yourself?
I can't count on you guys...
I will try to survive
no matter who's sacrificed...
As long as I survive,
the Land of Green can be revived.
That's the most important thing, right?!
I am a victim!
If I declare that other countries
will lend me their power.
If I take back the country and
I, the true successor,
become the feudal lord,
then people will definitely gather and
the Land of Green will return
to the way it was!
I don't think so.
You're saying that
the Land of Green won't revive?
I'm not saying that...
But I just thought what if I lived
in the Land of Green...
If I was a Ninja just like Yurinojou...
I won't guard a feudal lord like you!
Naruto!
What do you know?!
What do you know about me?!
What do you know about my life
as a hostage?!
Under watch 24/7,
not even allowed to have
my own free time,
I was Ionely everyday.
Because of that lifestyle,
I became sick and was
in bed for a long time.
I was finally able to return home
after being close to dying...
Naruto! If you're saying that
I'm wrong, then answer me!
Were the things done to me
in the name of protecting
the Land of Green all wrong
Then why did my father and mother
send me away as a hostage?!
Answer me! Naruto!
I won't count on you.
I will go by myself.
Wait.
I will go too.
I promised Hinata that I will
definitely protect you, princess!
With Hinata...?
She fought with
the second Janin
and got hurt badly...
Hinata did?
You guys said that you didn't accept
the mission of protecting me.
Then, why do you concern yourselves
with me?
I...
Not only me,
but Hinata and Choji, too.
We don't like it when somebody before us
is hurt or sad... That's all.
Well, let's go!
If we pass through the valley
ahead of us,
we'll get to the town.
If we do that, they probably won't
chase us all the way there!
Please be careful...
No one uses this deer path.
This should shake them...
I found you!
It's impossible...
to run away from me!
Choji?!
Don't make useless efforts...
I'll make you guys my hostages!
You guys take them back to the castle!
Yes!
If you wander around me
you might get caught
in my Jutsu and die.
That's it...
We're almost there!
There's no time to waste!
Let's go!
Okay!
Haruna!
I'm okay!
Oh no!
Wh What is this?!
I see... You have good sense
to dodge that attack!
Who is it?!
Where are you?!
Here, over here!
Too bad, but you guys won't
be able to reach that village.
Since you guys are going
to die here!
Yesterday's Call Sign,
was all from my cell phone.
In a strange park,
I play the Fuzz Guitar without enthusiasm.
Yellow Moon.
Even now, counting to three,
I open my eyes
Shadow Moon I am still dreaming.
Look at my eyes, look at my eyes,
as we face one another's back
Look at my eyes, when can we meet?
EveryDay EveryNight
With every word I can think of
Right away, my messy feelings as is,
A magical chord change, in a restless city
A daily JAZZ Guitar played
in a soft minor key
Damn! He is so troublesome!
How dare he use many
showy attacks.
There is no way I can retaliate!
I've gotta do something.
At this rate, I'm gonna get cornered
and shot.
But even if I wanted to hide,
Haruna's legs are...
Oh, damn it!
What in the world should I do?!
Next time: " Forecast: Death!
Cloudy with Chance of Sun!"