Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
I won't count on you.
I will go by myself.
Wait.
I'll go too.
I promised Hinata that I would definitely
protect you, Princess!
With Hinata...?
She fought with the second Janin
and got hurt badly...
Hinata did?
You guys said that you didn't accept
the mission of protecting me.
Then why do you concern
yourselves with me...?
I...
Not only me,
but Hinata and Choji, too.
We don't like it when somebody before us
is hurt or sad... That's all.
Well, let's go!
If we pass through
the valley ahead of us,
we'll get to the town.
If we do that,
they probably won't chase us
all the way there!
Forecast: Death!
Cloudy with Chance of Sun!
Too bad, but you guys won't
be able to reach that village.
Since you guys are going
to die here!
Wh Why is he floating in the air?
Hey kid, I bet a low class Ninja like you
can't even imagine my Jutsu.
Take this!
Naruto!
I'm okay.
But what just flew at me?
Don't waste your time fighting me.
I have already captured
all three of your friends.
What?
Just hand over the girl.
If you do that I'll spare your friends.
Choji and Hinata...
So, what are you going to do kid?
Naruto... Are you going to
abandon me too?
Oh no, this princess is
telling you to save her,
and let your friends die.
Well, I don't mind that kind of thinking
since it's the same as mine.
Same as yours?
That's right.
If someone is useful,
then you should make use
of them
even though they may be
your siblings.
There is one thing I need
to thank you guys for.
Thank us?
For what?!
For doing in Ruiga and Jiga.
I was going to put an end to them myself
sooner or later anyways.
What...?!
It was clear that they would
soon tell me,
"Big Brother, give us the property
and the money too.
Three feudal lords are not necessary
in one country.
And you still call
yourselves brothers?!
It doesn't matter.
Even though it's my parents
or my brothers.
I'll make use of anything I can.
Now, give her to me.
I refuse.
I see.
Naruto...
A person who would abandon
his siblings
would never keep his promise
with me.
Well, that's true.
It's impossible, Naruto!
You don't even know
what kind of Jutsu it is!
That doesn't matter!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Take this!
What is this guy?
There's something hard around
his body that I can't see...
Naruto!
I'm sorry, but none of
your Ninjutsu work on me.
Not even one.
Damn it!
What?!
What is that?
Crystallized ice...?
I can gather water vapor in the air
and instantly turn it
into crystallized ice.
So the things that just attacked me
were ice Shuriken.
Man! It's hard to see
if it's transparent ice.
Just that is not too interesting.
What is this great sense
of danger?
I'm sure his Jutsu has already started!
Where is it, where is it
coming from?!
Kid, do you know
today's weather forecast?
Weather forecast?
Cloudy and partly sunny.
It's a good weather for you to die.
What is this?
What?!
Look out!
Damn it!
Naruto!
That's a lens!
Lens?!
Yup, I turned the crystallized ice
into lens
to gather the sunlight and shoot it.
So, I can't really control it,
but it'll be an instant when you die.
As soon as the battle condition
at the Land of Green is prepared,
I'll burn up the surrounding countries
with this Jutsu.
This way!
It's no use.
I could even see things that are
a thousand miles away.
I found you.
Naruto... Why do you protect me?
I wonder why...
I don't know either.
Naruto...
Haruna!
While I distract him, run!
Don't even think you guys
could get away from my Jutsu
by doing that!
You decided to hand me
over the princess?
Who would hand over Haruna
to the likes of you!
What a fool.
I'm telling you that if you hand me
the selfish princess
and just go back to the village,
I'll let your friends go.
I promised with Hinata that
I will save Haruna!
Just to keep a promise
with your friend,
you're gonna risk your life to fight
in a hopeless battle, huh...?
You're just like the feudal lord
in Land of Green.
A good natured big fool!
Same as my father...?!
You're just like the feudal lord
in Land of Green.
A good natured big fool!
Same as my father...?!
This is what the feudal lord
foolishly said
to us who were trying to take over
the Land of Green:
"Please do not torment the people
in this country."
I beg you!
I don't care what happens to me,
but please promise me one thing!
This is a small weak country
surrounded by big countries.
Without the powers of the people,
the country cannot prosper!
In order for the country to prosper,
we must take care of
each individual people
and not sacrifice a single life!
I want you to consider the people
as a family
and not torment them.
I am the feudal lord!
It doesn't matter what I do
to the people, right?
That's why...
That's why this country has
been at peace until now!
Peace doesn't matter to me.
All I need to do is use the people
as the stepping stones
and feather my nest!
And because of that kind
of good nature,
his daughter was taken
as a hostage!
What do you mean?!
It seems like it was ten years ago.
A lot of the people were sacrificed
by the pressure of the big country...
Riots occurred in the country
and the country came close to corruption.
It was a bitter decision...
I had no choice but to let
my daughter,
who is more important than my life,
taken as a hostage.
I know that Haruna will
not forgive me...
A cold hearted father who sacrificed
his own daughter
just for the peace of the country.
Why don't you ask
your daughter directly?!
In the after life!
My father was...killed!
What an outrageously
good natured person, huh?
You're wrong,
he was a great feudal lord!
Naruto...
Listen!
There are two kinds of human beings
in this world.
Those who use others,
and those who get used!
In my case, I will get to
the top using anyone,
whether it's my parents or my friends.
You! I'll never forgive you!
Shut up!
D-Damn!
Die!
Naruto...
You can't move anymore?!
You're not the one...
It was because of Haruna's father
that this country was peaceful...
The person who is going
to succeed this country is...
The person is...
Haruna!
Stop!
Stupid!
Why aren't you running away?!
Kill me! If you kill me,
your goal will be fulfilled, right?!
Naruto, Naruto has nothing
to do with this!
So both the parent and daughter
are naïve, after all.
Why not complain to your father
in the afterlife
for making you sacrifice your life
for the country?
How scary...
Y You!
It's time for you to die, kid.
I'm not a kid!
My name is Naruto Uzumaki.
I'm not going to hand over
the Land of Green
to a person like you!
Naruto!
Die!
What?!
No... way...
But kid, it's too late even
though you took me down...
The Land of Green without
a feudal lord will collapse
due to the war between
the large countries over its territory.
It's too bad,
but that's not gonna happen!
Shizune!
It's a pain,
but we came to get you guys!
Shikamaru!
But... I didn't ask you guys
to come get us!
But you look pretty beaten up.
No no, this is...
Naruto!
Choji! Hinata! Yurinojou!
Everyone was safe!
Yeah.
We were rescued by
the people of Leaf Village.
Huh? Oh yeah,
why are you guys here?
We received notice of a coup
in the Land of Green
and Lady Tsunade herself ordered me
to come...
Princess Haruna's father was
very kind to Lady Tsunade and me.
My father...?
Please forgive us, when we arrived,
your father was already...
I see... I've caused
so much trouble for you.
Damn!
The position of the feudal lord
that I finally got a hold of...
But, then the surrounding countries
are not going to stay quiet.
It's okay.
An announcement has been sent out
to the neighboring countries
in the name of the next feudal lord.
Under your name, Princess Haruna.
Then we don't need to worry about
the country getting attacked anymore!
Haruna!
Haruna...
Do it.
You want to take revenge
with your own hands, right?
I'll do the same if I were you.
I am... not like you!
Haruna...
Kikunojou, please forgive me.
Princess Haruna.
Here, Kikunojou could look over
the Land of Green.
I'm sure that Kikunojou
will watch over everyone forever.
Well, Lady Haruna,
we are leaving now.
Thank you, Naruto, Choji,
and Hinata.
Shizune, I'd like to ask a special favor.
What is it, Princess Haruna?
My role is to take over my father's will
to protect the peace of Land of Green.
In order to do that,
I want to borrow some help
from the Leaf Village.
Our help?
Yes.
I want you to lend me Naruto.
Huh?!
Please, Naruto.
Princess Haruna.
I want you to help me
with the revival of the Land of Green.
I... I...
I'm sorry,
but I can't really do that.
I need to go back to my friends.
And I need to do more training
and become much stronger.
There are things that I must do.
It's all for my precious friends!
Then I can't take you away
from them...
Naruto, I'll promise that I will do
my best to keep my father's wishes
and strive for a peaceful country
where no one will be sacrificed.
Yeah!
It's a promise!
Thank you! Naruto!
Good bye! Everybody!
We'll come back someday!
Bye!
See ya!
Yesterday's Call Sign,
was all from my cell phone.
In a strange park,
I play the Fuzz Guitar without enthusiasm.
Yellow Moon.
Even now, counting to three,
I open my eyes
Shadow Moon I am still dreaming.
Look at my eyes, look at my eyes,
as we face one another's back
Look at my eyes, when can we meet?
EveryDay EveryNight
With every word I can think of
Right away, my messy feelings as is,
A magical chord change, in a restless city
A daily JAZZ Guitar played
in a soft minor key
No! He's looking over here!
Of course, he'll look!
Stop complaining and attack him!
No, no, it's impossible!
He just moved right now!
He moved, Naruto!
Of course, he'll move!
Hey, approach him more!
No, no, no. This is my limit.
Come on, just give him
a one good hit!
No, the enemy is that thing you know?
A monster, a monster!
This wouldn't be a mission!
Next time:
"Ino Screams! Chubby Paradise!"