Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
I'll give it to you straight...
Your next mission was commissioned
by a certain Feudal Lord's daughter.
You are to act as her double.
I don't know where she heard about you,
but you apparently bear
a striking resemblance to the princess.
Therefore she requested
that you be the one who carries it out...
A double...?
Is someone targeting the princess?
Well, if anything,
she's the one who's doing the targeting...
Huh?
Not to worry.
You're already an admirable
Hidden Leaf Shinobi.
Furthermore, I've arranged for you
to have an assistant.
Assistant?
Grandma Tsunade!
You have a mission for me?
And one from a Feudal Lord to boot!
Huh?!
Lady Tsunade!
Sorry, but all the other guys
are too busy.
Just me and this guy?
Yup.
Do your best to carry out the mission.
The client is
a Feudal Lord's daughter, huh...
Wow... I guess that means that
I've finally became good enough
to handle amazing missions
like this, huh?!
Hey, don't get too excited.
Terrible things happen
when you're like that.
I know...
Just leave things in my capable hands!
You're really a piece of work...
Ino Screams! Chubby Paradise!
Thank you for coming from afar.
That's the client?
She and Ino really do look alike, but...
I It's a bit of a stretch...
It's all right.
I have an idea of what you wish to say.
My physique doesn't really resemble
that of the double there...
That's what you're thinking, right?
- Oh... not at all... Umm...
- To be honest,
- I don't think you resemble her at all.
- Hey!
Well, I don't blame you for thinking that.
But here, have a look at this!
T That's... Ino!
That's what I looked like
a short time ago...
Truth be told, I only got like this
after it was decided that
I was to have an arranged courtship.
An arranged courtship?!
The other party is Master Chikara
from the neighboring Land of Udon.
Ever since I saw his picture,
my feelings for him
have deepened day by day.
And as the day
of the arranged courtship grows closer,
I have become increasingly nervous,
my cheeks have been flushed,
and my heart has been pounding.
I can't even sleep at night.
And because of that stress,
I've started overeating...
It goes without saying that
you'll get fat if you pig out.
Of course,
I've taken appropriate countermeasures!
I've been using something that cuts all
the fats and carbohydrates that I ingest...
"Easy -Peasy Slim Special
It didn't work, did it?
I placed too strong hopes in it...
How can I possibly have
an arranged courtship
with the man I'm infatuated with
when I look like this?
So that's my situation...
Now, let's get to the main issue.
I want you to attend
the arranged courtship in my place
and make it a success at any cost.
Huh?!
So this double thing
is just to act on you behalf
at some arranged courtship?!
What do you mean by
"some arranged courtship"?!
I mean, when you talk about doubles,
you thinks of situations
where someone's life is in danger
and that sort of thing.
What are you talking about?!
The princess's entire life is at stake!
This is major!
Oh! So you understand a heart in love...
I sure do...
A girl always wants to look cute
for the guy she loves.
Even if she's a fake?
It can't be helped.
I mean, guys prefer slender girls.
That's exactly right!
I'm counting on you.
Sure thing! Leave it to me!
But even if
the arranged courtship goes well...
The gap is just too big.
I'll just have to lose weight
by the day of the wedding.
I already have a plan in place for that.
This supplemental type diet food,
"Supplement Slender"!
If I supplement all three meals with this...
Why don't you draw on the lessons
you're supposed to have learned...?
In any case, I'll use my charms to make
this arranged courtship a success!
This annex is where
I often played in my childhood.
I plan to use this to listen in on
the arranged courtship from here.
Huh... That's pretty convenient.
I would love to meet him in person
if I could, but...
Hey, is he that cool looking?
Of course he is!
He's someone with
something really special about him!
Well then,
just make sure he falls for you.
Leave it to me!
I thought you weren't motivated...
Well, this is a mission after all.
So I think I'll pull myself together
and hustle!
Don't do anything unnecessary, okay!
W What's up?
The sound is getting closer!
- What?
- It's so bright!
There are many a handsome man
in this world,
but this man is
renowned even among them!
This man makes
Land of Udon what it is...
that sexy man
with glistening sidelong glances!
The oh so great young prince Chikara...
Kneel down and bow before him!
Sorry.
It appears that
I have kept you waiting, princess
You're... Master Chikara?
He's even more intense than
Intense Brow Sensei.
I'm sorry, pretty girl.
I have constitutional low blood pressure.
Dunno. He looks more like
he has high blood pressure to me...
What?
D Do you always scatter
flower petals?
Flowers are wonderful.
They truly allay the fatigue
of your mind and your body.
Don't you find them relaxing?
I I guess...
Okay then, next...
Hey, don't you think
he's different from her description...?
I mean, he's fa...
Fa?!
Stop!
These sweets are really fabulous,
aren't they?
Do excuse us a little.
What the heck are you doing,
out of the blue like that?!
It's women's intuition.
I got the same vibe from him as Choji.
That word is probably taboo.
Oh, I see!
Gimme a break!
What's up with that uselessly
intense chubby guy showing up
when she told us
he'd be a handsome prince?!
But wouldn't his physique
be a perfect match for her?
I'm sure there must be some mistake.
There's no way a girl
would fall in love with a guy like that.
But maybe that's
the princess' taste in men...
That's impossible. I mean...
He's flashy!
Intense...!
And a fatso!
He's a freak! A freak!
There's gotta be a mistake!
I'm sure of it!
Y You think so?
What are you saying?
There's no mistake that that's
Master Chikara, the man of my heart.
I thought so...
What an elegant man...
I deeply regret that I cannot see him
up close with my very own eyes.
I guess one could say that everybody
has their own set of woes.
Listen, make sure that
he takes a liking to me no matter what!
Stop complaining and get the ball rolling
with dogged persistence!
I will convey that to her.
Has you tension not eased?
Music is good for relaxation.
Please, you need not go to the trouble...
- What did she say?
- She said there's no mistake.
She wants you to bulldoze on ahead!
I can't believe it!
It's our mission, you know!
I know that...
Princess Fuku... do you like roses?
Yes... very much so...
Great!
I love roses too!
In the language of flowers,
they signify love!
But don't their meanings
differ depending on their color?
For example, yellow roses are
supposed to mean " Let's break up...
It's nonsense to discriminate
because of color...
I mean the flowers
are not at fault, after all.
For you.
Hey... wait!
Huh?
I can't do it! I can't do it!
There's no way!
He's too intense.
There's no way I can act as
a substitute for the princess!
Calm down.
Stop saying that and do your best.
Nope.
I just can't stand him physically.
Oh, I got it.
If you just think of him
- as a somewhat intense Choji...
- Choji has fat on him
for the sake of his Ninjutsu...
I don't have the slightest idea
what purpose that prince's fat serves.
That's a pretty severe opinion,
you know...
I'm going off somewhere for a moment.
Huh? Hey, where are you going?!
Gimme a break, that girl's a handful...
Well, this is for the sake of
a mission after all.
I guess it's about time for Naruto
to lend a helping hand!
What is it?!
I'm not judging you, but I think you
should pass on that young prince.
There's something wrong with his head.
I'm positive!
What are you saying?
He's a passionate and wonderful man!
But...
I hired the Leaf to
provide me with substitute for
the arranged courtship
and bring it to success.
You're a professional Shinobi, right?
So I suggest you get on it
and get the job done!
The atmosphere in there
hasn't been very congenial at all!
You need to be aggressive
in making yourself appealing to him!
I'm sorry to have
kept you waiting, Chikara!
That's right!
Just like that... huh?
That jerk...!
H Hey!
P-P-Princess?
Master Chikara... Could you loosen
my sash for me, please?
But... but...
Please.
Oh my gosh!
There's a creepy crawler up here
under the roof that looks like a sow bug!
Mind Destruction Jutsu!
A creepy -crawler
that looks like a sow bug?
An insect?
Oh... she vanished...
What the heck are you thinking?!
Where is the princess?
I don't know.
She vanished...
What is going on anyway?
This is starting to irritate me...
I can't get what's happening from here.
Why are you meddling!
I was just one step away!
What do you think you're doing,
dressed up like Princess Fuku?!
I'm telling you!
In one of Pervy Sage's books
happened to glance at,
this is the kind of thing that worked.
I don't believe that anyone would
use such a garish advance!
That's dirty!
There's absolutely no way
a type of guy like you
would ever be mistaken for
the protagonist of a boy's comic!
Huh! I was doing a way better job
than you were!
Gimme a break...
Now that things have come to this,
I need to take care of business
before another meddler gets in the way!
Huh... You gotta be kidding...
It looks like my help is needed
if this mission is going to be a success.
Princess...
where in the world have you been?
Please forgive me. I was so nervous
I just flew into a panic earlier on...
You really seemed like
a totally different person.
I'm so sorry.
You were such a wonderful person,
that it became almost unbearable...
Non. That is bad.
We must change
the air in here then.
Oh, in that case, I will...
Hi... Chikara!
Huh?
That just now,
outside the sliding paper door...
What's the matter?
There was one more... princess!
That can't be... Impossible.
INNERINO
Naruto...!
But I'm very moved that
you have such deep feelings for me
that you actually saw a vision...
Vision? No, I definitely saw...
You mustn't look!
P-Princess?
Damn...I did that without thinking...
Oh goodness me...
In my ardent desire for
you to look just at me, I...
What intense passion...
All right...
As you wish, princess.
- Huh?
- Allow me to catch
those hot feelings in fine style!
Could this be...?
Come, don't hold back.
Huh?!
You may not kiss him!
No kisses!
Oh!
Goodness, you cannot
be too careful these days!
Who told you that you could
go as far as kissing him?!
Oh, it's not that I wanted to...
I'd have to say that
you actually came to my rescue.
Don't bandy words with me!
Listen carefully, holding hands is
as much as I can concede to you...!
You're too loud!
The princess vanished again.
- Princess!
This isn't good!
I better hurry back.
Don't try anything funny in there!
I know that! In any case, we can't let him
see the two of us together!
Hurry back to your room, Princess!
All right.
Gimme a break that Ino...
Dumping me in the lake like that.
Thanks to her I'm freezing!
This is bad! I gotta pee...
Gotta go!
I don't know where
the toilet is around here.
There's nobody around...
Well, it is an emergency situation after all.
Huh?!
W W What the heck do you think
you're doing over there looking like me?!
No... this is... um...
How shameless!
Stop that immediately!
I can't stop it...
Do you not understand that
I'm telling you to stop!
It's impossible to stop so sudden!
Hey!
Wait up!
I wasn't quite
emotionally prepared earlier on...
However, the feelings I have
for you in my heart are true.
Princess...
Master Chikara...
I have harbored a secret love for you
for a long time.
Please, take me...
Huh?
- I wonder what that sound is?
- I have no idea...
Rain?
What a beautiful rainbow...
Stop, I say!
I told you, it's impossible!
Ouch!
Princess?!
Naruto!
You idiot!
Forgive me for this one, please!
I won't forgive you!
Look what you've done!
Ouch... Stop!
What in the world is going on?!
Oh no!...
Umm... this is, well...
All right, that's enough...
We can't fake it any longer.
I apologize for having hoodwinked you.
I am... the bona fide Fuku.
You mean to say that
the princess up to now was an imposter?
That is correct.
What is the meaning of all this?
I wouldn't have imagined that
things would come to such a finale!
No, that's not correct, Master Chikara!
Out of my way!
The super body I fantasized about
in my dreams! My ideal personified!
Bravo!
- Huh?
My cute princess. Please marry me!
I'm delighted, Master Chikara!
Hail the future wife!
What is this anyway...?
Somehow it seems like our mission
turned out to be success in the end...
I think?
Could it be? I put all my efforts
in making advances on a guy
who's not my type in the least
and got rejected.
Moreover,
it was a totally wasted effort...
Is that what happened?
But, everything turned out well.
So isn't it okay?
And both of them look so happy together...
That's not the problem!
A damsel's heart has been wounded...
I can't believe that, of all things,
I was brushed off by a guy like that...
He didn't even glance in your direction
at the end there.
Stop it! Don't remind me.
You can never knows
what a person likes, can you?
Nope...
there's no way I'll acknowledgerthat!
A man's got to like a slender girl better!
In order to become
even more of a woman,
I'm going on a diet! On a diet!
Wait... wait up!
On a checkerboard night
when the stardust's are rapidly dancing
I just can't come out and say,
"Ah, I don't want to go home yet."
Suggestively
Spat at that beloved face!!
Mister Cricket
The Trombone gradually going off key
While on the sweaty center stage
does bug me.
But more importantly, the fuzziness I feel
in my undeveloped chest,
I wonder if it's from
that coke I just drank?
Naruto, let's make some
bittersweet memories of youth together!
- Huh?
- No need to be shy.
I am ready both in mind and body!
What are you blabbing about
all of a sudden?!
It was long...
To think how much
I've waited for this moment!
I have no idea what you're talking about!
Here I come Naruto!
Please become my first.
Just a minute.
Next Time: "Viva Dojo Challenge!
Youth is all about Passion!"