Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
Milady, the skies have
begun to look threatening.
We should seek lodging for the night
before we get rained on.
I see. Carry on.
Yes, Milady.
What dense fog?!
We cannot see what's up ahead.
What was that?
Is something the matter?
Lady Kayo!
The Mysterious Curse
of the Haunted House
I hear that it happened while the mistress
of the Land of Honey, Lady Kayo,
was on her way to visit the household
of her parents in Land of Candy.
Attendants from Land of Candy
went out to meet them,
thinking it odd
that their arrival was delayed,
only to find that the palanquin and poles
had been cast away at the mountain pass.
I am told that Lady Kayo and
all of her attendants have disappeared.
Then, our task is to search
for the Lady, right?
That is so.
Hinata's Byakugan and Kiba
and Akamaru's keen sense of smell
should prove helpful
in this search mission,
and Naruto is, well, just Naruto.
What are you saying, Grandma?
That I have nothing in particular
to recommend me?
But isn't that the case?
I think that you have
good points, too, Naruto...
Oh! Leave it to Hinata.
Go ahead and list them up
for Grandma Tsunade!
Come on,
what are my good points?
Er... umm...
Let me see...
It shouldn't be that hard!
I didn't mean to make it
seem that way... Um... well...
Hey there, you two.
Are you done?
Say, Grandma, there wouldn't be
anything odd
happening in this mission, would there?
Something odd?
That is to say... might there perhaps...
be ghosts involved?
Ghosts?
Are you afraid of such things?
Well, umm, er... kinda.
There are no such things as ghosts.
Stop talking such nonsense
and get on your way.
Which brings us to the question
of where to, Fifth Hokage?
Kubisaki Pass.
K Kubisaki Pass?
As in the Broken Neck Pass?
I knew I had a bad premonition.
Fool!
A Shinobi shouldn't dally about such
things. Get to business!
You're scarier than any ghost!
We're off!
Excuse us.
It's always like this with that one...
Lady Tsunade,
Kubisaki Pass is where
the capital of
the Land of Necks once stood isn't it?
The ruined castle of the Kubisaki Clan,
which met its destruction 50 years ago,
must still be there.
And what of it?
Ruined castles may be found
just about anywhere.
Have you caught
Naruto's cowardice bug, Shizune?
N -No, that's not it.
Oh, this is the spot.
The Broken Neck Pass.
It gives me the creeps
somehow, I tell you.
It's started to rain. Let's hurry.
It's really coming down!
A castle.
I hadn't heard anything
about a castle standing here.
Somehow,
I have a bad feeling about this.
See, see?! This mission is starting
to seem creepier and creepier.
But this may be a major clue.
Let's go.
Yeah. At this rate,
we'll get soaking wet.
H-Hey, don't be in such a hurry!
What a magnificent castle.
Won't it be sort of rude
to suddenly intrude upon them?
It's almost night.
Maybe we'll be causing them trouble.
Naruto, don't tell me
you really are scared!
N-No way, I tell you!
Pull yourself together, Naruto.
Let's go.
The door opened by itself!
Excuse me, is anybody home?
The lights are turned on.
Please let us shelter here
from the rain for a bit!
Hey! Wait! Akamaru!
Excuse us!
Good evening.
Something sure smells good.
It's still warm.
Was someone here
until just a little while ago?
What's that?
That's one scary looking guy.
I wonder if he's the master of this castle.
If he's the master of this castle,
than that makes him a feudal lord right?
If this is the feudal lord's castle,
then the area around here
should be the capital.
But this is right on the country borderline.
Hey! Akamaru!
What are you doing?
You shouldn't eat that
without permission.
- Naruto?
- What is it?
Don't startle me like that.
Just now, the painting's eyes moved!
You moron. How could a painting move?
You're too much of a scaredy cat.
The table's set for seven people.
So, what of it?
The Land of Honey party that
went missing also numbered seven.
The Lady and her attendants
may still be in this castle...
Let's split up and search for them.
Wha...?
We gonna split up?
Since we're all here together,
why don't we search together?
What do you say, Kiba? Hinata?
Naruto, stop talking like a kid.
This is a mission!
You don't have to scold me so much!
I know that!
Hey! Wait a minute!
I'm just not cut out for this kind of stuff.
This is scarier than going to the bathroom
in the middle of the night!
This is creepy!
No!
Not again!
Kiba, Hinata, Akamaru!
I'm too scared alone, after all!
Do you sense it, too? I'm sure this is
the scent of a human being.
It's here.
There's no one here.
I'll eat you up.
Who's that?
Is someone there?
The ceiling...
Take that, you.
Look at all these books!
The History of Neck Castle...
This was written a full fifty years ago!
"The enemy forces
have already surrounded the castle.
"Our people were brutally
slaughtered and
"there're only few of the soldiers
left in castle.
"It seems certain that
I would not live to see nightfall either.
"But my thirst for vengeance
remains in the castle,
"and I vow with this castle
to consume every last man,
"every human setting foot
within these walls...
"Signed, Gosa Kubisaki."
Consume?
I'll eat you...
What is this?
Gosa Kubisaki!
Crap!
Hinata! Hey!
Hinata! Pull yourself together!
Naruto...
Naruto, Hinata, are you all right?
Kiba, Akamaru!
A castle that fell fifty years ago?
What nonsense!
That is how the scroll is dated.
It says that everyone who enters this castle
will be eaten alive.
True, we have been swallowed whole!
Naruto!
Are you okay? Hey!
That hurt!
There he is!
I I'm sorry!
What is this?
This isn't the armor of the Kubisaki Clan.
I wonder if this belonged
to an enemy soldier...
There's some more over there.
They are different armors.
Those armors bear
the crest of the Kubisaki Clan.
Let's hurry up and get out of here!
That's the same armor as in the painting!
Could it be...
that this is the real Gosa Kubisaki?
Gosa Kubisaki?
What's going on?
He's melting!
What is this?
Something smells really sour.
There is something
strange about this castle.
Hinata!
Yeah.
Byakugan!
The whole wall is covered
with a flow of Chakra.
Why?
It's moving!
This wall seems to be alive!
What if...
Gentle Fist!
A Are you all right, Hinata?
Uh huh.
I've seen something very similar to this
somewhere before.
The giant toad summoned
by the Pervy Sage...
from inside its stomach!
Inside its stomach?!
Then, I wonder if, by chance,
this smell could be... gastric juices?!
Gosa Kubisaki invoked
the Summoning d utsu
before the fall of the castle.
But the thing he summoned...
was big enough
to swallow the entire castle whole.
From the time we entered the castle,
we, too, have been gobbled up!
But, why would this thing go to the trouble
of transforming to a castle to eat us?
I don't know.
What was that?
Oh!
H Help!
Are you the Lady of the Land of Honey?
She's embedded in the wall.
We are from
the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
We have come to help you.
Here, I'll help you out now.
It's no use.
Please hang on!
Oh no! This thing is rounding up
all the humans inside here
and returning to its original form.
At this rate, we're in danger too!
Naruto, Hinata,
we've got to get out of here!
Man Beast Clone!
Fang over Fang!
I am the castle.
And by order of my master Gosa,
I am to eat all who set foot within.
Naruto!
Ouch...
I'll eat you.
How can w e get out of its stomach?!
I don't know.
If this creature was Summoned,
then there should be
a scroll for the contract.
If we tear up the scroll, then this creature
should return to the world it came from.
Is that so?
- Hinata!
- Right!
Byakugan!
Found it.
It's up above.
Probably in the castle tower.
How are we supposed to
get up there in this situation?!
The wall's Chakra have
begun to stabilize again.
Who's that?
Gosa Kubisaki!
I won't be fooled again.
That, too, is just a phantom
created by the Summoning.
Wait!
He looks different from the one before.
Wh What's he doing?
He seems to want us to follow him.
Huh? He disappeared!
Naruto, over there.
Oh, it's the scroll!
It's starting to act up again.
Hurry, Naruto!
Right!
This is...
It's the true form
of the Summoned animal.
The concentration of acid is increasing.
Hey, let's hurry and wind things up!
Wait a minute.
What if, when this summoned animal
goes back to where it came from,
it takes us with it, too?
We'll just have to take our chances.
We gotta do this!
Right.
Did that do it?
What the?!
Naruto!
Over there, Naruto.
It should be possible
to tear the wall at that spot.
Okay! Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Rasengan!
Naruto!
The lord of this castle must have died
resenting the people
who seized the castle from him.
But, he also led us
to where the scroll was hidden...
Then, does that mean that
he decided to let go of his grudge?
Surely that must be the case.
What's more, he must have felt sorry for
the Summoned animal that
nobly served him for fifty years,
and wanted to release it.
I see.
Then maybe he was waiting
for someone
to release the Summoned animal
from its spell.
And now, it has finally been able to
return to its own world.
On a checkerboard night
when the stardust's are rapidly dancing
I just can't come out and say,
"Ah, I don't want to go home yet."
Suggestively
Spat at that beloved face!!
Mister Cricket
The Trombone gradually going off key
While on the sweaty center stage
does bug me.
But more importantly, the fuzziness I feel
in my undeveloped chest,
I wonder if it's from
that coke I just drank?
How did it go, Bushy Brow?
Hush. He doesn't look himself.
He sure looks gloomy.
The results were bad.
I'd say considerably.
Huh? "Considerably"?
It can't be helped.
It must have been considerable.
Then... could it be that Bushy Brow is...?
Yes... I'm sorry but...
Then he's considerably...
considerably...?!
Next time: "The Third Super-Beast!"