Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
Say, Grandma Tsunada,
am I really so...?
Come to think of it, recently I feel dull
and I make more mistakes
with Jutsu than before.
And, what's more, even worse...
I can't eat more than five of
the large size ramen noodles at Ichiraku...
Might I perhaps have
some terrible illness?!
Come on, and tell me.
I'm prepared to hear the worst!
You are in good health.
Huh?
Hey! That's Bushy Brow's
medical record, isn't it?
Recently he's been avoiding
his regular check ups.
Bring him in, will you?
Huh? But, what about me?
You are stupid. That's all!
Be on your way!
- Put your clothes back on, you idiot!
- Yes!
Unbelievable!
How was it?
I'm fit as a fiddle!
I could tell that just by looking at you.
What's that all about?
He doesn't seem to be in
a very good mood, does he?
Oh, by the way,
have you seen Bushy Brow?
No, but I know where he is.
These days,
you can always find him here.
Oh...
2954... 2955...
2956... 2957... 2958...
That's just amazing...
Even after having surgery
for the kind of injury
that could prevent him from
continuing on as a Ninja...
- Bushy Brow!
- Lee!
Bushy Brow!
Lee...
It's nothing.
Grandma Tsunada told me to bring you
for your regular check up.
It slipped my mind.
I've been feeling fine lately, so I just...
You don't look like it though.
HIDDEN LEAF HOSPITAL
Rest for a while.
You are forbidden from engaging in
any missions or training for the duration.
There is cumulative damage
to your Chakra Network!
You were once injured so badly
that you had to give up on being
a Ninja for a while.
It's my self rule.
Your self rule?
Yes! To never forget
my original intentions!
As long as I keep on trying,
I will be able to continue on as a Ninja!
All right.
I will remove you from active duty
for a while,
but you may continue training.
Just don't overdo it.
Yes!
In particular,
I prohibit you to use Hidden Lotus!
Got that?
Y Yes...
Oh! Hey, Bushy Brow, how did it go?
What's wrong? Hey!
The results were bad.
Judging from the way he looked,
I'd say considerably...
By " considerably,
do you mean that considerably?
Yes.
Considerable, to be sure.
Considerable?!
What are you so down about?! Lee!
Guy Sensei!
I heard the results of the exam.
You have permission to train, don't you?
Yes, but the Hidden Lotus...
That day, you were crying right there...
Your surgery will be a success
because you have worked hard
all the way through.
You have the power to bring
your own future in the heavens.
And in the one in a thousand-
no, one in a million chance
that something goes wrong...
I'm going to die with you!
Ever since the time I met you,
my Way of Ninja has been
bringing you up to be a fine Ninja.
I promise you!
You believed me then and had the surgery.
And it was successful.
You must have faith in me
one more time!
If you can no longer use the Hidden Lotus,
then strive to attain an even
greater technique through your efforts!
There are no limits in
the face of your efforts.
Sensei!
You are a genius at effort!
Yes, sir!
I'll give you some training for
the first time in quite a spell!
First, dash to the Academy practice hall!
Please instruct me!
If you don't get there in ten seconds,
it's 500 push ups!
Right!
The Third Super Beast!
It was rash of us to think we could
make it in ten seconds, after all.
Just as well!
Five hundred...
It's been a long time since
I smelled this smell...
Who is he?
That's Yagura.
He's been here for a week.
An acquaintance asked me to determine
whether he has aptitude as a Ninja.
His name is Yagura, you say?
He's pretty good, isn't he?
Yes, he has the instincts for it.
He absorbs the things I teach him
like sand absorbs water.
Oh! You're Rock Lee, aren't you?
Y Yes...
I hear that you have superb techniques.
Sensei has told me about you.
No, nothing that great...
Don't be bashful, you.
- Master Guy?
- Yes?
I would like to receive some instruction
from my senior.
Fine, then. Begin!
Huh?!
Guy Sensei!
You came to train, anyway.
First, lend a bit of aid to your junior partner
and warm up.
I see...
He's a spring chick who has just arrived,
so try not to let him get hurt.
Right.
What's Bushy Brow doing in
the Academy practice hall of all places?
I thought his condition was
considerably bad!
Yes, considerably! Considerably!
- Huh?!
- Huh?
I'm inexperienced,
but please instruct me.
Oh, please bear with me, too.
Now, Lee and Yagura, I want you both
to give it all you've got
but to also observe
the greatest courtesy.
That is friendship!
That is youth. Get ready. Fight!
H He's fast!
Let's have you show me...
The depth of the Taijutsu that
Might Guy drilled into you!
What power!
Every single blow is heavy!
I haven't the strength to absorb them!
Leaf Hurricane!
Closing off the escape path above
and strike from a low position...
However...
The Leaf Hurricane was defeated!
Stop! Hold it right there!
Lee! Are you all right?
Pull yourself together, Bushy Brow!
What was that that just happened?
The Cross Method...
Meeting the opponent's kick
and pinning his foot between
the knee and elbow simultaneously -
a "bone crushing daring technique."
Where on earth
did you learn that, Yagura!
I didn't intend to do that.
My body just moved
like that involuntarily...
Sorry, Lee. Are you all right?
If Lee hadn't been wearing his weights,
his ankle would have been crushed.
It was a splendid move.
Well then, let's continue with the practice.
Let's stop here for today.
I'll take you to the hospital to
have them look at it.
No, I'm completely fine, I tell you...
We knew from the health check up
that Bushy Brow's injuries were
considerable to begin with, didn't we?
Considerable!
What was considerable?
I'm telling you,
just considerable, right?!
- Probably considerable...
- Considerable, I tell you!
Even with the weights on, that speed...
What was considerable?!
Fortunately, there's nothing wrong
with the bone.
I see.
Um... When can I begin training again?
Huh? What are you saying
You're going to need complete rest
for a while.
It's amazing that your Achilles tendon
remained uninjured, you know...
You said considerable, so...
I misunderstood it to mean that
he was in a considerable condition.
But...
he came out from the examining room
looking very down,
so I just assumed...
To be sure, he seems dispirited.
He was beaten by a trainee
who isn't even enrolled in the Academy.
A trainee? Lee?
Yes, a kid who has been studying Taijutsu
for only one week.
In any case,
he was incredibly skilled, that...
What's it called...?
The Cross Method!
Yes, that!
He's a genius to deploy
that at the instant!
I hope Lee isn't feeling down, though.
If he were the kind of guy to get
downhearted about a thing like that,
Lee would have quit being
a Shinobi a long time ago.
- Huh?
When Lee was in the Academy,
he was told that he had neither
the talent for Ninjutsu,
nor any talent for Genjutsu.
Had it been me,
I would have given up long ago.
But Lee got to where he is now purely
through effort and persistence.
If he can just heal his injuries,
he'll soon outstrip anyone with
natural talent alone.
- That's true.
- Darn right!
But...
I've heard that if you train too hard,
you can wreck your body and
become a decrepit...
Don't say such a thing!
You're talking about Bushy Brow!
I'm only kidding.
Just a slip of the tongue.
- Don't even say that in jest!
- Decrepit?
I know, I know.
But actually, we are grateful to Lee.
Huh? Grateful?
Yes, grateful.
Okay, today I'm going to teach you
about self rule.
Self...
...rule, you say?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Please teach me! Me! Me!
All right, ready?
To all things there are principles,
and to efficiently make use of things
in daily life, human beings have rules.
Okay, today I have something good
to give you all.
- Something...
...good?
This!
O Oh!
These tights of the type that
I habitually use...!
They have outstanding ventilation
and moisture wicking properties!
Developed for ultimate ease of movement,
it's a complete of of super athletic wear!
If you wear them when you're training,
you'll feel the difference immediately!
You won't be able to do without them!
Next thing you know,
you'll be wearing them all the time!
Yes, yes, yes!
Please, by all means, give me a pair!
Oh, I got a pair of those myself.
They look cool, don't they?
Oh... Is that so?
If it weren't for Lee...
This is youth!
This is guts!
This is Harutaro Minami,
spring chicken of the South!
- You got that all wrong!
I'm really glad that we've had Lee around.
Yeah, me too...
I'm sure a C rank mission would
feel insufficient for you,
but there's nobody left to ask but you.
Leave it to me.
Oh, by the way,
there's someone I'd like to take with me...
Yagura!
When my foot heals,
let's train together aga?
I feel no need to take lessons from you.
Even ruling out the fact that
you were wearing weight,
there seems to be nothing worth
stealing from you...
Stealing?
After all, skills acquired
purely through effort
make you nothing
but a pale imitation of Guy Sensei.
What did you say?!
As proof of that,
even Sensei has given up on you.
That can't be!
Guy Sensei promised me...
that his own Way of Ninja was to
turn me into a splendid Ninja, too!
Well then, I wonder why he's gone
so far as to ask me
to come on a mission with him
for practical training...
Not you, but me!
You?
Too bad. There's no way effort
can win out over talent.
Wait!
Did Sensei really asked you to?
No, it... can't be true...
Lady Tsunade!
Wh What is it?
Yagura has been injured and
is under protection.
What? Guy was with him.
What on earth happened?
No! Yagura is said to have been attacked
before reaching Hidden Leaf Village.
Then the trainee Yagura
that accompanied Guy is...
A total imposter.
Damn it, one nuisance after another...!
So, these three are the ones
that can be mobilized?
What shall we do?
Fine! Have Neji, Tenten, and Naruto...
these three go after Guy
and the phony Yagura!
Right!
Wait!
Have Sakura keep an eye on Lee.
If he learns about this,
he's apt to dash out,
even in the shape he's in.
Right!
Are you sure that Intense Brow Sensei
went this way?
Without a doubt!
His destination was
the Land of Mountain Streams.
He must have gone through this forest.
There's another way to go,
cutting through the mountains,
but it's too dangerous.
Yagura, are you with me?
Yes, Guy Sensei!
Don't slow down!
Take each step after first taking
the measure of the mountain terrain!
Right!
Lee could run through here blindfolded.
What's wrong? Yagura?
Oh no!
Yagura! Where are you?! Yagura!
Yagura!
He may be a genius,
but he's still a trainee...
I wonder if I expected
too much from him...
Yagura!
What? Were you in such a place?
Wooden Training Dummies
for kung fu training...
Oh my... It takes me back to my youth.
I trained with a burning spirit on
the same kinds of Wooden Dummies.
It makes my body to just start
moving uncontrollably.
But why are there Wooden Dummies
in such a place?
Who in the world...?
And for what purpose?
They move well for dummies.
But, after all, they just look
like automated dolls.
They only have one pattern of movement,
and no matter
how many of them there are,
their reach only extends for
a diameter of 3.5 meters,
so they cannot attack.
What? Mister, you can move?!
What the heck?!
Hey? Can't you see anything yet? Neji!
Even using the Byakugan,
I can't find a single footprint.
They can't have gotten that far away,
can they?
They wouldn't have used excessively
dangerous mountain paths either...
However they seem to be able to move,
they're just stick figures crawling
over the surface of the ground...
Mister, you can jump, too?!
Not just yet!
Wh What a...!
Pleasant, high energy training place...!
6,985... 6,986... 6,987... 6,988
6,989... 6,990... 6,991...
- There is no limit to training.
- 6,992...
- Even if I cannot use my legs,
- 6,993...
- my upper half is still in good shape.
- 6,994...
- Guy Sensei thinks...
- 6,995...
- my training is inadequate.
- 6,996...
- That's why he compared me with Yagura.
- 6, 997... 6,996...
- to show me that I wasn't doing enough.
- 6,998... 6,999...
7,000!
- I have faith in Guy Sensei!
- 7,001... 7,002...
They're moderately powerful, but...
their movements are monotonous.
Or...so I thought...!
Shall I say I am outnumbered?
There seems to be no limit to them!
Wh What is this sound?
What?!
On a checkerboard night
when the stardust's are rapidly dancing
I just can't come out and say,
"Ah, I don't want to go home yet."
Suggestively
Spat at that beloved face!!
Mister Cricket
The Trombone gradually going off key
While on the sweaty center stage
does bug me.
But more importantly, the fuzziness I feel
in my undeveloped chest,
I wonder if it's from
that coke I just drank?
I thought I knew,
but you do have incredible power, after all.
To think you have such
an amazing kick.
Looks like I have to put out
everything in myself.
Then I would put everything
I've got into this too.
Fine! Why don't you come at me
with intent to beat me?!
Please forgive me Guy Sensei.
But to me, this is the moment...
- to follow through with my own Ninja Way!
- To follow through with my own Ninja Way!
Next time: " Hot Blooded Confrontation:
Student vs. Sensei"