Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, "See you..."
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I'm not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
Kiba!
Naruto!
You okay, Kiba?
Yeah...
Is this also Genjutsu...?!
No one, including Akamaru,
can escape from Yakumo's Genjutsu.
It's because...
we have an enlarged neural tube...
the cerebrum...
Guys, move away from the door!
Parasitic Insects.
Please, Sensei...
Tell me the truth.
If you don't... I'll rub you out...
I reached the decision
to seal your Genjutsu power
at my own discretion.
It has nothing to do with
the Third Hokage...
Vent your resentment...
The only one you should hate is me...
I heard...!
I heard you and
the Third Hokage talking
about trying to destroy
the Kurama Clan!
Yakumo, you've got the wrong idea.
You lie!
No way could my mother
and father die in just a fire!
My parents were killed...!
What?!
Shino...
What's this?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
All right!
I'm counting on you guys!
- Right!
Now, I'm ready when you are...
One, two...
Charge!
Go!
N -Naruto...
Naruto?!
Kurenai Sensei!
What happened to your...?
Yakumo, did you do this...?
That person tried to eliminate me...
So she's just facing the consequences.
You're wrong!
Yakumo, you've
misunderstood something.
I heard everything about you and
Kurenai Sensei from Old Man Unkai.
Stop, Naruto!
Listen up.
Kurenai Sensei sealed your powers
because she cares about you!
What're you talking about?!
You're not the only one who's suffering!
Kurenai Sensei hid the truth all
this time and has suffered alone!
Stop!
The... truth...?
The Supposed Sealed Ability
Guy Sensei!
Hey, where is everyone?!
Shino and Hinata are standing
watch in the hallway,
but Kurenai Sensei and Naruto
are now inside the world
created by Yakumo's Genjutsu!
Huh? What do you mean?!
I'll explain...
Mr. Unkai, you should take it easy.
No... I must now
explain the truth...
Nobody has taken such affectionate care
of Yakumo as Kurenai.
Kurenai's resolve was to get Yakumo
to give up on being a Shinobi...
Yakumo was completely in low spirits.
Lord Murakumo was also concerned...
Then one day, that incident occurred...
The residence of the head family
burned to the ground
and Yakumo stood motionless
in front of it...
I saw it at that time...
The form of a monster with
a face like a female demon
hovering in the flames...!
After learning of its identity...
I became frozen with terror.
What is... the truth?!
Sensei... What the heck is happening
to Yakumo?
This is bad...!
Yakumo! You don't know...
You don't know anything!
Something's... Yes...
There is something...
in the recesses of my mind...
But... What is it...?
I can't remember...
Oh no...!
Naruto, stop that!
Huh?!
Naruto!
What is this thing?!
Damn it. Let me go!
All I want to do is live up to
everyone's expectations, and yours.
And yet...
Why does everyone get in my way?
I just want to become a Genjutsu user...
People have their respective
appropriate paths.
You probably have your own path.
That's right...
There's no need to force yourself
to become a Shinobi...
No... I don't want that!
Everyone may comfort me with words...
But I know.
I know they're disappointed in me.
I can't stand having to live
my whole life feeling that burden.
Yakumo, what's that...?
R-Run, Uroko!
Yakumo!
I remember...
Yakumo...?!
Yes... me...
The person inside me killed
my mother and father...!
I killed them with Genjutsu!
No, Yakumo!
That wasn't you...
You and that monster are different!
No, we're not different...
You see, that thing...
was living inside my heart.
Thanks... Kurenai Sensei...
Goodbye...
Stop!
Yakumo!
Wh What's... that...?!
In order for us to get
a clear picture of the incident,
we first requested
a complete examination of Yakumo...
As a result, we learned the monster
that appeared at the time of the fire
was an Id Monster so to speak,
created by Yakumo's sub consciousness.
An Id... Monster...
Then I made a direct appeal
to the Third Hokage...
Ultimately, Yakumo could
not endure the weight
of living up to our expectations
from the time she was little
and that triggered her sub-consciousness
to attempt to expunge everything.
Yakumo's sub consciousness
will probably attempt to
expunge the Kurama Clan
and eventually the entire Leaf Village.
I cannot consent to that...
Despite such a risk,
taking the life of Yakumo who has
no awareness of evil cannot be allowed!
It'll be too late
once her sub consciousness
completely awakens!
Then we just have to get her
to learn how to control it herself...
or seal her powers if that's not possible.
But...
Although slightly different
from Yakumo's case...
There's a precedent of a baby being used
to seal the Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit.
That's absurd...!
There isn't a Jutsu practitioner
who can seal the strong powers
Yakumo possesses...
There might be just one person
who can accomplish that...
However, it will become
a painful mission.
Hopefully, this person can teach her
how to control her powers...
But if it comes to sealing her powers,
the Jutsu practitioner will end up
erasing all the potential in the child...
The Jutsu practitioner will
have to live with the burden
of Yakumo's resentment
in place of the Kurama Clan...
The Third Hokage said that
and then cried.
The one who accepted that
painful mission was...
Yuhi Kurenai.
I see...
So that's what Kurenai Sensei
was talking about.
I... didn't know anything about Sensei...
I knew that Kurenai had sealed
Yakumo's powers...
But it's the first time I've heard
about the incident
her sub consciousness caused.
Yes... The Third Hokage passed away
and at this point, it's a secret known only
to the Kurama Clan and Yuhi Kurenai.
She made herself into the bad guy
and kept the secret, huh...?
Kurenai Sensei...!
You go, too!
- But...
- Sakura...
I'll take over things here...!
Guy Sensei...
You're concerned about Naruto
and the others, right?
Go to them...!
Right!
I leave Yakumo... to you...
What is it...?
I don't know... But...
This feeling...
It's somehow
entirely different from before...
My insects are acting strange.
What's going on inside?!
Is Kurenai Sensei okay?
It's powerful...
A massive Chakra beyond compare
is being produced...!
Naruto...
Why? Why do you have
to take your own life?
What...?!
What must be destroyed are the ones
who forced you to shoulder
a heavy burden
and on top of that,
tried to eliminate me!
Who're you...?
I crept into an opening in the depths
of your mind and was nurtured.
My name is Id...!
She's finally awoken...
Kurenai Sensei,
what is that thing?
It happened soon after I was made
Yakumo's personal instructor.
It was when I had doubts about
the high level of Yakumo's Genjutsu
and looked into her deep psyche.
I discovered that thing!
I could only stand motionless
in front of that terrible figure.
It wasn't Yakumo whom
the Third Hokage said to eliminate...
It was her Id monster...
So that's what it was...?
This ominous ghastliness...
is more powerful than before.
But I must stop it from getting
into the real world,
even if we have to kill each other...!
Kill each other?!
I see...
She was that determined...
So that's why she quit Squad Eight.
I'll take your feelings into this body
and settle the score...
You jerk!
You're in the way. Move it!
Naruto!
I don't know
what the heck you are...
But Kiba, Shino, Hinata,
they're all waiting for Sensei's return!
Naruto!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
My Jutsu won't activate in this world...!
You are a thorn in my side...
I'll erase you first.
Look out!
Yakumo, you're the only one
who can defeat it now!
What...?
Listen, Yakumo... All people have
a fanged beast in their minds...
It always lives in the depths of
a person's mind
and will suddenly appear.
The power of the beast that
appears is enormous and
regardless of one's own will,
it can inadvertently hurt those around it.
But... if that monster can be tamed
and then controlled
with one's own power...
It becomes a magnificent power
and acts to make
your dreams come true.
Now, fight!
A bate by your own hand
the monster you created!
B-But...
Yakumo, only you can do this!
Die, boy...
Darkness in my mind, abate!
Die!
Why...?
I... served... you well...
Kurenai Sensei,
you're back to normal!
Kurenai... Sensei...
You did well, Yakumo...
You defeated your own darkness.
Sensei...
You did it, Yakumo...
Yakumo...
She knew exactly who was
really trying to save her...
- Kurenai Sensei!
- Sensei...
It's okay now!
Kurenai Sensei...
You'll go back to being
everyone's teacher, right?
That's right...
My final mission from
the Third Hokage is over...
- Sensei!
That's great that things could
get back to normal...
Sakura...!
Naruto...?
I will too.
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I'm told that
there is no bright future
I'll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
This isn't funny!
Why do we have to get all worn out
for someone like him?
Exactly! We were told to protect
the Beauty of Nature,
but he keeps getting in our way.
Is this some kind of joke?
Plus, he uses people as scapegoats
and shields.
He thinks it's only natural for
Shinobi to die in missions.
I can't take this anymore!
Me neither.
If it comes to this, then I'm...
...gonna use Rasengan!
...gonna use Gatsuuga!
- And beat up this client up so bad!
Next time:
"The Weight of The Prized A rtifact!"