Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, "See you..."
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I'm not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
The Weight of the Prized Artifact!
More to the right!
Okay! Okay!
There it is! That's it!
But...
A teacup like this a treasure, huh...?
A delivery mission?
No, it's delivery protection
to be exact.
There's a higher risk of danger
than a regular delivery.
The Beauty of Nature is a treasure
of national importance so to speak.
In monetary value, you could buy
one or two mountains with its value.
For real... ?
I'd like you to deliver it safely
to Kale Avenue
where it will be put on exhibition.
At any rate, what's with
that humongous safe?
You're late.
Kiba...
Lady Tsunade told me to come
as pursuit personnel
just in case something happens
to the delivery item...
Have you heard anything else?
Nothing special other than
it's an incredible treasure...
No Trespassing
Hey, you with the stupid look.
Huh?
Can't you see
the "no trespassing" sign, huh?!
No, we came here on a delivery mission
from Lady Tsunade for that thing.
That's right!
Here's the paperwork.
Huh?
Look out.
It's going to fall!
Run, Naruto!
Hey, what're you doing, bro?
Hm? What're you doing?!
Stop it, quickly!
You came on a mission, didn't you?!
Get to work, you idiots!
H Hey!
Even if you die, don't knock it over!
All right!
That was close...
S So what should we do with this, bro?
Die.
You jerk...
As for you brother, what kind
of person are you?!
We were just about to die!
Huh?
Ninja are supposed to risk their lives
on a commissioned mission, right?
Just a minute, buddy!
I'm not your buddy!
I'm your client on this mission, Shinemon.
Come on...
Get a move on if you're not dead.
Akamaru, Fang over Fang!
No, I'll pound him
with my Rasengan!
Don't get so serious!
Hey! What's the deal?!
Are you guys not fired up?!
Jeez. Getting all
uselessly carried away.
You'll get no sympathy
if you get all tired later on!
This here is not like you guys, this here!
So you got too carried away
and dropped it?
I'm so sorry!
Jeez... Well, we've got the time,
so I guess all we can do
is go down and get it.
No... It seems we don't
have that much time.
Huh?
Wh What do we do, Kiba?!
If we took the roundabout way,
we'd never make it in time!
All right!
All right?
What're you going to do, buddy?!
Let's bungee jump!
Why me...?!
Die like you just don't care!
I'll pick up your bones for you!
I did it!
No way?!
That was a close one.
Idiot! Naruto, behind you, behind you!
Huh? What?
No way!
That was a close one...
Y You...
You got a problem? Huh?
A Ninja expects to lose his life
on a mission, right?!
Buddy, you want to try dying once?
Don't stop me, Kiba!
I'll pound him no matter what
with my Rasengan!
S Stop it! Calm down, Naruto!
I'm really sorry!
Hey, act more natural.
You idiot...
I am acting natural,
no matter how you look at it...!
No way... Totally unnatural...
Just a minute, you guys.
Jeez...
It seems there's something
very valuable in there...
If you like,
we could carry it for you instead.
Now... Hand it over here.
We'll carry it for you with care.
N No...
It's not really anything valuable.
I mean, how should I put it... right?
That's right. It's not like that at all.
Right, buddy?
What're you guys talking about?!
It's extremely valuable.
Have you forgotten that there's
a national treasure class relic inside?!
It's the Beauty of Nature!
It's the Beauty of Nature
more valuable than human life!
Hey, are you guys underestimating it?!
Wh What're you saying?!
Hey, buddy, do you understand
the situation?!
Shut up! Situation?
You gotta be kidding!
I absolutely won't forgive anyone
who insults the Beauty of Nature!
So... A treasure more valuable
than life, huh?
Then you won't have a problem
with being killed, right?
Oh, sorry... I must be going
as I've got cram school today.
Run!
- Hey, hold it!
I'll take care of things here.
You escape with Shinemon, Kiba!
Right! Come on!
Others have popped up!
What're you doing escaping with me?!
Do something quickly, you idiot!
Jeez, what a jerk...!
You go on ahead!
Okay... Let's go, Akamaru!
A battle has started again, huh?
Yes. A battle has started again.
It's a sad thing.
Yes. It's a sad thing.
H Hey!
You're late, you idiots.
I'll get you, no matter what!
Akamaru, Fang Over Fang!
Fang Over Fang!
I It's a joke, man! A joke!
At last we've nailed down the location
of the treasured Beauty of Nature...
Something coming!
Buddy, you stay right here!
R-Right...!
Stop hiding and come on out!
A smoke screen.
That's a good idea...!
What're you doing
getting impressed, you idiot?!
Do something, quickly!
We know!
Let's go, Kiba!
Yeah!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Now, let's tear it up, Akamaru!
Since our vision has been sealed,
we'll just use scent!
Let's show them, Akamaru!
Where are you hiding?!
The Beauty of Nature is mine.
Oh no!
Let's go, Akamaru!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry:
Man Beast Clone!
Fang Over Fang!
Then... we'll do this! Akamaru!
Dynamic Marking!
Whoa! What's this?!
Buddy, what's the matter?!
S Something's salty!
I'm coming!
Naruto, where are you?!
Get over here now, you idiot!
You're late, Naruto!
You okay, buddy?
Naruto...
Spraying piss?!
I'll pound you guys for sure!
Taking back the treasure comes first!
That's right!
Oh man! I knew I should've
taken charge of it!
If we trace the scent of
Akamaru's Dynamic Marking,
it should work out, but...
I see, Akamaru...
They're still not far?
All right, let's go!
We did it... We finally did it!
What're you doing?
Shut up!
They came to take this back!
Let's get out of here!
You won't get away!
Hold it!
Impertinent! Go!
We'll handle things here.
So you go after him!
- Right!
- Let's go, Kiba!
Right!
Hold it!
You won't get away, you jerk!
It ends here! See you later!
Let's hurry!
I won't hand it over...!
Let go!
Boy, I was going to let you
slide by with your life, but...
Give it back...
The Beauty of Nature...
Give it back...!
Haven't you
misunderstood something?
You'll let me off with my life?
That Beauty of Nature...
is a super first rate treasure
more precious than human life...
The question of my life
was never of a concern!
Don't make light of me! Got that?!
You okay, buddy?!
Jeez, you Genin are really useless.
You're all beaten up yourself, buddy!
Y You jerk!
Damn it! I'll put an end
to things here at once!
Everything's over!
We'll be in a fix
if we don't hurry, Naruto!
Let's get a move on, brother!
Buddy!
Quick! Take the Beauty of Nature
to a safe location.
No way, what're you saying
You'll get crushed if you don't hurry.
Wh What're you guys looking at?!
Take the Beauty of Nature while you can...
What're you saying?!
Hurry!
Buddy! You okay?!
Oh! The Beauty of Nature!
Don't move, buddy!
Gently, hold out your hand!
Idiot, what're you doing?!
Just hurry up and come this way!
You guys are the idiots!
Forget about me.
If you're Ninja,
do something about
the Beauty of Nature
rather than my life!
Naruto, let's just forget
about this guy!
He should just die like
a dog on his own!
Let's hurry and get out of here!
Yeah, do as you like!
The Beauty of Nature...
Brother!
Am I...going to die...?
We were just about to die!
Huh?
Ninja are supposed to
risk their lives
on a commissioned mission, right?
Come on...
Get a move on if you're not dead.
It's the Beauty of Nature!
It's the Beauty of Nature,
more valuable than human life!
Hey, are you guys underestimating it?!
I'm gonna...just like this...
Haven't you misunderstood something?
You'll let me off with my life?
That Beauty of Nature...
is a super first rate treasure
more precious than human life...
The question of my life
was never a concern!
Heck no...
I don't want to die!
There's nothing in this world
more valuable than life!
Nice... bungee jump...
Now then, what shall I do now?
Y Yeah...
Sure enough...
without the treasure...
Don't mope like that.
That's why you guys are useless.
But there's no point without
the treasure after all!
Huh? If there isn't one,
then I just have to make one.
Make...? You say that
like it's easy, but...
That's a picture of you, buddy.
The creator of the dauntless artifact...
Beauty of Nature...
Shinemon, the living national treasure?
So basically...?
That means you made
the Beauty of Nature, buddy?!
But, you're... the client...
You got a problem
with the client being the creator
and a living national treasure?
But no matter how you look at it...
This here's not like you guys!
This here!
Well, you know...
It means my life rather than
the treasure was the correct answer.
You do pretty good work for Genin.
Thanks for the help.
Now then, I guess I'll hurry
and make a masterpiece to
exceed the Beauty of Nature!
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I'm told that
there is no bright future
I'll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Your mission is to take that Ninja Dropout
we caught all the way to the capital.
What's a Ninja Dropout?
It's a gang of thieves consisting
of Rogue Ninja,
who don't consider themselves
Shinobi anymore.
I can't forgive them for using
their Shinobi powers for evil.
So, well, you can figure out
the rest by now.
In other words,
there is a possibility that they will
come to save one of their own.
Exactly.
You are assigned to the mission
of guarding the Gantetsu convoy!
Roger!
Next time:
"The Enemy: Ninja Dropouts