Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, "See you..."
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I'm not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
- Monju.
- Yes, sir.
Darn, didn't know there was a kid here.
I'll do it.
Okay, it's in your hands, Gantetsu.
Okay, Let's pull out!
Set this place on fire!
Don't leave any evidence.
The Enemy. Ninja Dropouts
Wait up!
Over here! You're it. Try catching me!
Darn...
- Yeah!
- This way! This way!
I said wait!
Lady Tsunade...
With regard to the next request...
What, there's more?
Yes.
Boy oh boy...
This is the last one
so please try to focus.
All right.
When the weather continues
to be warm like this...
And what's the request?
About the escort for the convoy with
the fugitive who was secured...
What about it,
that's hardly a difficult mission.
Well, actually there's a bit
of a problem.
Please look at this.
I see. This is somewhat of
a nuisance.
All of the Jonin are out
on S rank missions,
and 90% of the main Chunin and Genin
have been allocated elsewhere.
Who's left?
Let's see... well...
Multi Clone Jutsu!
Let's go, Bushy Brows!
Here goes, Naruto!
Leaf Hurricane!
You jerk!
Another serving of
Shadow Clones for you!
You ain't seen nothing yet!
You let your guard down!
Pretty good, Bushy Brow...
The same to you, Naruto...
Naruto! Lee!
Hey, are you guys all right?
Hey, stop moving.
Sakura, can't you be
a little more gentle?
Shut your mouth.
Really, you're being reckless.
That's not true, Sakura.
See, the 100 man
Shadow Clone grapples
are excellent training
for enhancing one's Taijutsu skills.
It's like killing two birds with
one stone for Naruto, too
because this kind of friendly training
lets him polish
his Shadow Clone skills
at the same time.
That's exactly right.
What are you talking about?
All you're doing is slugging it out.
This is what ends up happening
when two guys get together.
That's right.
Anyway, this isn't the time to be
acting carefree like that.
Lady Tsunade is calling for you.
Grandma Tsunade?
What does she want?
Ninja Dropouts?
Yeah.
Ninja Dropouts are
Rogue Ninja who,
of their own free will,
choose not to be Shinobi and leave
their respective villages to join up.
They're a gang of thieves who use brutal
and villainous means to steal.
That's horrible... using their abilities
as Ninja for criminal purposes.
That's unforgivable.
One of their members was
captured yesterday
in Ogi Pass
in the Land of Forests.
This guy is the only member
whose wanted notice is
circling around the lands.
He was found wandering about
and taken prisoner.
His name is Gantetsu.
For a former Ninja,
that's pretty lame.
Gantesu is being taken to
the capital city of the Land of Forests
in order to do an exhaustive investigation
into this matter
for the purpose of wiping out
the Ninja Dropouts...
However, there is a possibility
that the Ninja Dropouts will try
to rescue him along the way...
A police escort has been sent
from the capital
so it is fully prepared for the convoy.
But since the opponents are ex-Ninja,
the idea is that Shinobi would be
the best countermeasure for Shinobi,
so they requested that the Leaf Village
also send out some Ninja.
That's what this request is all about.
I'm getting excited! I'll show'em
how great Leaf Ninja are!
- Got it!
- Let's give it a shot!
All right! Naruto Uzumaki,
Sakura Haruno, Rock Lee.
The three of you are assigned
to the mission
of guarding the Gantetsu convoy!
- Yes, ma'am!
- Roger!
Look, the harbor.
Huh... So they're gonna
transport him in this.
The only way to get to the capital
of the Land of Forests is
to go up this river.
Hey, look over there.
That's...
The Ninja Dropout, Gantetsu.
Are you the Leaf Ninja?
Yes. Uh, and who are you?
I'm Tsuzumi with the police department.
I'm supervising this convoy.
My name is Naruto Uzumaki.
This guy here's Bushy Brows and
her name is Sakura Haruno.
Hmmm... You guys are still kids...
Are you really Ninja?
We sure are.
Huh, we might not look it,
but we're all full fledged Ninja who've
been tested by fire numerous times.
We'll display our skills for you
at some point.
Just leave it to us.
Well, I have a strong team of
experts handling security,
but if it ever comes to that,
I'm counting on you to use
your specialty, Ninjutsu.
Got it.
Those are the security personnel
guarding the prisoner.
They're all dressed alike, aren't they?
Huh, they don't have much style.
Naruto, that's rude.
Captain Todoroki!
What is it, Commander Tsuzumi?
These people came from
the V illage Hidden in the Leaves
as reinforcements.
The name's Naruto Uzumaki.
I'm Sakura Haruno.
My name is Rock Lee.
Commander, I told you already.
We already have enough security on this.
Can't be helped.
It's something the bosses decided.
There won't be any role for
you guys to play.
We will guard Gantetsu.
I promise that on this sword.
Huh... That sword's nothing.
Snapping that thing in half would be
as easy as apple pie.
Yeah, with just one finger.
Stop it, you guys!
Please excuse them...
Be careful not to get seasick.
Well, I leave it to you.
Y Yes, sir. Thanks.
Gantetsu...
All right...
Put the cage into the belly of the ship!
Okay... Okay...
Okay, lower it!
Wow...
This feels great!
What the heck is this anyway?
They won't let us even get near him.
They're totally treating us like nuisances.
If only those Ninja Dropout guys
would launch an attack,
we could show them how awesome
we are.
Don't say stupid things like that.
The best scenario would be that
the Ninja Dropout won't show up at all.
Our mission is to transport Gantetsu
safely to the capital, you know.
But this is getting too boring...
there's no thrill to it.
Better just grin and bear it.
There are missions like this too.
Well, I sure understand
how you feel, Naruto.
Yeah... I guess this is getting
a little boring.
Dig in...
Gimme a break...
Who do those guys think we are?
But this stuff is pretty good.
Yeah, very tasty.
It makes me so mad...
I mean, why did we go to all
the trouble of coming all this way?
I'm gonna do my mission.
Gonna stand guard over Gantetsu.
But the captain's gonna scold you.
I'm doing this out of Ninja pride!
Uh, Naruto!
Naruto!
He does have the face of
a criminal after all.
Todoroki?
What the heck is he doing here?
Akio...!
Damn!
Father! Mother!
Akio...
Akio!
Damn!
Akio...!
I will avenge your death right now!
Oh!
What the heck are you doing?!
Are you in your right mind?
What was it you were about
to do just now?!
Ninja Art: Crimson Mud.
Oh?
What's the matter, Sakura?
Lee, over there.
That's strange...
I've never knew this river has a tributary.
Why are you in here?
Why does that matter?
What were you about to do to Gantetsu!?
What are you talking about?
It looked to me like
you were going to kill him.
Huh? Me?
That's a stupid thing to say.
It's my mission to guard this guy.
Why would I?!
Yeah, I guess.
Even if he is a criminal,
you can't just kill him off
without interrogating him first.
A brat talking like he knows, huh?
There isn't any need to interrogate him!
This is the guy who did it!
Huh?
This guy...
These guys... slaughtered a lot of people
without mercy...
Even innocent children.
If things continue like this,
we'll be sucked into the tributary...
What should we do?!
Ninja Art: Link and Slay.
What the heck?!
Wh What is this?
Th The ship's been sliced in half...
Naruto!
You jerk!
It's them! The Ninja Dropouts!
So they showed up after all...
Gantetsu...
Reinforcements, huh?!
Hey, who are you guys anyway!
The head of the Ninja Dropouts,
Shura, on the scene!
Ninja Dropouts...
We'll take Gantetsu...
I'm not about to let that happen!
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I'm told that
there is no bright future
I'll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Lee, are you all right?
Yes, somehow.
More importantly, what happened?
I don't know.
Only thing I know is that after
that huge crash,
suddenly the ship was sliced in two...
I see.
Well then, we need to confirm everyone's
safety for the moment...
Well...
What's wrong, Sakura?
I can't find the prisoner, Gantetsu,
Captain Todoroki, and Naruto.
Next time:
"The Bewildering Forest