Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, "See you..."
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I'm not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
Who are you guys?
They want to fight, it seems.
I won't be fooled.
You...you...
Todoroki!
Stop it, Todoroki!
You said you were going to deliver
Gantetsu to the capital, right?
This guy... There's no way
I'll forgive this guy!
What are you talking about?
This guy... killed my family...
he killed my little brother!
Wh What was that...?
Gantetsu killed your family?
Yeah.
Five years ago.
I'm positive that
this is the guy I saw.
Fire!
Oh!
This is horrible...
Is anybody still inside?
Damn!
Father! Mother!
Akio.
Akio!
Memory of Flames
Akio...
Todoroki, I found out who
attacked your family.
Really?
A gang of bandits called
the Ninja Dropouts.
Ninja Dropouts?
They're ruthless...
Evil personified...
When they rob the victims
of money and valuables...
They massacre everyone in that house.
Why?
So as not to leave any witnesses behind.
The bodies of your parents
were found but...
The fire spread quickly and
Akio was still small so...
Probably nothing of him remained.
I'm sorry, but you need to
let your little brother go...
That's impossible.
I can't do that.
Damn it!
It's ironic, isn't it...
When I finally find the killer
of my parents and little brother...
My mission... forces me
to escort him to the capital.
Todoroki.
I'm a full fledged police officer now.
I'm not a spring chicken!
I didn't mean to bring
my personal grudges onto the job...
This guy will eventually
be sentenced to death...
That thought has allowed me to endure.
But, right now,
right in front of my eyes...
The same face in the flame...
The face that killed my little brother!
Your... little brother?!
Die, Gantetsu!
- Don't get in my way!
- Stop!
He's a thug who's killed
countless innocent people.
It's your mission to deliver Gantetsu
to the capital, right?!
It doesn't matter!
He killed my little brother!
It may be true that Gantetsu is evil, but...
You can't do that...
There's nobody watching...
That's right, here in the middle
of this forest.
H-Hey, Todoroki?
Nobody's watching...
There's no way they'll know.
Todoroki... I said, calm down!
I'm telling you, I'm watching!
No, nobody's watching...
Todoroki!
As long as you keep your mouth shut...
No... Better yet, if you w eren't around...
Wait a second!
What the heck are you thinking?
Calm down!
I'm extremely calm.
You too must...
It can't be helped...
If things come to this,
I guess I have no choice but to fight!
What's the matter?
Why don't you just come
right out and fight?!
You guys, too! Why don't you stop hiding?
Come out and show yourselves!
Huh?
Y You guys are...
Stop bullying Gantetsu!
Give Gantetsu back!
What is this?
I have no idea...
Who the heck are they?
Everybody!
W Wait a minute...
How are you connected
to Gantetsu?
Stop that!
Let's get out of here!
Calm down.
We should be able to
understand each other
if we just try to talk things over.
You guys aren't Shinobi, are you?!
It's dangerous for amateurs
to hold blades!
Lee, what are we gonna do?
This is a problem...
'Cause if our opponents are amateurs,
we can't go all out...
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Damn it! Let go of me!
I need to avenge the deaths
of my family... and my little brother!
Calm down!
Calm down and think about
this whole thing ag ain!
Your... little brother?
Don't be stupid, Gantetsu...
Don't come over here right now!
Gantetsu!
What's going on?!
Damn it, I can't move!
It's futile.
That string is stronger than steel.
There's no way you'll be able
to cut through it
with human strength alone.
Who the heck are you?
I'm Monju, a Ninja Dropout.
Ninja Dropout you said?
I, Monju will take Gantetsu.
As long as I have him,
I have no more business with you guys.
Those nets will shrink
as the temperature rises.
So you'll suffer till the end.
In half an hour or so...
It will cut you into pieces.
Farewell!
Todoroki!
Gantetsu!
Damn it... I'm not about to die
in a place like this.
Our mission is to deliver
Gantetsu to the capital...
Are you an idiot?
Take a good look at this situation!
We'll be goners before that happens.
I don't believe that those Ninja Dropouts
are Gantetsu's comrades.
Gantetsu was telling the truth.
Those guys might kill Gantetsu.
That's why I should have killed him
with my own hands!
But remember, that guy was
calling out your name to the very end!
So what's up with that?!
There must be something
he wanted to tell you!
I don't want to hear
any excuses from a thug!
I find it hard to believe that
Gantetsu's that evil a guy.
What was that?!
I'm telling you,
I'm not about to kick the bucket
until I've heard what Gantetsu
wanted to say!
Stop it!
Hey, I'm positive we can work
things out if we just talk.
Shut up!
Wait.
Let's stop this.
I just assumed you were a Ninja Dropout,
because you're a Ninja.
We're Shinobi from the Leaf Village.
We were called here to be
part of the police escort
taking Gantetsu to the capital.
Please spare Gantetsu.
That can't happen.
Gantetsu saved us from
the Ninja Dropouts.
Saved you?
Who in the world are you guys?
We're all kids whose families
were killed by the Ninja Dropouts.
But Gantetsu secretly rescued us
because he wanted to save
at least the children...
What was that?!
Gantetsu took care of all of us kids
who had become orphans...
Gantetsu.
Is it the Ninja Dropouts again?
I'm sorry.
Where am I?
So you woke up.
Mother...? Father...?
Where's Mother?
You poor thing...
But we're all in the same boat.
You're not alone...
We're here for you...
We're your new family.
I'm leaving the Ninja Dropouts!
I can't stand this any longer.
I can't commit robberies with
those guys anymore.
But if you don't,
they'll kill you, Gantetsu.
I'll steal their money.
Huh?
And I'll get myself captured
by the police.
Come on...
If I do that,
they'll show up in front of
the prison to try to get me back.
That's the only way
they can be captured.
Are you saying you're gonna
be a decoy...?
It's so that there won't be
any more victims.
This is my only choice.
Gantetsu really did steal their money
and was captured by the police.
We came to this forest
because we were worried
about Gantetsu's safety.
We were praying that the Ninja Dropouts
would get caught. However...
So Gantetsu reformed himself
and betrayed the Ninja Dropouts, right?
We have to do something about
the real evil, the Ninja Dropouts!
I don't really care about
the Ninja Dropouts right now.
What's important is that
we rescue Gantetsu.
I'm guessing that Gantetsu
is with Naruto.
Don't worry because he won't have
been captured by the Ninja Dropouts.
Okay, let's believe that.
Damn...
If things continue like this,
we'll turn into dried fish.
Huh?
H Hey... It loosens up a little
when sweat soaks into it.
What?
Are you serious?
Oh, you're right.
Yeah, I know...
What?!
I'm used to its venom.
It's nothing.
I find it hard to believe
that Gantetsu's that evil a guy.
I'm gonna meet up with Gantetsu
one more time
and find out for myself,
no matter what it takes...
That's right...
I need to see Gantetsu again, too.
I will then avenge the deaths
of my family... and of my little brother.
We did it!
That was a narrow escape!
All right... Let's hurry up and
rescue Gantetsu!
Yeah... I will find him no matter what
and I'll cut him down!
Huh?
- Gantetsu.
- Huh?
That's definitely Gantetsu.
Those guys are...
I Idiot...
- Gantetsu!
Gantetsu!
That's as far as you'll go, kid.
That guy is...
Don't tell me he's a Ninja Dropout?!
Good answer.
I'm Monju, a Ninja Dropout.
Give Gantetsu back!
I'm not forgiving you for this!
Hey, hey...
Who are these little brats?
Perhaps they're inexperienced
in the ways of the world, but...
to tell me to give Gantetsu back...
Give us back what we want.
That's our line, right?
Who the heck are you guys?
You Ninja Dropout jerks...
We are avenging our families' deaths!
What?!
You brats just stay quiet.
Damn it!
Stop! Monju! Let that kid go!
It looks like you don't quite comprehend
the position you're in right now, huh?!
And moreover, what do they mean
by avenge, huh, Gantetsu?!
Stop!
Ninja Art: Mesh Cage!
It's my turn!
It doesn't even budge.
It's useless... You won't be able to
tear through this net.
Come on, Gantetsu, answer me.
I refuse.
Huh... I see.
Then how about this?
Akio!
Stop it! I get it.
I'll talk, so please stop!
You should have done that
from the start.
These children are the children
from the homes
that we, the Ninja Dropouts, attacked.
I rescued them and gave them shelter.
What? You betrayed us?
I see... You jerk...
You took our treasures and
gave them to these guys.
They belonged to their families
in the first place.
Don't mess around with me...
You traitor!
Stop that!
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Naruto Uzumaki has just arrived!
Naruto!
Naruto, you were safe!
Of course I was!
I'm not handing Gantetsu over
to you no matter what!
Gantetsu.
That's...
It can't be...!
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I'm told that
there is no bright future
I'll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Is that the Ninja Dropout's hideout?
Yes, Akio is probably in that mansion.
Damn those Ninja Dropout bastards.
I can never forgive them.
How dare they interfere with
the happy return of the siblings!
This is outrageous.
All right, let's go, Bushy Brows!
I'm always okay to go.
Even if the enemy is an ex Shinobi...
We're going to beat them one and all,
and definitely going to get
Todoroki's brother back!
Next time: "To Each His Own Path