C'mon!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
Hey, you there.
Identify yourself.
I'm not obliged to answer...
What...?!
Cute...
So those are Kakashi and
Guy's treasured brats...
Well, for the time being,
their applications will pass.
Yeah...
It appears this year's
test takers will be amusing.
For us proctors too, eh...
Now then!
Sasuke, Naruto, let's go!
Don't pull.
Sasuke... Sasuke Uchiha, eh.
Does that kid concern you?
Hmph...
Lee, let's go.
What're you doing?
You guys go on ahead.
I have something I want to check out.
What's that about?
Why should I know?
You, with the unpleasant look.
Wait a minute!
Huh?
- Oh!
- Yikes!
What is it?
Why don't you fight with me
here now?
Chunin Challenge.
Rock Lee vs. Sasuke!
A fight here now...?
Yes.
My name's Rock Lee.
When asking a person their name,
I'm supposed to give
my own name first, right?
Sasuke Uchiha...
Hmph... So you knew?
I want to fight with you!
I want to test out how effective
my techniques will be
against the descendant of the
clan reputed for genius Ninjas.
Also...
Sakura. Love.
Noooo!
Those lower eyelashes are awful!
The hairstyle is awful, too!
Those bushy eyebrows,
just too intense!
Everything is!
You're an angel!
Noooooo!
You are good at it.
Then, how about?
Really... That was super close.
You! Don't throw strange stuff!
I was dodging for my life!
You don't have to resent me that much.
It's Sasuke again!
Darn it! Darn it!
To be honest, you're a naive one,
knowing the name of Uchiha
and challenging me.
Do you want to realize
what this name is, Bushy Brow?
I insist.
I'm lucky...
to be able to have a bout with
the number one rookie right away.
And, I'll prove it to you, Guy Sensei!
Wait!
I AM going to take out
the Bushy Brow. Believe it!
Hey, you!
Big deal.
I'll be able to take care of him
in just five minutes!
The one I want to fight isn't you...
It's Uchiha.
All these people...
keep saying Sasuke, Sasuke.
How annoying!
Darn it!
Leaf Whirlwind!
As I thought, he's strong...
I declare. You are absolutely
no match for me.
Because...
among the Leaf Village Genin,
I'm the strongest now.
He stopped my kick...
What's with that Chakra in his arm...?
Interesting. I'll do it.
Oh...
Stop! Sasuke!
There's less than thirty minutes
until the 3:00 registration.
Don't worry.
It'll be over in five minutes.
Here he comes!
I'm sorry, Guy Sensei.
I may end up breaking the taboo.
I may end up using...
that technique!
Leaf Hurricanes!
I can't get completely out
of the way...
Guard!
What...?!
Sasuke!
W-What's going on?
But...he did guard himself
just now, no mistake.
He got around my guard.
What is it?
Is it Ninjutsu...?
Or is it Genjutsu...?!
As I thought, he's going to get up!
Hmph... That's okay.
If that's the case,
this is a good opportunity
to get used to THAT.
I'll do it.
Huh?! C-Could that be...?
Sharingan!
Sasuke, when has he...
Why is that in his eyes...
And in both eyes...!
Is that the Sharingan?
Sasuke's awesome, after all!
If this is the same Kekkei Genkai
as Kakashi Sensei's...
he can read Bushy Brow's Jutsu!
Genjutsu or Ninjutsu...
It's some kind of magic either way...
I'll reveal that!
It feels like Sasuke's rapidly
getting stronger.
That's to be expected
of the Uchiha clan.
That's right...
Sasuke should not lose to a guy like this.
Huh?!
The Sharingan...!
To not be able to discern the Jutsu
with the Sharingan...
Could it be...that his technique is...!
That's right...
My technique is neither
Ninjutsu nor Genjutsu.
S-Sasuke!
That's right!
My technique is
mere Taijutsu... Sasuke.
You may not be able to
believe it just like that, but...
Punk!
It's said that the Sharingan has
the ability to spot
all Genjutsu, Taijutsu and Ninjutsu.
Make no mistake,
the Sharingan reads Ninjutsu
and Genjutsu that
require the principle of building up
Chakra and weaving Signs,
and can most surely handle such Jutsu.
However, only Taijutsu is
a little bit different...
W-What do you mean?!
Even if you can spot my movements
with the Sharingan,
your body is not equipped with
the speed to respond to my Taijutsu.
In other words, even if you understand
with your eyes,
there's nothing you can do if your
body can't keep up.
Do you know?
There are two types of strong people,
genius types and effort types.
If your Sharingan is
a genius type drawing Uchiha ability...
I'm an effort type who has
patiently mastered only Taijutsu.
In a manner of speaking,
your Sharingan and my ultimate
Taijutsu have the worst compatibility...
Guard!
Huh?! Dancing Leaf Shadow!
And I shall prove it with this technique.
Prove that effort exceeds the genius.
W-What's he going to do...?!
It's my victory!
Huh?! Dancing Leaf Shadow!
And I shall prove it with this technique.
Prove that effort exceeds the genius.
W-What's he going to do...?!
It's my victory!
Huh?!
- Huh?
- Huh?!
That's...!
That's as far as it goes! Lee!
W-What is it...?
What's going on?
Sasuke!
Sasuke was beaten?!
What happened while
I was knocked out?!
Are you okay?! Sasuke.
He's agitated...
To think he couldn't fall properly.
Y-You were watching...?
Lee! That technique just now
is prohibited, you know!
W-What's with that turtle...?
I-I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
He's...getting scolded or something...
Could that be...Bushy Brow's teacher?!
B-But, of course,
I didn't even remotely have
a mind to use the Hidden technique...
There's no mistake!
- Huh?
Hey-hey.
What...?
That thing... It's a turtle, right?
Right?
Isn't it obvious?!
Say! Say! Can even a turtle
become a Ninja teacher?
I don't know!
Fool!
You think such subterfuge will work?!
You should know very well what
it means
for a Shinobi to give away
his technique!
I... I know.
To think I lost to someone so flippant...
Have you prepared yourself?
Y-Yes sir...
All right, if you will, Guy Sensei!
Man! Life treating you good, huh?
Huh?!
Whoaaa! An even more
intense guy has appeared!
Yo, Lee!
Super intense.
The extreme bowl cut...
T-Those are some incredibly
raging brows...
I've never seen anything like that
in my life.
H-Hey! You guys!
Don't mock Guy Sensei!
Shut up!
I'm at a loss for a reaction because
of those bizarre things appearing
one after another!
What?!
Hey, Lee! Drop it!
Yes, sir...
Idiot!
Lee, you... you...
S-Sensei...!
L-Lee...
Sensei... I... I...
Enough, Lee!
Don't say anything!
Sensei!
Lee!
I lost to a guy like that...
Yes... this is adolescence!
Sensei!
That sort of tone's kind of nice, too.
I-Idiot! That's dangerous!
Very dangerous!
It's okay, Lee!
Mistakes come with adolescence.
Don't worry about it!
You're so kind... Sensei!
Now then, take a hundred laps around
the Training Field toward that setting sun!
Yes! Sensei!
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Hey, wait a minute.
We're still in the middle
of the conversation!
What're you going to do
about the Chunin Exam?!
There's no time!
Huh? Oh, that's right...
Lee, you will be punished for attempting
to break the prohibition on top of fighting...
in principle, after
the Chunin Exam.
Okay!
Five hundred howls of adolescence!
Yes, sir!
Idiots...
Say! Say!
By the way, what's with that turtle?
If I'm not mistaken, those kids are...
Kakashi's...
Oh! No, he's looking this way!
You guys... how's Kakashi Sensei?
You know Kakashi...?
I know him all too well.
People call us...
eternal rivals.
Sounds like a lie!
What're you saying?!
Guy Sensei really is...
That's fine.
"Action speaks louder than words"
anyway.
Huh?!
By the way, my record is fifty wins
and forty-nine losses.
Huh?!
This guy...
When did he.?
One thing, I'm stronger than Kakashi...
N-No way...
He's fast! He's faster than Kakashi!
Is he human...?!
How about that?!
Guy Sensei is awesome, isn't he?!
Darn it...
This time around,
Lee caused the trouble.
Out of consideration for my face,
forgive him.
Out of consideration for
this pleasant face.
He's better than that Kakashi...?
Darn it! He's...
not just all talk...
You guys and Lee should probably go
to the classroom pretty soon.
He...!
Then, do your best, Lee!
Farewell!
Yes, sir.
What?!
Sasuke...
I have one last thing to tell you.
I actually came here to
verify my own ability.
I lied before.
The strongest man of the
Leaf Village Genin might be on my team.
I'm entering in order
to defeat that person.
And, you are one of my targets.
Please prepare yourself for the Exam!
Sasuke...
Ha! So...
I guess Uchiha clan's not all that, huh?
Naruto!
Shut up!
I'll knock him flat next time!
Ha! That from someone
who just got whipped.
Hey... what's your problem?!
Naruto, you!
You saw it, didn't you? His hand...
That Bushy Brow probably did a heck
of a lot of special training.
Day after day...
More than you have...
That's all it is.
Sasuke...
Interesting...
Hmph!
It's starting to get interesting...
the Chunin Exam!
What's next?
Yeah!
All right!
Let's go, Naruto! Sakura!
Yeah!
Whoaaaa!
There are tons of people here!
Are they all here to take
the Chunin Exam?
Ino, Shikamaru, Choji, Kiba,
Shino, Hinata and Rock Lee?
So you're all here, too?
Yeah, I'm pumped, pumped, pumped!
Open up your eyes and watch me
become the Hokage!
Next episode:
"Genin Takedown!
All Nine Rookies Face Off!"
As for me,
I'm going to kick butt once again!