C'mon!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
He's late.
Naruto!
Stay still.
Why's it that only
our squad's teacher is late?
The other squads have gone off
somewhere with their new teachers,
and Iruka Sensei's also left.
Don't look at me.
Hey, what're you doing, Naruto?!
Hey!
Lt'll be his fault because he's late.
Man! You're asking for it!
I like stuff like this!
A Jonin wouldn't get caught
in such a weak booby trap.
That's right. You're such an idiot!
I got him, I got him...
I-I'm sorry, sir.
I tried to stop him,
but Naruto did it on his own...
It's all good.
Get real.
Is he really a Jonin?
How can I put this?
As for my first impression
of you guys?
Well, I hate you.
Pass or Fail. Survival Test
Let's see.
First off, let me have
you guys introduce yourselves.
Introduce ourselves...
What should we say?
Your likes, dislikes, your future dream,
hobbies, things like that!
Hey! Before that, please tell us
about yourself.
Me? My name's Kakashi Hatake.
I don't feel like telling you
guys about my likes and dislikes.
I've never really thought
about my future dream...
As for my hobbies, I have many.
In the end,
isn't all we know his name?
Yeah.
Next is you guys.
Let's start with you.
My name's Naruto Uzumaki!
I like instant ramen,
but what I like even more
is the ramen from Ichiraku
that Iruka Sensei treats me to.
What I dislike is the three minutes
after pouring hot water
in the instant ramen.
My hobby is eating and
comparing ramen!
And my future dream...
is to surpass the Hokage!
And so I'm going to get
the entire village
to acknowledge my existence!
I see...
this kid's grown up in
an interesting way.
Okay, next.
I'm Sakura Haruno.
What I like... I mean, who I like is...
And, my hobby is,
I mean...
My future dream is...
And?
What about your dislikes?
Naruto!
Girls at her age are probably
more interested in love
than the Ninja Arts.
And lastly.
My name's... Sasuke Uchiha.
I have lots of dislikes,
but no likes in particular.
Oh...
And...
I don't feel like summing up
my ambition as just a dream
but I do have an ambition!
The ambition to restore my clan
and without fail...
to kill a certain man!
He doesn't...
mean me, does he?
Sure enough, Sasuke's cool.
I knew it...
Good!
The three of you are very distinctive
and interesting!
We'll have a mission tomorrow!
Yes, sir! What kind of mission?
First, we'll do what we can do
with just four people.
What what what?!
A survival exercise.
Survival exercise?
Why are we doing an exercise
even though this is supposed
to be a mission?
We've had more than our share
of exercises in the Academy!
This is no simple exercise.
Then... then what kind of exercise is it?
Hey! What's so funny, Sensei?
Uh, well, if I tell you,
I know you'll grow disenchanted.
What?
Of the twenty seven graduates,
only nine will be recognized
as junior ninjas.
The remaining eighteen will
be sent back to the Academy.
In other words, this exercise
is an extremely difficult test
with a failure rate of 66% or higher!
See, see?
You got disenchanted!
That's crazy!
To have suffered that much!
T-Then, what was
the graduation test for?
Oh, that.
It was just to select those who have
the potential of becoming Genin.
Whaaaat?!
Well, that's the way it is.
I'll be determining whether
you pass or fail.
Bring your complete set
of Ninja tools!
We meet at five in the morning.
N-No way am I going to be
dropped now!
I've got to have my strength
recognized for real.
I'll be separated from Sasuke
if I fail this test.
This is an exercise of love!
Okay! You're dismissed.
Oh... And you'd best skip breakfast.
You'll throw up.
Morning.
Hi, folks. Good morning!
You're late!
Well, a black cat crossed
my path, you see.
Ahem! Oh well...
Okay, it's set for 12:00!
Today's assignment is to take
these bells away from me by noon.
Those who can't do it won't get lunch.
They'll be tied to that...
and I'll eat my lunch
before your very eyes.
So that was the point...
for us not to eat breakfast...
But, hold on.
Why are there only two bells?
There are only two,
so at the very least,
one will have to
go to the logs.
That person will be disqualified
for failing the mission...
and will return to the Academy.
It might be one person
at the very least,
or it could be all three of you.
You can use your Shuriken.
You won't be able to take the bells
unless you come with the intent to kill me.
But, that's dangerous, sir!
Y-Yeah, that's right!
You couldn't even evade
a chalkboard eraser!
In this world,
those who aren't skilled enough
tend to complain more.
Well, just ignore the loser...
Begin when I give
the "ready-go" signal.
Loser, loser, loser.
Don't be so hasty.
I didn't say start, yet.
No way...!
I didn't see him at all.
So this is a Jonin.
But, that's fine.
At least you came with
the intent to kill me.
How can I put this?
I feel like I'm finally starting...
to like you guys.
We're going to start.
Ready... start!
What do you want to know?
I didn't think you just
came here to drink tea.
The Jonin in Naruto and company's
Group Seven...
What kind of teacher is he?
Is he strict?
You mean Kakashi?
Does he concern you?
I heard a rumor that concerns me.
What's this?
It's a pass fail list of
the junior ninjas
Kakashi has been
in charge of up until now.
Let me have a look.
T-This is!
Fundamentally, ninja must mask
their presence and hide.
Okay, everyone is hidden pretty well...
Alright! Let's face off
fair and square!
Oh?
That goof.
Say, aren't you a bit
off kilter?
What's off kilter
is your hairstyle!
I'll teach you the first
Shinobi Battle Jutsu...
Taijutsu.
Taijutsu...?
That's ninja hand to hand combat...
That being said...
he's going to use weapons?
Make Out Paradise
What's the matter?
Why don't you come at me?
But hey... what's with the book?
Why do you ask?
It's because I was curious
about what happens next.
Don't worry.
With you guys as opponents,
it makes no difference
if I'm reading or not.
I'm going to rip you apart!
Damn! This time a spin kick!
Man!
Wha?!
Ninja shouldn't let the enemy take them
from behind multiple times, fool.
The way his hands are positioned...
Is that the Sign of the Tiger?!
No way!
With Naruto as his opponent,
that's too strong a Ninjutsu
no matter how you look at it.
That Sign...
It's a fire style skill.
That idiot teacher's doing more
than just running around?
Naruto, get out of there quick!
You'll die!
Too late.
Leaf Village Secret!
Ultimate Taijutsu!
One Thousand Years of Death!
Oh, it's not a Ninjutsu.
Those two are idiots.
Alright...
Even so, isn't that against the rules?
What're we supposed to do
about his strength?
Damn it!
It wasn't supposed to be
like this.
It... can't be!
This is more than just a rumor.
Kakashi's test might
be a bit difficult...
Even so, this means absolutely
no one has passed!
That's right...
Kakashi has never had someone pass.
They have all...
been annihilated...
What's the matter?
You won't get lunch if you can't
take the bell by noon.
I know that, I say.
You're not very energetic,
considering you said that
you'd surpass the Hokage.
Damn it! Damn it!
I can fight even if I'm hungry.
I didn't even have dinner last night.
I shouldn't have gone on a diet.
I just got a bit careless earlier!
Damn! I'm hungry, so my strength...
But... I've got to take the bell,
no matter what.
No matter what...
I'm... not...
turning back now!
I'm going to become a Ninja!
Security is your greatest enemy!
Now for my favorite
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Seven... Narutos?
What? They're not just images?
Are they all real?
The real thing?
Not the clone,
but the shadow clone, eh.
If you ever lay a hand on Iruka Sensei,
I'll kill you!
Show me what you can do, Demon Fox!
Those aren't just images
but actual clones!
That's an advanced Ninjutsu!
It's the forbidden Jutsu
that did in Mizuki.
Judging from your ability,
that Jutsu should have
a one-minute limit.
Even if you talk trash,
Naruto is Naruto
after all is said and done...
You still can't beat me with that skill.
W-What?! Behind me?!
Ninja shouldn't let
the enemy take them from behind.
Right, Kakashi Sensei?
Using the Shadow Clone,
I had one of them come up
from the bottom of the river
and sneak behind you!
Here's one for that attack
on my butt earlier!
Naruto, not bad!
So... a diversionary tactic, eh?
Now... allow me to punch you!
What?!
The one who got punched was...
Naruto?
Ouch!
You!
You're Kakashi Sensei, right?!
You used the Transformation Jutsu
to change yourself, didn't you?!
It's you!
You're Kakashi Sensei, I say.
You smell like Kakashi Sensei!
The smell of an old guy!
Why you!
Hey! For the time being,
let's try undoing the Jutsu.
If we do that,
only the two will remain... so...
You should've realized that sooner,
you idiot!
You're me, you idiot!
Just undo the Jutsu!
Naruto...
You're embarrassing to watch...
That was the Substitution Jutsu,
you fool.
Essentially, it's a skill used
to quickly switch one's own body
with an object or animal.
This makes your enemy think
you're being attacked,
but then you strike during
their unguarded moment.
After letting himself get caught
by the real Naruto,
the Jonin fool switched bodies
with one of the clone Narutos.
Not only did he make Naruto
think he'd been nailed...
he used Naruto's own attack on him.
A bell?!
You really must have been in a hurry.
You've dropped a bell!
What the heck is this?!
Of course it's a trap...
H-H-Hey!
That jonin doesn't lower his guard
even when he's fighting Naruto.
The bell!
You have to think when using Jutsu.
They can be used against you.
Also...
...don't get caught in
an obvious trap, you fool.
A Ninja must see
through deception!
I know that, I say!
You know, I'm telling you
because you don't get it.
Listen up!
Your movements are wasteful.
Now!
He finally dropped his guard!
You're so...
No way!
You jerk Sasuke!
You're overdoing it!
Damn it!
At this rate, there's no way
I can beat Kakashi Sensei.
But if I don't take the bell...
I won't get lunch...
No... I'll fail the test!
He says a Ninja must see
through deception,
but I have no idea what that means.
How in the world can I take
the bell back
from Kakashi Sensei?!
Next episode:
"You Failed! Kakashi's Final Decision"
Don't miss my outstanding performance!