Press down hard on the gas
That's right, there's no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We're speeding through life,
squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you're not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we'll go far off into the distance.
And the next match.
This year's rookie looks challenging...
Naruto Uzumaki vs. Kiba Inuzuka
It's here, it's here, it's here!
What we've been waiting for!
It's finally my turn!
Yeah! Lucky us!
If it's this guy,
we'll absolutely win, Akamaru!
Show us how much you've grown.
I'm going to do it!
Akamaru Unleashed!
Who's Top Dog Now?
The seventh battle,
Naruto Uzumaki versus Kiba Inuzuka.
I got sick of waiting!
It's finally time for me to shine!
Believe it!
That's my line!
With you as my opponent,
I've as good as won!
Right, Akamaru?
Don't get excited!
You won't be able to beat me!
Why you little...!
Hey! Don't bring your puppy!
He'll get in the way of the match!
You fool!
Akamaru's going to fight with me.
Hey, hey! Is that okay?
Yes.
Animals and insects are treated
the same as ninja tools.
There's no problem.
Well, that's fine!
It's a perfect handicap!
Talking tough!
Then...
Akamaru, don't put a paw in this.
I'll fight him by myself!
Naruto! Don't lose to a guy like this!
It's finally come.
Naruto, huh?
I'm sorry, but he can't beat Kiba...
Kakashi.
Naruto...
I-I want to support you, but...
Kiba's on my team...
Kiba will get mad...
But...
Naruto...
Kiba's lucky.
Hah!
Hah! I don't know how strong he's become
since this guy became a Genin...
Today we'll run through Transformation Jutsu.
You'll change yourself into Lord Hokage...
His ability was "that," so...
Transform!
So noisy...
I was sleeping comfortably...
T-That was a joke!
I-I did it on purpose!
Enough, Naruto!
It's your third year
at the academy!
Wha?
Goodness sake, who is that guy?
We've just switched to this class
and already found someone funny.
That guy, he's on a roll.
He's an attention-seeker, huh?
One more time, fool!
Transform!
You...
Is it possible...?
Hey hey, are you serious?
You've been here for three years and
can't even do a respectable transformation?
All of you watch now!
I will absolutely someday become
the true and a real Hokage!
Lame!
What Hokage?!
Some sympathy at the very least...
I'll do you in, in one clean blow!
Really? But you can't beat me!
I said not to act tough.
Well then. Please begin!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry.
All Four Jutsu!
Here I come!
Fast!
It will be a while'til
he opens his eyes, Mr. Proctor.
Just as I thought.
That Naruto can't be equal to Kiba.
Naruto...
That was too embarrassing to watch.
See...
What was that?
That guy is weak.
Naruto!
Huh?
Yes, that's it...
I'll surpass Hokage!
Then everyone in the village will
acknowledge my existence!
Those are his words...
I've always made fun of them, too.
This is the Jonin...a true Ninja...
I have to escape...
If I stay like this...
I'll really, really be killed!
Are you hurt...
Scaredy cat?
You just need to become
stronger than me!
Damn you!
You!
What are you doing all of a sudden?!
T-This stupid coward is...
absolutely...not the Sasuke I know!
Don't mess with me!
W-What?
But, it was wrong!
Hey...
are you hurt?
Scaredy cat?
I won't change my words,
that's my way of Ninja!
Naruto...
Say it to everyone!
Don't...
underestimate me!
Yeah!
He seems to have grown
to say such thing.
Naruto...!
Go, Naruto!
What are you talking about,
bleeding like that?
Your tough talk has gone too far!
I didn't use my power fully...
to observe your strength first!
You too, cut out the tough talk
and use the dog or whatever you want!
You'll regret this...
Let's go Akamaru!
Smoke Ball?
Take this!
I can't see!
This is bad!
I have to get out of the smoke...
or I'll be done for.
It worked!
What is it...?
Shoot... I can't see anything.
Yeah! We did it!
Yay! Good job, Akama!
A-Akamaru...
Why?
You took the bait!
Y-You!
Transform Jutsu?!
Ouch! Shoot!
Let go!
You smell like a dog!
W-Where's Akamaru?!
Over here!
Akamaru! Damn!
No way!
That's Naruto?!
An equal match with Kiba...
No, it may be more than equal!
Applying Shadow Clone Jutsu
to Transform Jutsu, that's a clever trick.
Naruto shouldn't be able to do that...
His timing at using Jutsu's is very good.
What? He's better than I thought.
But, to get mad like that after
biting the opponent himself...
What a funny guy.
N-Naruto... amazing
That's amazing, Naruto!
You got a little bit stronger.
But it's over.
Next, I'll attack you seriously.
Oh really?!
But you will absolutely not beat me!
During this exam,
he's matured again.
This is a surprise...
That's Naruto, the perpetual goof...?
Evidently it's no longer "that" Naruto.
Yeah.
I wonder, what kind
of trick Kakashi used...?
Still...
Huh?
As for the development of
my Kiba and Akamaru,
it's probably more than Naruto.
Naruto... I'll take Akamaru... back!
W-What's this?!
What did you feed him?
His fur turned red!
That's why he's called "Akamaru", red boy.
Food Pills huh...?
That Kiba...
He intends to end it with this.
Here we go, Akamaru!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry!
Man Beast Clones!
T-There's something wrong
with their eyes!
He's using some weird drug
Isn't this doping?
Is this okay?!
Yes. Food Pills are one of Ninja Tools.
You, that's all you say!
What?!
What did that guy eat?
It's Food Pills.
F-Food Pills?
Food Pills are a secret medicine
that people in the military take
and fight for three days and
three nights without a break...
They're high in protein,
easily absorbed and
have some types of component
that influence agitation or sedation...
Kiba and Akamaru's Chakra must
be doubled right now...
It's over with this...
Let's go!
All Four...
Jutsu!
N-Naruto!
That Naruto is in danger!
Kiba's the gung ho fighter type
who will attack
like a beast with Chakra wired
throughout his body.
And the Food Pills that double one's
Chakra are quite simply...
the perfect pill for Kiba.
Naruto...
This isn't good...
There's no way to counterattack...
All I can do is gather all
the Chakra in my legs
and do my best to escape...!
At this rate...
Here's my chance!
Take this!
Man Beast Taijutsu Ultimate Technique!
Fang Over Fang
This is the difference in
our true powers.
I'm going...
to become the Hokage!
I can't lose here...!
You? Hokage?!
When you're weaker than me?
I'll become Hokage for you!
You know deep down inside
that you can't become the Hokage.
So quit acting tough!
You're wrong, Kiba...
Naruto...
He's not that weak...
I'll receive the name...
of Lord Hokage!
All of you, just watch!
Naruto, unlike me...
he has always believed in his own worth.
I thought it was really amazing...
It must have been really hard...
I understand that.
And yet before not even one person...
tried to see Naruto.
Hey, that's the kid...
I heard he's the only one...
who failed.
Humph! Serves him right!
It's trouble if a kid like that
becomes a Ninja.
After all, that kid is really...
Stop! Anything further is taboo.
Nobody tried to acknowledge
real Naruto.
Clone Jutsu!
But now...
Everyone's watching...
Stand up! Naruto!
Everyone is acknowledging him!
If you compete with me for
the name of Hokage...
You... will be the loser!
Hey, can you hear it?
The clear, blue sky goes on and on
The ocean spans limitlessly
Please keep that smile on your face forever
Or else I'll cry
You won't have to search around you
It's all ok now.
Everyone is inside
this hand
when you want to cry,
and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born, and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia, feel the telepathy
Hey, can you hear it?
That Kiba, he sure is stupid.
Think hard about your Jutsu
when you use them.
Otherwise, your opponents
will take advantage of the Jutsu.
Well, the outcome of you and me
could be seen from the beginning.
The way you've torn me apart
up until now,
I'll give it back all at once!
Next episode: "Surprise Attack!
Naruto's Secret Weapon!"
This is the trick I've been saving up!