Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let's start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only "the beginning,"
I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
Hey! Open up!
Huh?
What's all this noise at this hour?
Idiots! I told you not to let
your eyes off him, didn't I?
Could Gaara have...?
Where on earth did he go?
I hope nothing bad happens, but...
Hospital Beseiged.
The Evil Hand Revealed!
Wow, he's sound asleep...
I wonder if he's dead?
If that's for Sasuke,
he's not back yet.
Hmm.
Ino...
I'm way ahead of you on
Sasuke information.
Missed your chance on that one,
eh, Billboard Brow?
No! This is for Lee!
Huh?
The one from before should
be wilted by now too...
Oh.
Lee! Stop it!
191...
Don't touch me!
I'm...not...done yet...
Here.
Thanks.
I hope Lee's better.
Yeah.
Huh?
What the...?
Oh man, it's all clogged up.
What a drag...
Yo!
You finally woke up, eh?
Where... am I?
In the hospital!
They told me that you've been
sound asleep for 3 days and 3 nights!
Three days...
Three days and three nights?!
W-What?
Shikamaru! When does
the final competition start?
T-Tomorrow.
What?!
Why didn't you wake me
up earlier!
I can't be just snoozing through
in a place like this!
And what about Pervy Sage?
Where's Pervy Sage?!
I've got to have him watch
over my training.
Huh? What are you talking about,
all of a sudden?
I don't know what's got into you.
Huh? My clothes are missing
Where are they?
Where, where?
- Sleeping away like you're in a coma,
- Gone!
- Then running around out of control.
- Where're my clothes?!
Settle down a little!
You know what?
It isn't gonna make a difference
if you rush around
one day beforehand.
Resting is training, too, you know...
Huh? Hey... Naruto.
What in the world
is going on?
I'm... so... hungry...
Don't keep scaring me like that...
Oh yeah.
It's such a drag but...
I bought this fruit basket as
a get well present for Choji.
But the doctor said he couldn't have it.
So let's eat it together.
Choji? Is he that sick?
No, no, don't be fooled.
He got sick from eating
too much BBQ.
That's just like him!
Yeah well, and neither of you are the type
to have female visitors.
So here...
Looks good.
W-What is it?
Since Choji can't have any,
let's eat in front of him.
What a drag this guy is!
Huh?
No one's here.
Out to lunch?
Oh well...
Okay!
Hmm?
Lee, I'm putting the
flowers here, okay?
I'm still hungry!
Are you harassing me, Shikamaru?
Oh yeah.
Why...save him?
He's an important subordinate
whom I care for.
My body... isn't moving.
You jerk!
What the hell do you think
you're doing?!
Hey Naruto...
During Shadow Possession Jutsu,
it's moving me too! Okay?!
Sorry! Shikamaru.
What the hell were you
trying to do?
Choji, are you better?
Oh, Ino!
All right! The age of
the chubby has arrived!
What were you trying to do
to Bushy Brow here?!
I was trying to kill him.
What?!
How can he be so calm?
Especially when he is not able to
move with my Shadow Possession Jutsu...
Why'd you have to do something
like that?
You beat him in the match, right?
Do you have a personal grudge
against him or something?
I don't have anything like that.
I just wanted to kill him, that's it.
How can you say something
so selfish, you bastard?!
You... you had a lousy upbringing,
didn't you?
All you care about is yourself.
Or there's something weird about him.
It gives me the chills!
If he tries anything, it'll be too much
of a burden for me and Naruto...
What the heck should we do?
If you get in my way,
I'll kill you both too.
What?! Go ahead, if you can!
Hey Naruto, hold on!
Should I try to scare him with a bluff?
I know you're strong from seeing you
in the competition with him...
But... we can keep up with you.
We didn't show you our best skills
in the preliminaries.
And it's two against one!
You're the one who's at a disadvantage.
If you're smart, you'll do what
I tell you and just get lost.
I'll say it again...
if you get in my way...
I'll kill you.
Where the heck do you get off...?!
There's no way in hell
I'll let you do that!
I've been telling you
to back off, haven't I?
This guy has the strength of a monster.
You get it, don't you?
I have a real monster in me!
I'm not going to lose to this guy!
Huh?
I heard Naruto was here too,
so I came to see, but...
What a mess...
Well, I guess this means he's okay.
Huh?
What's worth making him mad,
you idiot!
A monster, huh...?
Me too, actually.
It's just like you said.
I had a terrible upbringing.
When I came into this world,
I took the life of the woman
some might call my mother.
So that I could become
the strongest Shinobi...
my father brought his
Ninjutsu upon me,
and so I became possessed
by a Sand Spirit.
I was born a monster.
A Sand Spirit?
It's called Shukaku, the living wraith of
an old monk
from Village Hidden in the Sand
who was sealed inside the tea caldron.
It must be a type of
cacodemon possession Jutsu,
performed to a baby before it is born.
To go that far...
they must have been totally nuts.
Is it possible...that there could be
something inside him too?
What a thing for a parent to be doing!
Such a twisted kind of love.
Love?
Don't measure me by your standards.
Family, huh...
Let me tell you what kind of ties
I have to my family.
They're ties of hatred,
ties of murderous intent...
My family's just lumps of flesh.
Nourished with the life of my mother,
I was crafted as the
ultimate masterpiece of the village...
The Kazekage's child.
I was taught by my father
the innermost secrets of the Shinobi...
spoiled, over protected,
and left on my own.
And I thought that was love...
Until that incident happened.
That incident...?!
What are you talking about?
Just what happened?!
In the six years since the time
when I was 6 years old...
My real father has tried to assassinate me
more times than I can count!
But I thought you just said that
your father spoiled you...
What's going on here?
Those who are too strong are
apt to become feared.
Born through the Jutsu,
my mind was unstable...
I guess the idiots in my village
finally realized that
I had emotional problems...
For my father, Kazekage
at the same time I was
the ultimate weapon for the village
I was also a dangerous,
fearsome presence.
It seems I was labeled a dangerous figure
as soon as I turned six.
And I was treated politely simply because
I was feared.
To them, now I'm just a relic of the past
that they want to see disappear.
So what did I have in this life,
why did I keep living?
When I asked myself that,
I couldn't find the answer.
But, as long as you're alive,
you need a reason...
If you don't have one,
it's just the same as being dead.
What's this guy saying?
I...can understand that...
He...is the same as me.
So this is the answer I came to...
I am living in order to kill
human beings other than myself.
After living in the fear of never knowing
when I might be murdered,
finally I became calm.
By killing assassins, I finally
comprehended the reason why I live...
I live fighting for only myself
and loving myself...
And if I see that all other people
in this world exist
only to make me realize that,
there could be no world
more wonderful.
And as long as there are
others to kill
who can make me feel
this happiness to be alive,
I will never disappear.
W-What's this freak talking about...?
He's real gone!
I was also alone...
And suffered 'cause
I didn't know why I was alive...
But Iruka Sensei recognized me
for who I was...
and that was the first time
I realized why I lived...
But this guy...
this guy grew up alone.
And he ony feels alive
when he kills other people.
H-How can there be someone like this?
The worlds we live in
are too different...!
There's no way...
that I can beat a guy like this!
W-What's wrong, Naruto?
What? Shadow Possession Jutsu should
have stopped him from moving, but...
Naruto!
Naruto! Hey, get yourself together!
What a drag this guy is!
Naruto!
Now, let me feel it...!
Oh no!
Stop right there!
Tomorrow's the final round!
There's no need to rush like this!
Or do you just want to
stay here starting today?
Don't leave me alone!
I'm not bleeding, but
it hurts a lot right here.
What...am I?!
I will... kill you all without a fail.
Just wait.
One! First, Tyson jumps and slamdunks
Two! He kisses and hugs everyone
randomly and says "I LOVE YOU"
Three! Masala masters Yoga
but hates curry
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter. Ole!
All over the world, the sky's smiling,
so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
One! Bodimahattaya san devotes
his time for digging black ships
Two! Peking Duck, Action Scene,
Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
Three! Popo loves to polish his Coteka
Four! Japanese people,
now lend me you hand!
All over the world, the sky's smiling,
so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
All over the world, the sky's smiling,
so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Hey! Konohamaru!
How could this be the ace route?!
I'm already late!
And you're making me later
by taking a longer route to get to the field!
The final competition
will start anytime now.
Darn it!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Run, run, run, run!
Next time, "The Final Rounds:
Rush to the Battle Arena!"
I can't trust your "ace" route at all!