Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let's start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only "the beginning,"
I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
Naruto!
He came in totally late.
Hmm? Where's Sasuke?
The Dosu guy I'm supposed
to fight isn't here, either.
Hey, you guys over there.
Throw out your chests and
show your faces to the spectators!
You guys are the stars
of this "final round"!
Sasuke hasn't been found yet?
A team of several Anbu members
are searching all over,
but they have found nothing.
He might already be in
the hands of Orochimaru...
If that's the case,
we may never find him.
I understand.
Well well... Lord Kazekage.
You must be tired having
come all this way.
No... I'm glad the arena
is in the Leaf Village.
Even though you're still young, it would
probably be a tough journey for you
if you had to go to the trouble
of traveling someplace else.
Shouldn't you decide on
the Fifth Hokage soon?
Please don't treat me
like an old person.
I'm still planning on
being Hokage for another five years...
Now then, I guess it's
about time to begin.
Everyone, thank you very much
for coming
to the Village Hidden in Leaves
Chunin Exam.
We will now begin the
"final round" matches
for the eight who made it
through the preliminaries!
Please watch until the end!
If there are supposed to be eight,
it looks like there's one missing.
I have something to tell
you before the match.
Look at this.
Huh?!
There was a slight change
to the tournament.
Check who you'll be facing
one more time.
Here, I had more preliminary
matches than the others...
So the Dosu guy dropped out?
I thought I'd pound you here...
If I did that,
there'd be the possibility for me,
as the one remaining after
the first battle, to fight Sasuke.
W-What are you?!
Say...
...say.
What?
Umm... Sasuke still hasn't come.
What'll happen?
I wonder if Sasuke really did sneak out
of the hospital room at that time.
Something could've happened to him...
In case a competitor does not arrive
by the start time of his match...
he or she will lose by default!
It doesn't make sense.
Knowing his character,
he'd come even if he had to drag himself.
Where are you going, Gaara?
To verify my existence...
one more time.
One more time.
What's wrong?
You should still be able to move, right?!
Sasuke! Come on!
Could it be...?
Even after I warned him to avoid
doing anything to stand out...
He didn't kill that Sasuke Uchiha
also, did he...?
Listen up, you guys.
The terrain is different,
but the rule is that there are no rules,
the same as
in the preliminaries.
The matches will continue until one
or the other dies, or acknowledges defeat.
However, if I judge that it has been settled,
I'll stop the match there.
Arguments will not be allowed.
Understood?
So the first match is...
Naruto Uzumaki.
Neji Hyuga
Just those two remain and
the rest of you go to the waiting room.
Byakugan vs. Shadow Clone!
Hey, Hinata! These seats are open.
Uh huh.
This match will be quite interesting
Naruto...
Say, Sakura.
I understand that you're worried
about Sasuke.
But why don't you cheer
for Naruto at least a little bit?
Hmm. You're right.
That being said,
with Neji as his opponent,
Naruto has no chance of winning
That is...!
Not so, is what you're
going to say?
But to think that brat would
survive until this point...
I wonder if this is
as far as it goes
for those who survived
just by luck, after all.
That Naruto.
This is not a good opponent at all.
No matter how you look at it,
he can't beat the Hyuga clan.
Well, that's what I thought
at the beginning...
But you'll all be surprised
if you underestimate him.
Akamaru, what's wrong?
What did you say?!
What?! Where?!
There!
What's Anbu, the Black Ops,
doing here?
Is something going on...?
You seem like you want
to say something
I said it before, too, didn't I?
A failure is a failure.
You can't change.
I promise...
I'll win, no matter what!
He has the look...
of being sure of himself...
It's as if he's not all worked up...
That makes it
more worthwhile for me.
I look forward to your look
of disappointment...
when you know the true reality...
Stop whining.
Let's... get started!
Now then, round one.
Begin!
Watch carefully, Hanabi.
Nobody has inherited such
a strong Hyuga Kekkei Genkai.
To say nothing of your older sister.
More than big sister?
Perhaps more than you, too.
This time, it's not an opponent
that can be managed easily.
He has that Byakugan.
Close combat is no good...
Does Naruto know that?
Idiot! Why would anyone
attack from the front?!
No! Naruto.
The opponent can see
your Chakra Points!
They're called Chakra Points.
If those pressure points
are pressed accurately...
the flow of an opponent's Chakra
can be stopped,
amplified or controlled at will.
Uh oh!
I missed, huh...?
In other words, he'll press
the pressure point if I get too close
and I'll become unable
to use Jutsu.
That means all I can do
is fight from a distance.
You understand, right?
You have no way of winning.
Heh... All I did was to verify your power.
The real fight is just getting started!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You used your head,
didn't you, Naruto?!
With the Shadow Clone Jutsu...
Heh. He's an interesting kid.
Shadow Clone Jutsu is
a Jonin level technique.
To think he could use
such a Jutsu...
Who knows how this'll turn out?
Shadow Clone Jutsu?!
I get it. If Chakra is evenly distributed
among the clones,
indeed, I can't detect the
real one even with my Byakugan.
But there's only one real one,
after all!
Heh. Don't be acting tough!
If you're going to come,
then come.
It's pointless.
In front of that Neji's defense,
it's not just all attacking.
Hey!
Don't... you... underestimate...
...me!
Here they come!
He hit!
Fool.
Wha?!
Dang it!
I'll get you next time!
Here!
This guy...
Does he have eyes behind him?
You're going to become...
the Hokage...?
With this level, it's impossible.
I can generally tell
with these eyes...
Intrinsic abilities are set.
Figuratively speaking,
everything inherent about people is set.
Why...?
Why are you always so
judgmental like that?
Then... are you going to say
that anybody can become the Hokage...
if they just work hard?
Only a very small percentage of
Shinobi are chosen to be the Hokage!
Look more at reality!
Those who become the Hokage
are born with a destiny.
It's not something you become
by trying to become it.
It's determined by destiny.
People must live within
their different respective currents
that can't be defied.
The one single...
destiny everyone has equally...
...is death.
Those eyes...
He still holds a grudge
against the head family, huh?
So...
So what?!
I don't know when to give up!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
One! First, Tyson jumps and slamdunks
Two! He kisses and hugs everyone
randomly and says "I LOVE YOU"
Three! Masala masters Yoga
but hates curry
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter. Ole!
All over the world, the sky's smiling,
so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
One! Bodimahattaya san devotes
his time for digging black ships
Two! Peking Duck, Action Scene,
Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
Three! Popo loves to polish his Coteka
Four! Japanese people,
now lend me you hand!
All over the world, the sky's smiling,
so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
All over the world, the sky's smiling,
so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Darn it! What is going on?!
It was clear that my punch got him,
but I'm the one who was thrown!
Darn it!
Even though I promised Hinata...
I really cannot lose at
a place like this!
The next hit will be the big one
that I'm gonna give him!
Just prepare for it!
Next time, "Ultimate Defense:
Zero Blind Spot!"
I hardly give up things!