Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let's start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only "the beginning,"
I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
- Start the operation!
Zero Hour!
The Destruction of
the Hidden Leaf Village Begins!
Lord Hokage!
Leave it to me!
Lord Kazekage!
What is going on?
Lord Hokage!
Gaara!
Squad One, above.
Squad Two, below!
Protect the lords!
You're in the way!
Lord Hokage...
Please... flee...
It's finally our time to
come on the scene.
We've been transformed
such a long time.
I'm totally pent up with frustration.
You guys smell all sweaty!
Come on, we're all comrades, right...?
Sound Ninja...!
Raido...
We're heading out to
back up Lord Hokage.
Be careful of any traps!
Do it...
Yes sir!
- Ninja Art!
- Four Flames Formation!
Barrier!
Lord Kazekage...
Barrier Ninjutsu, huh?!
To think that they could outwit Anbu...
They're not just ordinary...
What are you doing here?!
Lord Hokage is in danger!
What a nuisance...
To think that the enemy was
masquerading as our Anbu...
So it was also that guy
who used Genjutsu!
Yeah... there's no mistake.
I didn't expect that...
Sand Village would betray Leaf Village.
The treaty is simply a camouflage to
make the enemy let down their guard.
The petty little battle game ends now.
From this point on, the course
of history will change!
Are you saying that
you're starting a war?
That's right.
One should avoid resolution
through armed force
and should rather seek
a solution through negotiations.
There's still time... Lord Kazekage!
Perhaps one gets addicted to
peace as one grows older...
Sarutobi Sensei!
You're...
Just my bad luck...
to have lookout duty
on a day like this.
I wanted to watch Chunin Exam too.
Stop fussing.
The Chunin Exam takes
place twice a year.
You'll have many more chances
to see it.
But this year, that kid from
the Uchiha Clan is taking part, right?
And I won't have
a chance to see that...
I won't be able to die peacefully.
What's that?!
It's time! Begin!
The Summoning has succeeded.
Huge boa!
Notify Lord Hokage immediately!
I'm not letting you in the village!
Dispatch the reinforcements immediately!
Yes sir!
Sand Ninja!
What's going on?
Stop that, Gaara!
I'll kill him...!
There's no meaning in
continuing this fight!
Don't forget our mission!
Out of my way...!
What are you guys doing?!
The operation is already underway!
What in the world is going on?
Gaara!
What's the matter?!
His wound is deeper than
I thought!
And moreover his Chakra
is pretty drained!
In that case,
what about using that thing...?
That's impossible to do right away!
Idiot! It's all because
you didn't wait for the signal
and tried to become
the Perfect Possession...
What should we do?!
Are you saying we have to do
this without Gaara?
Isn't Gaara here yet?!
Gaara is Sand's trump card.
We have to get Gaara to do his work,
no matter what!
You guys leave for the moment and
tend to Gaara's wounds!
As soon as Gaara's Chakra has
been restored...
the operation will recommence!
Got it!
What about you, Sensei?!
I'm gonna suppress those guys!
Do you think things will
go according to your plan?
I'll make them so...
Go!
Okay!
Is Orochimaru the host of this party?
Dunno... In any case,
let's heat this thing up.
Sasuke...
Sorry, but the Chunin Exam ends here.
You've already achieved Chunin level.
If you're a Leaf Shinobi,
be of service to the Leaf!
In other words, I'm supposed to
take down that jerk Gaara, right?
A continuation of earlier on, right?
Don't pursue too far.
From here on, it's no longer an exam.
It's the real thing!
What I have to do though...
is the same!
I won't let him through!
Sasuke...!
Boy oh boy...
We intended to take Sasuke
while Gaara was causing the trouble.
But not everything goes as planned.
I see... Is that so?
So Leaf Village and...
Sasuke were the target, huh?
Is the Leaf such a big catch?
More importantly,
if Gaara wakes up,
I'll be able to show you something
much more interesting.
Well, anyway...
Your thick-headedness has caused
the Leaf to be outmaneuvered.
It's my win.
Nothing is decided
until the very end.
I believe that's what I taught you...
Orochimaru.
I thought this day would
eventually arrive.
However...
You won't get my head that easily!
I told you, didn't I?
It is preferable to decide
the Fifth Hokage quickly...
Third Hokage...
because you will... die here.
I wonder how the Chunin Exams
are going?
I wonder if Naruto's match is over yet?
The first match was
with Neji, right?
I want him to win that
match somehow or other.
That's no good!
A teacher mustn't root for
one particular student!
All the graduating students
are dear to him!
I must root for all of them equally!
But I still...want Naruto to win...
Are you worried about Naruto?
Well, of course...!
As I thought...
Y-You guys...
I told you to do ten laps around
the school grounds, didn't I?!
We finished that long ago.
While you were daydreaming, Sensei.
When our teacher is in that state,
he can't teach a class!
So let's call it quits for today!
N-No, no!
I'm continuing with class.
I wonder what that smoke is...?
That's coming from the direction
of the exam arena...
Isn't there some disturbance
to the east?
I wonder if something happened?
That Orochimaru...
What should we do?
Should we send reinforcements?
No... It's dangerous to make a move
when we don't really know
what the situation is.
If the mastermind is Orochimaru...
even more so.
Is Orochimaru...
that dangerous a guy?
Originally... he was a student
of the Third Hokage.
So why did he become a Rogue Ninja?
Long ago, when the Fourth Hokage
was decided...
Orochimaru apparently asserted that
he was capable of taking on that role.
But his request was denied.
And shortly afterwards,
that guy slipped out of this village
Orochimaru most likely holds
a grudge against
the Third Hokage because of that.
Revenge... is it?
Probably.
Long ago, when I was a kid...
there's one thing I remember
thinking when I saw that guy...
That he didn't seem human...
That he seems to be something
that just took on a human form...
Frightening...
Simply... frightening.
Reporting
A large boa has appeared near
the eastern gate of the Leaf Village!
And behind it, some one hundred
Sand Ninja are infiltrating the country!
They are currently engaged in
armed conflict with our Shinobi
who were patrolling nearby!
The Sand...?!
Leave Squad One and Two behind
and make for the eastern gate.
Immediately!
- Yes sir!
We won't let you past this point!
There's quite a large number.
We were careless!
And even Lord Hokage has been...
Kakashi! Look inside the Barrier!
Yeah.
What...?
Orochimaru!
Orochimaru?!
Why is that guy...?
Don't tell me that
they're after Sasuke again?!
Sasuke!
Huh?
He's not there...?
Sakura, stay there for a while.
I'm gonna go reduce
the number of enemies.
Darn! I'm worried about
Lord Hokage, but...
Leave above to Anbu.
Besides...
Lord Hokage isn't the kind of guy
who can be taken down that easily.
But...
After all, he is the Hokage
the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
Are you so happy, you're crying?
Or...
do you have an iota of sadness
in your heart to kill me, your teacher?
No...
Since earlier on, I was feeling so sleepy...
but I'm finally awake.
That's what I thought.
I know you aren't someone
who would hold a grudge.
You have neither a goal nor motive.
Hmm... I guess...
I do kind of have a goal.
If I were to explain it...
It's interesting to watch things
that move.
I get no pleasure if
something doesn't move.
Like a windmill that doesn't turn...
Well, it may have some kind
of appeal once in a while.
But usually,
it's not worth looking at it.
Right now... with a wind called
"Destroy the Leaf Village
I want to turn that windmill.
You're the same as always...
Sakura!
It was worth teaching you Genjutsu
survival training
during the Genin Exam.
You truly have a talent for it.
Huh?
Release the Genjutsu and
wake up Naruto and Shikamaru!
Naruto will be delighted.
He'll be getting a mission
after such a long while.
What do you mean by a mission?
Be careful...
It's the first A ranked mission
since the Land of the Waves.
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Yes, breathe in the air
Lift your face to the sky and jump
If it rains, take a break
Go where the wind takes you
So many regrets
Don't let this scar be for naught
Let's go carve the badges in our chest
Yes, it's Show Time, life begins now.
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Transform sadness into the wind
and continue to forge on
Forge on strong
Yes! I've been waiting for this!
Finally, it's the first A Ranked mission
in a while!
Listen, Sakura and Shikamaru!
As long as I'm with you,
it will be an easy one.
I'm the super hero who
can wake a sleeping lion.
Just keep watching
Mr. Naruto's stellar performance!
Next time: "Village in Distress:
A New A Ranked Mission!"
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go