Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let's start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only "the beginning,"
I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
Uh oh!
Pakkun?
Sakura?
Why did you stop
all of a sudden?!
The scents of Sasuke and the other two...
are quickly moving away!
It smells like Sasuke is
chasing those two people...
What?!
Sasuke is?
There are no other signs
of movement.
But...
Let's not just stand around.
Let's go after Sasuke right away!
But... what?
The people who are left are going
to fight each other.
We'll end up taking a little longer way...
but all there is for us to do
is to avoid it.
Why?! If we do that, it'll only delay our
catching up to Sasuke.
Let's just speed on through!
What are you saying, Naruto?!
We don't know what'll happen
in the battle zone!
Even if we don't desire it,
there's a possibility that
we'll be irrepressibly caught up in a battle.
That doesn't have anything
to do with it!
Kid! Our mission is to bring
Sasuke back.
So the cardinal rule is to avoid battle
as much as possible until then!
- Let's go!
- Got it!
Fine!
Puppet Master Jutsu!
I'm from the Aburame Clan
of the Leaf Village...
When we fight,
we never underestimate our opponent,
no matter what puny insects
they may be.
I'll advance with full force!
Bring it!
Put me down, Temari.
Can you move, Gaara?
Gaara!
Kankuro is delaying Uchiha now.
We must use this opening...
If we don't get a move on,
the operation will...
Huh?!
Temari, go over there.
What?
Just beat it! You're in the way!
Astonishing Truth!
Gaara's Identity Emerges!
Poison on the blade!
I won't let you get away!
That's... Sasuke Uchiha!
Did he get past Kankuro?!
No... No matter how you look at it,
it's too soon.
Did another assailant come?
I don't know what you Sand Ninja
are scheming...
but I'll stop you!
And...
I'll ascertain your true identity!
Gaara!
Don't tell me...!
Is he going to rouse that thing
in a place like this?!
This is no joke...
It's out of my hands.
Stop, Gaara!
Have you forgotten the operation?!
You who are strong...
You who are called Uchiha...
You who have friends...
You who have a purpose...
You who are like... me!
By killing you...
I will exist in this world as
the one who destroyed all of that...
I can truly experience "life."
What is it?
It's so obvious if you release
such a blood thirsty aura...
Come on out.
So it's you, eh...
What's your purpose?
Why do you seek power?
It's none of your business.
Beat it!
You're a hindrance to my training.
You...
have the same eyes as I do.
Eyes that seek power,
brimming with hate and murderous intent.
You're like me.
Don't forget... You're my...
You're...
my...
You're... my...
my prey!
It's started...!
A Substitution?!
You're naive.
All right!
Insects?!
To think you'd make
a clone out of insects and
wrap around behind me...
Not bad!
Your reach encompasses from medium
to long distance and you use a puppet.
I didn't think you would
do well in close combat.
With that Puppet Master Jutsu
where you have to concentrate
on the control of the puppet...
the one casting the Jutsu is
prone to openings in defense.
You're very aware of the weakness
of a puppet master!
However, from here on,
I'll show you the essence of
this Ninjutsu fighting style!
The real terror of Crow...
my puppet of warfare!
This is Poison Smoke Bomb!
Did I inhale...a little bit?
I get it...
And the caster of the Jutsu hides, eh?
Listen, everyone...
Even if enemy Shinobi appear,
don't panic.
Go into the hidden room quickly.
Your Jonin and Chunin Senseis
will protect you all with their lives!
Oh!
Konohamaru...
It'll be okay!
Everyone's doing their best.
They can drive away
the enemies right away.
Cracks in the face rock
of the Hokage Lords...
How ominous...
Grandpa...
To have come this far...
To have come this far...!
Do I already lack the power
to drag out his soul?
With this feeble body...
even though I'm prepared to die,
is it not enough...?!
You probably could've killed me
if you'd been ten years younger.
Sarutobi! If you don't kill him now,
the village is doomed!
Do you understand?!
I... understand!
Useless... old man...
Now... Let me feel it!
That eye!
That eye...from before!
This doesn't look like it'll end
by the time you come for back up...
Shino...
It looks like the poison has
slowly started to circulate.
I'll finish this!
Insects, again?!
But he shouldn't be able to
move so much in that state...
I'll make things easier for you...
Hey! What's wrong?!
What's happening...?
Don't tell me...!
It's futile...
He can't move anymore...
I had the beetles burrow
into every joint...
He stuffed beetles into its joints
so that the puppet can't move?
That was his aim from the beginning!
The beetles are passing through
the threads of my Chakra...
Why...?
That's it!
As I recall, their food is Chakra.
At this rate,
my location will be found out!
He cut the Chakra threads himself...?
You got careless!
Instantly reattaching the Chakra threads
that have once been cut
is simple for a first rate puppet master.
And...
Crow is a puppet...
that has a weapon in each
and every component of the body!
It's a big mistake if you think
this has ended...
by your stopping my movements!
There's lots of poison
on the tip of the needle...
Die!
What?!
Just like that, the insects...!
The Chakra threads have been
bitten through!
What?! Why...?!
Where did these insects
spring out from?!
By beating away the bait insects
along the Chakra threads,
you dropped your guard.
You didn't notice...
the wriggling insects behind you.
The insects were moving
the whole time...
heading for your headband.
W-What did you say?!
The one blow earlier...
I pretended to miss and
stuck one of those beetles on you.
But how did you know where I was
with one such beetle?
I... hate explaining the same thing twice.
Shino?
Why are you here?!
I put a female beetle on you
before you left the arena!
The females have almost no smell...
Only a male can sniff out
the subtle smell of the female.
Then, this one beetle on my forehead...
Right... It's a female.
The poison has circulated
through my whole body, huh...
It looks like I won't be able
to go to back you up...
I'm sorry, Sasuke Uchiha.
Is he a... monster?
Are you scared of me, Sasuke Uchiha?!
Of my existence?!
Come out...
Sasuke Uchiha!
You're... my...
prey!
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Yes, breathe in the air
Lift your face to the sky and jump
If it rains, take a break
Go where the wind takes you
So many regrets
Don't let this scar be for naught
Let's go carve the badges in our chest
Yes, it's Show Time, life begins now.
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Transform sadness into the wind
and continue to forge on
Forge on strong
What a speed and strength!
If I didn't use my Sharingan
to foresee his movement,
I would have been in pieces!
But a merely defensive battle
will do no good.
What do I do?
How should I stop him?
Do I need to use that?
But Chidori may not...
Next time: "Sasuke's Decision:
Pushed to the Edge!"