Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let's start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only "the beginning,"
I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
Assassin of the Moonlit Night
T-This guy...
Sasuke!
So we were too late...
Those guys...
Sa... Sakura...?
You guys...
T-This...
He probably fought recklessly...
like that time!
Sasuke!
Kakashi Sensei said there was nothing
to worry about with the bruise!
So tell me... Sakura...
Sakura!
What do you want?!
This guy... Who is he?!
His outward appearance
is different, but...
he's that guy called Gaara.
When I came into this world, I took the life
of the woman some might call my mother.
So that I could become
the strongest Shinobi...
my father brought his Ninjutsu upon me,
and so I became possessed
by a Sand Spirit.
I was born a monster.
So that's what he was saying...
He's the one who hurt Sasuke...
Hey young girl!
I want you to know that
I'm not the fighting type!
I can see that by looking at you!
In any case,
I need to get away from here
and somehow take Sasuke to
where Kakashi Sensei is!
You...
Sasuke...!
Well! Your limit is two shots...
That's about it...
The third shot won't be activated...
Remember this well.
If you try to force a Jutsu to activate...
not only will the Jutsu
not properly activate,
but your Chakra will deplete to zero...
and in the worst case, you'll die!
Even if you were to survive,
absolutely nothing good will come of it.
Especially in your case...
Is it the Curse Mark...?
If you let your hatred take over you,
and rely on the power
of the Curse Mark...
your development will stop there.
If that happens, you won't
be able to beat Itachi.
In any case,
I need to get control over this.
Sasuke!
I see you're...
the one I failed to kill that time.
I live fighting for only myself
and loving myself...
And as long as there are others to kill...
I will never disappear.
L-Let's run! Everyone!
Die! Sasuke Uchiha!
Sakura!
Out of the way!
How could she stand
in the way of that Gaara...?
Darn! Darn!
What the heck should we do?!
Just with him, I don't want to...
Now, let me feel it!
Why...?
Gaara, Please calm down.
It's no use after all...
The sand gets in the way.
Gaara...
Yashamaru!
I may not look it,
but Lord Kazekage charged me
to look after your physical condition
as a member of medical corps
and to be with you.
Please do not do such things
in front of me.
Although the sand will protect you...
Yashamaru... I'm sorry...
Oh, this.? It's just a scrape.
A scrape...
Is it painful?
A little bit... But it'll heal in no time.
Hey Yashamaru...
What is it?
What is pain?
I've... never once had a wound so...
I wondered what it's like...
Well...
How can I explain it?
It's like it's distressing, or difficult...
In other words, to be hit or cut...
Maybe I should say it's a feeling
of not being able to bear it,
of not being able to stay normal...
I can't say it well,
but I suppose it means a situation
that's not very good.
Yashamaru...
Yes?
So, do you dislike me... Yashamaru?
People live their lives while
hurting others and while being hurt.
But it's not so easy for
people to dislike others.
Thank you, Yashamaru.
I think I sort of understand
what pain is now.
I see...
So... maybe I'm injured too?
The same as everyone?
I'm always... in pain.
I'm not bleeding, but...
I've been having a lot of
pain around... here.
Blood does flow from a wound
on the body
and the wound may appear painful.
But as time passes, the pain
naturally disappears.
By using medicine,
the healing is even faster.
But what's dangerous is
a wound of the heart.
Nothing has more trouble healing
A wound of the heart?
A wound on the body and
a wound of the heart are slightly different.
Unlike a wound on the body,
there is no ointment and sometimes,
it doesn't heal for one's entire life.
But there is one thing that
can cure a wound of the heart.
However, this is a complicated medicine.
It can only be given to you
by another person.
What? What must I do to...?
The thing that can cure
a wound of the heart.
That is...
Iove.
Love?
Yes.
H-How can I get it?
What do I need to do for this pain to be...?
It has already been given to you, Gaara.
Huh?
Love is... a heart that desires to serve
a precious person who is close to oneself,
to love and watch over that person,
just like my older sister did.
I believe that my older sister
loved you, Gaara.
Sand Spirit Shukaku is a spirit of a living
person used for the purpose of attacks.
The sand which automatically tries to
protect you is like the love of a mother.
I believe that sand is filled
with your mother's will.
My sister... probably wanted to
protect you even more after dying...
Yashamaru...
What is it?
Thanks for what you did earlier...
for stopping me.
You are welcome.
You are a precious person
who is near me, Gaara!
Can you understand... my pain?
It tastes like iron...
Twenty!
Twenty one!
Leaf... Hurricane!
How many did you take
down Kakashi?
Twenty two.
Huh, it seems I win again!
That was my twenty third.
Yeah, yeah all right...
That poser attitude of yours
still makes you cool!
That's the reason you are my rival!
- Let's go!
- All right!
Hey, Yashamaru...
I have a favor to ask!
What is it?
I want some ointment.
Sorry about earlier...
It must've hurt.
This is medicine.
If you want it
Go home... freak!
Oh, what the?!
Hey, be careful, you brat...
Y-You are...
- Again...
- Go home, freak!
These eyes...
Y-You are...
Why...? Why?!
H-Hey!
What the? What's going on?
It's... it's Gaara!
Hey! This guy's dead.
Father...
As I thought... Things don't go well...
Why is it...that only I'm such a freak?!
What...am I?!
The thing that can cure
a wound of the heart is love.
Yashamaru!
Huh?
Why? Why me...?
Why always me?!
Who...? Why...?
Well done... Gaara.
Yashamaru...!
It's those eyes...
What's the matter?
Weren't you gonna run away?
Sasuke...
Naruto...
What are these two... to you?!
T-These two are... my friends!
Try laying so much as
another finger on them!
I'll clobber you!
So... what's the matter?!
Weren't you gonna clobber me?
Hurry up and come at me...
Darn it!
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Yes, breathe in the air
Lift your face to the sky and jump
If it rains, take a break
Go where the wind takes you
So many regrets
Don't let this scar be for naught
Let's go carve the badges in our chest
Yes, it's Show Time, life begins now.
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Transform sadness into the wind
and continue to forge on
Forge on strong
I know this guy's strength.
I may seem like a senseless
weakling to him.
But... what's?
What's this feeling welling up inside me?
I don't know...
I don't know,
but I just don't want to lose to this guy!
Next time: "Light vs. Dark:
The Two Faces of Gaara"