We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road
filled with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes and
take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose,
so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh!
Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
For a start, wake up
that medium kid.
It will release that Jutsu!
How do we go about waking him?!
Give him a good punch!
But with that said...
I'm not particularly good
at transformations...
Huh?
So you will act as my will
and make the Sign!
Time for a combined transformation!
We got to have fangs and claws!
Let's go!
Transform!
Beyond the Limit of Darkness and Light
F-Fox?
What a battle...
I can't call this place safe either, huh...
Darn it!
His power is increasing
more and more!
Chief! We got to hurry up and rouse
that guy out of his sleep!
I know that!
Here goes...!
Go to hell!
All right! Now!
Okay!
Wake the hell up!
You jerk...
All right!
Not that much time has passed
since the medium went to sleep!
In that state,
one blow should be enough!
Darn!
It hasn't been long since I emerged!
The Jutsu has been dissolved!
Even if the Playing Possum Jutsu
is dissolved,
he's still putting on the pressure?
That guy interfered with my Jutsu...?!
Sand Coffin!
- Pop!
- Yeah!
It's the chief's tongue...
Don't take me for a fool!
Darn!
What kind of strength
does this guy possess?
This doesn't look good...!
Both Naruto and I have already
completely disgorged our Chakra!
You will be killed by me!
I will not cease to exist!
Leaf Hurricanes!
Besides just the Sound Ninja,
I wouldn't have imagined that
this many of the Sand Jonin
would enter into the village, too!
Well, it's understandable.
This is what is called war.
It's taking much too long.
It's impossible for a battle
between Shinobi to last this long.
What the heck is happening inside?
You're still grabbing my arm...
I can't use my Jutsu this way...
Come on,
let go of me once and for all.
I'm not letting your ambitions
interfere with the village... any longer...
There's no stopping my ambitions!
You will die here!
You old dotard...
As the Third Hokage,
are you saying you still have
the power to save this village?
Do you understand...
the current situation?!
Many Hidden Sand Shinobi and
my subordinates
have infiltrated this village.
Your side... the Leaf Shinobi...
will be annihilated down to
every last woman and child!
I will accomplish the destruction
of the Hidden Leaf Village!
It's empty inside!
There's nobody there!
That's very strange...
Huh?
Why is there so little resistance
when we've closed in
all the way to the center
of the Hidden Leaf Village?
That's...
And also... there's not one woman
or child in sight.
What is the reason for that?
Huh?!
Konohamaru?
What's the matter, Konohamaru?
I gotta use the toilet.
M-Me too...
I do too...
K-Konohamaru...!
This is an emergency situation!
If the enemy finds us,
it will cost us!
Go back to the other room
and stay quiet!
I-It's not that... I gotta pee!
Hold it!
I don't think I can hold it...
Gimme a break.
In that case, come along with me...
Can't hold it!
Can't! Can't hold...!
That's...
At last, huh...
I'll get revenge for you
no matter what...
Hayate.
That's the signal. Let's go!
Roger!
You don't get it, do you, Orochimaru?
Don't underestimate the Shinobi
of this Village!
Are you all right?
Yeah...
Is that... the last?
Yes, the evacuation is complete!
W-What's happening?
The Village Hidden in the Leaves
has an instruction manual
outlining what to do in case of
a sneak attack by the enemy.
Step One:
Eliminate the enemy's sneak attack force.
In case one is unable
to eliminate them,
proceed immediately to Step Two.
The immediate evacuation
of noncombatants!
Evacuate the women and children
to shelters around the village!
When that has been completed,
proceed to Step Three!
Step Three...?
Through the collective strength
and efforts of the Village,
eliminate the enemy!
In that case...!
The counteroffensive... starts now!
We will not allow you to take
even one step beyond this point!
Sakura!
Rescue Sakura,
if it's the last thing you do!
I'll protect Sakura no matter what!
You will be killed by me.
I will not cease to exist.
My back is against the wall...
I have to hurry up
and stop that Demon Raccoon...
Please...
Just a small amount is fine...
Give me...
some Chakra!
What are you doing...?
There's only one opponent!
Hyuga is the magnum force
of the Leaf Village.
Don't forget that!
M-My... body... is immobilized...
Is this the first time
you're experiencing
the Leaf's hidden technique,
Shadow Paralysis Jutsu?
Well, take this too while I'm at it...
The Leaf's hidden technique...
Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
Expansion Jutsu!
Mind Destruction Jutsu!
W-What's this?!
My body is... all on its own...!
S-Stop...
Stop!
Reminds me of the old days!
Yeah!
The original Ino Shika Cho Trio reunites!
Kuromaru... let's go
Right!
In order to protect the village,
all the Leaf Shinobi will risk
their lives fighting
Real strength doesn't lie
in the mastering of all Jutsu!
The poison in my body is...
Don't move, Shino.
I inserted my Parasitic Insects.
They are removing the poison.
Dad...
I believe I taught this
to you too, in the past...
It is when one protects
someone important...
that the true strength of
the Shinobi will emerge!
I will protect everyone!
Here I come! You idiot raccoon!
Die...!
Darn...
Darn it!
D-Did he win?
A simple head blow...
His manner of fighting
is incredibly clumsy,
but to think that he could squeeze out
Chakra at that critical stage.
I've never seen a knucklehead Ninja
like him before, but...
he sure is the first phenomenal kid
I've seen in a long time.
It's too bad that I can't see this through
to the end,
but I've reached my limit.
Gamakichi, let's head home!
Okay! Pop!
As might be expected, even I...
am empty now...
You are too, aren't you?
We're much alike...
let's make this time the last!
It appears that...
I don't have the strength left
to yank out your entire soul.
However, your ambition ends here!
Not yet!
There's no stopping my ambition!
I have a suitable punishment for you
who have become addicted to the Jutsu
and who have overindulged in the Jutsu!
I will take all your Jutsu away with me!
What did you say?!
There!
Don't tell me that?
Stop that!
Seal!
My... My arms...
Now... you can no longer use
either of your arms.
And since you can't use your arms,
you can't weave Signs.
You no longer possess Ninjutsu!
Your ambition of crushing
the Hidden Leaf... dies right here!
You old dotard!
Give me back my arms!
Orochimaru, you fool...
It's unfortunate that
we can't leave together,
but, my disciple...
let's meet in the other world one day.
You old dotard...
whose life is hanging by a thread!
How dare you!
How dare you take away my Jutsu!
In places where the Leaf dances,
a fire burns...
The shadow of the fire
will illuminate the Village...
And once more the Leaf will sprout...
A cycle of hardship, right?
Inside, we were crying, right?
But the one thing we won't give up
is the dream we've chosen, right?
It's a secondary role,
a role in the shadows
But in reaching for that dream,
let us stay centered,
let us stay true
Over and over,
we hung on without giving up
we kept coming back up
Over and over,
we believed and dreamed
we've seen fools
Over and over,
we've stood in the shadows of others
Now, it's our turn...
Let us bask in our dreams
Lord Third Hokage...
The ambition that you had
seems to have been passed on
to the young Shinobi
in the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
The flame in their hearts will
burn large and strong in the future.
And someday,
they will illuminate this Village...
just as you have done for us!
Next time:
"The Third Hokage, Forever..."