We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road
filled with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes and
take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose,
so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh!
Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
Sasuke...?
No... Who is he?
He's got the same Sharingan
as Sasuke.
Really...
who'd believe a kid like you to
have the Nine Tailed Fox in him.
Why does that guy know
about the Nine Tailed Fox?!
Naruto, you will come with us.
Roar, Chidori!
Howl, Sasuke!
That guy is...close by!
That guy!
Elder Brother...
Today...
when school's over,
help me train for a Shuriken Jutsu...
I'm busy... Have father teach you.
But you're better at Shuriken Jutsu,
Elder Brother...
Even I can see that.
You always treat me
like a pest, Elder Brother.
Ouch!
Forgive me Sasuke...
Some other time, okay?
I don't have time to
pay attention to you today.
You're always jabbing my forehead
and saying "Forgive me, Sasuke."
You also say "not today,"
but there's never a day.
Father.
Huh?
Why doesn't Elder Brother
pay any attention to me?
That guy's a little strange...
He's the type that doesn't really like
to become intimate with people.
Why?
I don't know.
I am his father and
still I can't read that boy...
Here!
Your boxed lunch, Sasuke!
If you're worried about doing
Shuriken Jutsu practice,
I will watch you when you get home.
They're not practices,
they're training
See you later!
Sasuke, are you on
your way to school?
Yes.
I saw Itachi earlier on.
He's really become a man.
He's already a top-notch Shinobi.
He graduated at the head of his class
at the Academy at the age of seven,
and attained Chunin level
at the age of ten, didn't he?
He became adept at using
Sharingan at the age of eight.
Yes, I remember.
That boy is truly
the pride of the Uchiha clan.
By the way,
how old are you now, Sasuke?
I'm the same age as
when Elder Brother graduated,
but I can't...
What's the matter?
Hey!
Stop talking nonsense!
Oh my, dear.
Sasuke, both you and Itachi
come from the same Uchiha clan,
the pedigree of
the Hidden Leaf Village
Have confidence!
You'll be an amazing
Shinobi just like Itachi one day.
Yeah!
See you later!
Do your best!
Study hard!
That's right...
I come from the same Uchiha clan
as Elder Brother...
I won't lose to Elder Brother!
I'm pretty late...
What was that?
I had the feeling
there was someone there...
The lights are out.
Even though it's not time for bed...
What's this?!
W-What's this?!
What in the world is this?!
Uncle... Auntie...
Father... Mother...!
Father? Mother?
Aren't you here?
There's somebody here!
Move!
Father! Mother!
Elder Brother!
Father and Mother are...!
Why? For what reason?!
Who in the world would do
something like this...?
Elder Brother... What are you?
What are you doing
Elder Brother!
Foolish little brother...
Mangekyo Sharingan!
My legs...!
Stop!
Elder Brother!
Don't make me see this!
Why...?
Why did you, Elder Brother...?!
No!
No...
Auntie! Uncle!
Father! Mother!
Stop it! Elder Brother!
Don't kill Father and Mother!
W-Why...
Why did you...? Elder Brother...?
To measure my abilities...
Measure your abilities...?
Just for that?
Are you saying that...
Just for that...
you killed them all?
That is of great importance.
What do you mean...?
Don't talk rubbish!
I'm scared...
I'm scared!
Don't kill me...!
D-Don't kill me!
You are not even worth killing...
Foolish little brother...
If you want to kill me, begrudge me!
Hate me!
And keep on surviving in
that unsightly manner...
Just continue fleeing and fleeing
and hang onto your life!
Shall we go outside...?
These guys aren't just anybody...
Itachi, it'll be a pain in the neck
if this kid moves around and...
Maybe I better chop off
a leg just in case...
W-What did he say?!
Now then...
Long time no see...
Sasuke.
Uchiha Itachi!
Uchiha... Itachi?
The same as Sasuke...
An Uchiha...
Huh... Sharingan...
And moreover,
he resembles you a lot...
Who the heck is he?
He's my younger brother.
But I heard that the entire Uchiha clan
had been murdered.
By you.
Itachi Uchiha... I will kill you!
I must kill one certain man
without fail!
That man...
My elder brother...
I thought I couldn't die...
without killing him, but...
That's the guy that Sasuke
was saying...
The man he wanted to kill...
It's just as you said...
I held a grudge against you
and hated you.
For the singular purpose of
killing you, I...
I...
have lived my life!
Sasuke...!
Chidori...?
I will kill you!
Die!
W-What's going on?!
I can't believe that Sasuke's Jutsu
was so easily thwarted...
This doesn't look good!
I've got to do something!
Chakra permeates the air...
I see...
So this is the Nine Tailed Fox Chakra!
You jerk!
You're in the way!
Sasuke!
Darn it!
Ninja Art. Summo...
You're too slow!
Huh...? I can't feel the Chakra...
Darn! Darn! Why is it?!
My sword Shark Skin
has the ability to...
cut through and eat Chakra!
It's a pain in the butt
if the kid moves around
and uses Jutsu like that...
Before these legs...
Should I chop off these arms?
Why doesn't it emerge?!
It's pointless...
What?
You guys just don't know me much,
do you?
This man Jiraiya does not fall victim
to any woman's allurement,
but rather his forte is
winning women's affection!
I'm not made to blindly follow after
a woman's feminine charm!
When you get to my level,
women yelp with delight
at my sex appeal!
A cycle of hardship, right?
Inside, we were crying, right?
But the one thing we won't give up
is the dream we've chosen, right?
It's a secondary role,
a role in the shadows
But in reaching for that dream,
let us stay centered,
let us stay true
Over and over,
we hung on without giving up
we kept coming back up
Over and over,
we believed and dreamed
we've seen fools
Over and over,
we've stood in the shadows of others
Now, it's our turn...
Let us bask in our dreams
Watch out, Sasuke!
Naruto, don't help him.
But... Sasuke is!
It is your duty to watch
through this battle, Naruto.
What?!
This is his fight...
This represents everything that
he has been carrying up to now.
Next time: "Hate Among the Uchihas:
The Last of the Clan!"