We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road
filled with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes and
take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose,
so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh!
Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
A hot spring?
Yeah, just off of this road
there's a nice town with a hot spring.
Yunosato Hot Springs...
They say it does a world of good
for fatigue and beauty.
Aren't we going straight home?
Everyone's waiting
Naruto's right.
Our hometown is in
a state of emergency,
there's no time to procrastinate.
It won't make much difference
if we're one or two days late...
It's really popular with girls,
and it's mixed bathing...
Hey?! Pervy Sage!?
Sometimes it's necessary for humans
to take breathers.
We'll take one bath!
That's not what you said before!
It's okay. Well, let's go!
That's her, no mistake.
We've finally... found her.
Kidnapped!
Naruto's Hot Spring Adventure!
We have the pleasure of
a visit from four people and one piglet.
- Welcome!
Even though this has mixed bathing...
I'm all alone with this brat.
I'm so unlucky.
Well then, shall we play pachinko
or something?
We have plenty of time before dinner.
You're not going to the hot spring?
If we go right now, there are fools...
So, let's go, let's go.
I'm going to get out already.
Not yet, not yet.
Not until the girls get here.
Oh, I see...
Well, c'mon girls.
All of you, come on...
Welcome!
Ah, that was refreshing.
W-We've been robbed!
The necklace I got from
Old Lady Tsunade is gone!
Where! Where is it?!
"If you want your necklace back,
give back the money"?
"Will wait at the three cedars on
the mountain behind."
Signed, the Akagi Family.
Money?
What are they talking about?
Girls came in, all right.
But...
they're all female monkeys!
I want to bathe with people.
Hey, here I am!
Come out! Akagi Family!
What do you want, kid?!
That's my line!
I haven't borrowed any money
from you people!
So give me my necklace back!
"My" necklace?
Did we mistake his stuff
for that woman's?
Ah, that's it!
Give it back!
W-Wait!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Go!
You thieves!
- Take this!
- Go!
H-Help...
People came, all right...
But...
They're all men!
- Bring it on!
- Cheers!
I want to bathe with women...
Huh? So the one who borrowed money
is Old Lady Tsunade?
Yes... nicknamed
the Legendary Sitting Duck.
She played at the Akagi gambling den
until she was penniless.
We loaned her what she lost.
That's right, and there's an I.O.U.
Wha?! There are so many zeros!
I'm Senta, this guy is called Bunzo.
The boss ordered us to collect
on the debt three years ago...
We set out on a journey
from Akagi Mountain
prepared not to return
until we get the money back.
We've heard rumors about
the lady here and there...
But, she sure was something
She was elusive and quite hard to find.
Then recently, we caught
some information that she'd appeared.
We were waiting on
the side of the road...
That's when we came along
with Old Lady Tsunade.
But why did you raid the room
so stealthily?
Rumor has it that
that ordinary means don't work
against the Legendary Sitting Duck.
We didn't think that
if we tried to collect amicably,
she would pay us.
She's certainly stingy...
We heard that she cherished the necklace
next to her life,
so we thought she'd pay
in exchange for it.
No way. After all, you raided my room.
We never even dreamed that the owner
of the necklace would have changed...
Err... Can't you ask the lady to pay?
Uh, even you say so...
Please! If we don't get the money back,
we can't go home!
Our wives and kids are waiting for us
to come home!
- Please... I'm begging you!
It's all gone...
Bad luck...
Darn it. I'm stone broke.
Well, let's call it quits with pachinko.
It's about time for a bath...
- Shizune...
- Yes?
My bag is at the front desk of the inn.
What?!
Y-You can't mean to bring it here?!
Everything to your name is in it...
I've just lost! I can't repress this feeling!
Just bring it without complaint.
Yes, ma'am!
Huh? Could you be...
Y-You are...!
There are women, all right...
But...
I was hoping for younger,
more titillating women...
This one, right?
Thank you...
Are you with Ms. Tsunade?
Yes.
This came for her not long ago...
To Tsunade
A letter? I wonder who could've...?
Lady Tsunade! Lady Tsunade!
Lady Tsunade!
Huh? Lady Tsunade!
She's not here...
Okay, Tonton...
You know to search for
Lady Tsunade, right!
What, impossible? Why?
I see! The smell of the sulfur
from the hot spring interferes...
Well then, the only way
to search for her is on foot!
Lady Tsunade!
Lady Tsunade! Lady Tsunade!
Where are you!
We have a problem!
Lady Tsunade!
Oh, what in the world should I do?
We have Naruto Uzumaki.
If you want him returned unharmed,
please return all of the money you owe!
We'll wait by the three cedars on
the mountain behind. The Akagi Family
What should I do?
I have to help Naruto.
On top of that, if it's discovered
that Lady Tsunade has a huge debt,
talk of her installment as
the Fifth Hokage will probably end.
That's right, we have
to handle this by ourselves.
Right, Tonton?
Do you think it's going to work out well?
No problem.
Here she comes.
Old Lady Tsunade!
Stop!
You know who we are, right?
You're the henchmen of the Akagi.
Then I'll make it brief.
Pay back your debt
in one lump sum.
Or else...
his life is over!
Help me!
Whatever.
His life doesn't matter much to me.
- Huh!
- What did you just say?!
Well then, the money...
Why did it come to this?
This isn't titillating
this is just tight!
Drats! Let me have patience!
Didn't you hear me?
It doesn't matter to me
what happens with his life.
You... darn old hag!
Was what I would have said,
until just a little bit ago, I think.
Once I become the Hokage,
he'd be a precious subordinate.
I can't leave him in the mess.
Old Lady Tsunade...
Right now, this is all I've got.
Take it.
Let me make sure of this.
I don't mean it's paid off in full,
but that'll do it for the interest, right?
Fake!
You're not going to pay
the money back?
It's none of your business.
These guys can't go home!
Don't you feel sorry for them!
You couldn't possibly?
In that case, I'll have to use force
to get it back!
Naruto's Shadow Clones?!
I see, Naruto has joined hands
with the Akagi Family...
So, where did Naruto and company go?
As expected...
I didn't think she'd hand
the money over meekly.
But to be that much of a coward...
What should we do?
Old Lady Tsunade has a huge suitcase.
No doubt there's money in it.
We have to do something
to get our hands on that suitcase.
Shoot!
I'm supposed to be kidnapped,
and she's casually drinking sake.
It's that suitcase.
How do we get it out?
Leave it to me.
Lady Tsunade, you've returned.
Ah, here's the suitcase.
It's dangerous,
so let's leave it at the front desk.
Well then...
Look, I went and got it!
- You did it!
Old Lady Tsunade!
Shoot... If you're the Hokage...
If you're the Hokage,
then pay your debt back
like a Hokage would!
A Hokage is meant
to protect everyone!
These guys can't return their home,
they are desperate!
Why don't you do something?!
Naruto...
Or do people from other countries
not matter to you?
That kind of Hokage...
I cannot accept!
Now!
Here!
Hurry up and run away!
- Right!
- Okay!
Oh, she's already catching up!
It's all or nothing!
Huh?
- You did it!
Tonton?!
Naruto!
Just hand over the suitcase! Or else!
F-Fork over the suitcase!
If we take a direct hit from
Old Lady Tsunade's attack,
then it's over!
Out of the way, out of the way!
Purse snatchers?
Excuse us!
Hey what's going on?!
Hey! Don't cause trouble
for the general public!
It's because you're following us!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
What's going on...?
Naruto, we leave it up to you.
This is no good.
If the contents of that suitcase
become known,
it will be a disaster...
That's right, that happened too.
And I was young then too.
Gulp it down.
Excuse me, Boss.
What is it? You're in front of a guest.
W-Well...
A clone!
That's a clone too?
Wrong again.
Sheesh, which is the real one?!
The rest...
- Where are the rest?!
Over there!
- Hold it!
- Naruto!
- Wait!
Prepare yourself!
Shoot, let me go! Let me go!
Settle down!
G-Got it!
The money!
Okay, they got it!
IOU's?!
It's not money?!
- Oh no...
- This is too much!
What are you doing?!
This is in the middle of town!
Huh!
T-Two Old Ladies?!
You're mixed up in
this commotion as well?
I'd like to hear your reason
for it, Shizune!
Hello... Lady Tsunade...
What?! Shizune...
And you guys belong to the Akagi.
B-Boss Jirocho!
Who?
You don't know?!
He's the number one gang boss,
Jirocho from the Land of Tea!
He's an old friend of mine.
As luck would have it,
we met by accident on the street.
You're Bunzo and Senta
if I'm not mistaken.
Just in time.
I have something to say to you!
- What?!
You mean the debt to the Akagi Family?
I paid it back a year ago.
Is that true?
That was last year,
when we were near Akagi's.
Did you forget?
I-I'm sorry.
Hey!
It's a circular from Akagi
addressed to me.
I'll just read the part addressed to you.
"Senta and Bunzo,
"The debt is paid, come home soon."
Signed, Shugoro Akagi.
See?
You've gotta be kidding.
All that energy spent, for nothing.
- Thank you for helping us.
- Now we can go home relieved.
Go in good spirits.
- You too, Naruto. Take care!
Hey, if the suitcase
doesn't have money in it,
why were you so serious
about getting it back?
That's...
If the IOU's were discovered
by the people in the village,
they'll oppose Lady Tsunade's
installment as Hokage
You worry too much.
The Hokage and the debt
are unrelated.
Not only that,
she said she returned the money,
so there's nothing to worry about.
At least the Akagi debt was...
What?
Don't worry, don't worry!
What? We forgot something?
Finally, the time has come.
Communal bathing with girls...
Patience paid off...
I believe your promise,
its a true heart give me courage
Always I feel it
the precious time with you
On your still shoulder
I feel the wind that blows
towards tomorrow
The city lights are like pieces of stars
That hold us together
"Each one of us glows differently,"
you say laughingly
but you look most dazzling
Like a comet,
like the rainbow after the storm
You bring light into my heart
Being lost can be the answer
Let's promise we won't cheat
Uh...like a shooting star,
we do go ahead.
You're awesome,
Old Lady Tsunade!
Kakashi Sensei and Sasuke
are all right now!
You can't rejoice yet.
The current situation
in the village is serious.
You're right.
I have to do my best,
And work hard for
the village as well.
Hey! N-Naruto,
where do you think you're going?!
I have to fill my stomach first!
You have no sense of emergency...
Next time: "Tsunade's Warning
Ninja No More!"
What is that supposed to mean?!