Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
Two Heartbeats.
Kabuto's Trap
Huh?!
It can't be!
Even if you put up a bluff
I can foresee...
that you are already... finished.
Poor thing.
This child is trembling
like a puppy
Now, Kabuto...
Get rid of her,
but don't make her suffer.
I understand.
Sasuke...
I I'll do anything for you!
So I'm begging you...
Please stay here!
You are really annoying.
Please don't go!
Sakura...
Thank you...
Sasuke...
Wait!
Hmm?
Did you... say something?
Wait!
Where's Sasuke!
Where is Sasuke?
It couldn't be that...
your body is already Sasuke's...?
There's no need to keep it
a secret any longer.
It's all right, Kabuto,
go on and tell her.
He was a little late
in getting here.
Lord Orochimaru wasn't able to
wait for Sasuke,
and already had been reincarnated
into another vessel.
So Sasuke is all right?!
Somewhere in this building...
Lord Orochimaru gave Sasuke
the Curse Mark,
so he could wait for
the next opportunity to reincarnate.
But...
Not all humans can
tolerate Curse Marks.
No way, there's no way
that Sasuke could be...
That's right, Sasuke wasn't able
to tolerate the Curse Mark
and so he died.
That's a lie.
It has to be a lie!
What would telling a lie
like that accomplish?
To someone that's going to die...
As you are?
If you want to see him that badly
I'll let you see him.
When you die, you can see him
in the other world.
Sasuke...
Sakura!
Sakura, don't you believe...
what a guy like him says!
Naruto!
So it's Naruto, I thought you'd drowned
and died a long time ago but...
When I make a promise
I don't give up.
That's my Way of Ninja!
I ain't gonna die,
until I get Sasuke back!
This is interesting!
Sakura, go hide!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I'm over here!
Hey stupid, over here!
Over here, over here!
Where're you looking?
I'm over here! Over here!
What're you doing? Hey!
So you've used up all
your Kunai Knives...
I'm gonna... completely blow you away!
How annoying!
Fire Style.
Misty Flames Dance Jutsu!
- Ouch!
- That's hot!
- Yikes!
- Oww!
You're too slow!
Rasengan!
Naruto!
Since you and Orochimaru are here,
it means Sasuke is probably here too!
Tell us the truth right now!
Wh What the heck?
My body won't move...
Have a good look at yourself.
Wh What's this?
Those are Chakra Threads.
Chakra Threads?
While you were attacking earlier,
I wrapped the thread around you.
Take a good look at where
that thread is connected.
That's right.
Those Chakra Threads are...
connected to my heart's
Chakra Network.
And Naruto, the thread that's
wrapped around you
is connected through my Chakra Network
to your organs and to your heart.
See, can you hear that?
My heart and your heart will
eventually become connected as one!
- Damn!
- Naruto!
It's no use. That thread is formulated
and spun with Chakra
and it will absolutely not break.
Now our hearts are
completely synchronized...
The Chakra which passes
through this thread
via the Chakra Network from my heart
is controlling your heart, you see.
It's no use, even though
it's my heart...
If my heart beat gets faster,
your heart will get faster too...
And when my heart stops beating...
you will die too!
Don't! If you stop your heart,
you'll die too!
That's right.
But that doesn't mean much.
Since I've already promised
my body to Lord Orochimaru...
Wh What the heck are
you gonna do?!
If I crush this heart...
you will die too!
Now, together we will...
Naruto!
How's it feel to have
your heart seized?
It'll be all right...
You'll be out of your misery
right away!
Stop it!
How foolish, if you kill me
Naruto will die too.
What I'm gonna cut...
is this!
There's no use you know,
It's impossible to cut thread formulated
and made from Chakra.
Even Lady Tsunade's great strength
wouldn't be able to break it.
What should I...
What should I do?!
Naruto is suffering right
in front of my eyes and yet...
I can't do anything!
Sakura...!
I... absolutely will not lose!
Until I've fulfilled my promise!
You bravado ends there.
Now, shall we die together?
And go to the place where
Sasuke is waiting?
Naruto!
Sakura!
- Sasame?!
- Sakura...
Stick this tag on a Kunai Knife!
Naruto!
Naruto?!
Hey, are you okay? Naruto!
No way...
It can't be...
No way!
Naruto!
Ahh... My chest right now
is beating with joy.
Idiot! It was a waste for me
to have worried!
Sorry, Sakura...
You're so worthless!
That's right, Sasame!
Why are you here?
Well, it's...
I was saved by Sasame,
you know.
Me too.
What do you mean?
Water came rushing into that
trap pit we were in earlier...
That's it! The lid to the pit!
Damn!
When the water reached
the ceiling,
I desperately tried to open the lid,
but wasn't able to escape...
I was told by Master Jiraiya
to go to where Hanzaki is.
But I got concerned about Arashi,
so I came...
Naruto!
Hey! Thanks!
Th The frog spoke...!
Well, come to think of it,
there's no way you could open the lid
of the trap by pushing on it.
Geez!
But how come the thread that
I couldn't cut with the Kunai Knife,
be cut when I wrapped it
with Sasame's tag?
Because the Chakra Thread
is a Secret Technique
within the secrets of
our Fuuma Ninja Technique...
Of the Fuuma?!
Oh I see...
So who the heck is this?!
Oh!
She is... from earlier!
Mistress Kagero...
She's a Fuuma Jonin.
Sasame!
Sasame...
I was resurrected
by Lord Orochimaru...
You! You're being tricked
by Orochimaru!
Where is Sasuke?
And Arashi?
Where's Sasame's cousin!
Lord Orochimaru is...
going to raise our Fuuma clan...
to the center stage
of Shinobi again.
You're still talking about
that stuff?!
At least tell Sasame the truth!
So it's there! He's in there!
Sasame and Arashi...
You two were so close...
Then it'd be better
if you didn't see him.
Mistress Kagero...
What do you want to do, Sasame?
Do you want to wait here?
I will see him!
No matter what's in store for me!
I came all the way here
to see Arashi!
Yeah! You've got guts!
All right! Let's go together!
Yeah! Let's go!
Sasame...
There might be some sort of trap...
Leave it to me!
Orochimaru?!
Good of you to come, Sasame...
Why...?
Arashi...!
Arashi!
Arashi?
I'm no longer...
Arashi...
Wh What the heck is going on?!
The skills and bodies of the Fuuma Jonin
were combined into one...
and I've been reborn as
the ultimate Ninja you see...
Now, I'll show you
my ultimate Ninjutsu... Sasame!
No... Arashi...
Damn, Orochimaru!
I will not forgive him,
no matter what!
When I recalled the parts one by one,
I felt as though
I had understood everything
Faded words which I kept so close to me
Speechless nights, a hint of warmth,
and
and this distant yearning for you
I live, simply repeating this cycle
Held in my two hands
A droplet of time
Softly clutching forgotten memories
Lost words
I'll keep these thoughts...
Sorry... I'm sorry, Naruto.
I haven't been able to do anything,
after all.
I'm always dragging you down.
I hadn't changed at all.
But Naruto, Sasame,
you two taught me.
That's why I want to change
the kind of person I am!
This time, this time,
it's my turn to give it my all!
Next time, "Sakura's Determination!"