Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
Sakura's Determination
Where's Sasuke!
Where did you put him?!
Heh! You're Naruto, right?
You wouldn't believe anything
I said anyway, would you...?
That's right! I won't believe
that Sasuke's dead!
Naruto...
That's right. Sasuke is alive.
I'll bring Sasuke back!
I made that promise!
Naruto...
In that case, take me down!
If I were the wimp I was in the past,
I would probably have
told you the truth.
Arashi!
No! The old Arashi is dead!
The person you see here
is just a block of flesh
kept alive by
Ninja Art: Cadaver Puppets!
Sakura, please look after Sasame!
Stop it, Naruto! Don't fight with Arashi!
No!
This guy isn't the same gentle Arashi
you once knew, Sasame!
Jigumo! Go!
No!
Sasame! I'm sorry!
Over here!
Naruto!
Don't, Sakura!
Kamikiri...!
Finish him!
Naruto!
You're... next...!
Sakura!
That was close...
I almost let my guard down.
Just when you had a chance
to launch a sneak attack.
You blew it, didn't you, Naruto?
Naruto!
All because of that ball and chain...!
Ball and chain?!
Naruto... I'm sorry!
That's not true at all!
This kind of injury...
is nothing... at all!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
If there's three on your side,
I'll go with five on mine!
Kamikiri!
Naruto!
Are you all right?!
You're badly hurt...
Sakura... This injury is nothing!
"Sakura... This injury is nothing!"
Stop it! If you say more than that...!
I won't say more! I'll bring this to an end.
Kamikiri! Jigumo!
Give me your Chakra...
Boar, Dog, Rat,
Rat, Snake, Rooster, Dog,
Dog, Monkey, Dragon,
Boar, Boar, Rat, Boar, Dragon...
Why does Arashi know that technique?
It's a Hidden Jutsu that only the past chiefs
of the Fuma clan could use...
What was that?!
Fuma Ninja Art:
Spell of the Mandala!
This ain't good!
Naruto!
What the heck is this?!
This is the end!
What?!
Naruto!
The Chakra cage gradually shrinks...
And the human enclosed therein
is crushed to the size of a tiny nugget.
You can't break it.
As long as I myself do not
dissolve the Jutsu.
Naruto!
I'm incapable of doing anything...
There's nothing I'm capable of doing...
The person I am now isn't...
capable of doing anything!
Arashi!
Sasame...
You!
Sasame!
Please... come to your senses...
Become the old Arashi again!
I told you, already!
The old Arashi is dead.
Arashi...
I'm sorry, Sasame...
I wanted power...
I wanted the Fuma Clan to find
a place in the sun once again...
Yes! I understand that!
I understand that!
But, enough now...
Let's go home.
Let's go back to the village.
But, I'm just a mere monster now...
That's not true!
This is agony...
Sassme...
Please... kill me...
Please... kill...
How dare you try to kill me!
Arashi!
You'II... die!
Sakura!
Sakura?!
You wanna be... the first to die?
Sasame taught me that...
dying isn't anything to be scared of!
I see...
But what's scary is to live one's life
without having been able to do anything...
I'm not afraid to die in the service
of someone who is important to me!
Don't!
I'm telling you...
Whatever happens, you mustn't die...
No matter what! Sakura!
Naruto!
Give it up!
What is it you think you're capable
of doing the way you are now?!
That's so useless!
Vanish from this world
get crushed into nothing...!
Sasame!
Stop that, Arashi!
Sasame... you!
Naruto!
Hey! Let go!
No!
Arashi?!
I'm sorry, Sasame...
I caused you so much hardship...
No, you haven't!
The person who experienced
the greatest hardship is you, Arashi!
Is there anything I can do for you?
What should I do for you?!
You've already helped me
more than enough...
See... Thanks to you, Sasame,
I was able to return to being
the person I was in the past...
Naruto!
Sakura...
Even if it's to be of service
to someone...
There's no life that
should be lost for that!
Yeah!
Run! Sakura!
Pervy Sage!
Sorry to be late!
I was faced with a number of obstacles
on my end too!
Gimme a break...
Now then...
Climb on, climb on!
Hurry! Let's get back above ground!
Oops!
Sasame!
She's fine... She just fainted.
Naruto!
Orochimaru assigned us a mission...
To make sure nobody takes Sasuke back
to the Village Hidden in
the Leaves under any circumstances!
Then, Sasuke is...?!
Yeah... He's alive!
Orochimaru had to protect Sasuke
because he is his vital vessel which
he will possess in three years!
Arashi...
Arashi... This place is gonna collapse!
Hurry up and come over here!
I'm already just a puppet...
I cannot live my life anywhere
except here.
Arashi...
All right!
No! Arashi!
Sasame...
Thank you.
Including Arashi,
we've paid an extraordinary price but...
The Fuma Clan has been
able to cut itself free
from Orochimaru's spell...
You can start again anew.
I will rebuild the Clan again without fail!
With this life...
that Arashi protected.
Yeah!
I am truly indebted to you.
Sasame...
Hanzaki, I'm leaving these two
in your hands!
Yes, sir!
Please take care along the road!
I will.
- Thank you!
- We thank you!
- Take care!
- See you again!
Hey! Hang in there!
Well, we weren't able
to find Sasuke,
but at least we now know
that he's alive somewhere...
We'll have to settle for the fact
that we were able to ascertain
the new information that we still have
a grace period of three years
before he becomes a vessel
to be possessed by Orochimaru.
Yes...
Sasame knew what she needed
to do for her clan...
But this time again all I did was cry.
All I did was depend on Naruto...
Sakura!
You gave your best effort too!
No, I was just a ball and chain
to everyone...
I wasn't capable of doing
anything alone...
That's not true!
Seeing you give your best effort
like that gave me a lot of courage, Sakura.
If you hadn't been there, Sakura,
I'd have been crushed just like that.
It's thanks to you, Sakura!
Naruto...
Wow, you've grown into someone
who can say that sort of thing!
Oww! I'm an injured man!
Treat me with a little more care!
Oh yeah, that's right!
All I was thinking about at that time
was protecting someone I cared about...
What I'm capable of
doing right now...
I was thinking...
What?
There are many variables such
as mission level,
or platoon's member structure...
But no matter how small
a platoon might be,
I think it's important to assign
one Medical Ninja to it...
I know that already...
I wrote exactly the same thing
in a report long ago
regarding the survival rate and mission
achievement rate of small platoons.
But it's not that easy to
nurture Medical Ninja.
They require a different set of skills
than that of fighting types Ninja...
The minute perfection
of Chakra control,
the ability to assimilate a huge volume
of specialized knowledge,
the brains to apply that in a broad way...
patience...
And there is the most important thing
for Shinobi who are to develop
into a Medical Ninja...
Well, I'm busy right now, so...
The most important thing... huh?
Hidden Leaf Hospital
I'm all wrapped up in bandages again...
This way I can't even
hold chopsticks...
Sakura, when it's time for
my meal, feed me, okay?
I'll open up my mouth just like this and...
Huh? Sakura?
I'm sorry! I was just joking!
I'm sorry... Naruto...
Huh?
This is gonna mean that
I'll keep you waiting a little but...
Nex. T time, I definitely won't...
be a ball and chain to you!
Huh?
Enter!
I came here with a request!
What is it?
Please make me your apprentice!
You're very desperate, aren't you?
Sakura Haruno,
I heard from Kakashi that you have
a brilliant mind as well as will power!
All right.
But in exchange,
I'm not gonna be easy on you!
Yes, ma'am!
This recent mission...
Iooks like it wasn't wasted
on her, after all.
When I recalled the parts one by one,
I felt as though
I had understood everything
Faded words which I kept so close to me
Speechless nights, a hint of warmth,
and this distant yearning for you
I live, simply repeating this cycle
Held in my two hands
A droplet of time
Softly clutching forgotten memories
Lost words
I'll keep these thoughts...
He makes me so angry,
that Pervy Sage!
Didn't he say " I'll make you
my disciple and hone your skills"?!
When Sakura's already become
the Old Lady Tsunade's
and is working so hard!
And he just leaves me to
my own devices! Hey!
All because he was assigned
a mission by Old Lady Tsunade!
If things come to this,
I'm gonna give the Old Lady Tsunade
a piece of my mind!
Next episode, " The Three Villains
from the Maximum Security Prison"