Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
- Sumptuous meal!
I feel a little thrown off balance.
Let's regroup, everybody!
Go!
I'm itchy, Elder Brother.
Yeah, itchy...
Huh?!
My punches aren't having
any effect whatsoever.
Naruto...
This doesn't look good.
Again!
Huh?
I It itches, Elder Brother.
Yeah... feels like I'm getting a rash.
D Damn!
I'm not done yet!
Stop it, Naruto!
It's futile...
- You won't swagger like that for long!
This feels so good!
What's up with those guys anyway?
You're an idiot brat as always.
You have it hard, don't you?
Having to go on a mission
with that failure of a brat.
Don't you, Iruka?
Why, Mizuki?!
I'm asking you, please stop
this kind of foolishness!
Are you intending to betray
your comrades from the village again?
Comrades?
That's right!
Your comrades from the Leaf Village
with whom you shared
both pleasures and pain!
You can understand that,
can't you?
Comrades... huh?
As usual, you are naïve,
aren't you... Iruka?
What I believe in is power!
Don't think you can shackle me with
such vague bonds like that of comrades!
Mizuki...
I will soon get my hands
on the ultimate power!
Lord Orochimaru's power!
Orochimaru?!
Then I'll teach you a lesson!
About how meaningless it is...
that thing you and the other Leaf guys
describe as camaraderie or whatever!
Mizuki...
You were an excellent Shinobi despite
having committed that crime, you...
Don't talk so knowingly!
Damn! They're dodging all my attacks!
Iruka, if you insist so much,
why don't you show me?
What degree of feeling
you really have for your comrades...
I wonder whether you'll really
be able to stop me?
Come!
Wait!
Naruto! Forget about these guys!
Pursue Mizuki!
Damn...!
I'm gonna settle this later
without fail!
Elder Brother, that guy went off.
They all went off, didn't they?
Elder Brother, could this be
a game of hide and go seek?
Hide-and -go -seek! Hide-and -go -seek!
So does that mean we're "It"?
Those jerks!
Making us "It" without even deciding
by scissors paper rock!
- Let's go, Raijin!
- Okay!
A New Squad!
Two People and a Dog?!
Over here... Iruka.
Hurry, Naruto!
Don't be fooled this time!
Shut up! It's 100 years too soon
to be arguing with me!
I'm telling you,
if you dilly dally the situation's gonna
get really troublesome again!
What?!
Found you!
Good job, huh, Elder Brother!
Yeah!
I don't have time to be
dealing with these guys!
Elder Brother, hide and go seek is fun,
but aren't you getting hungry?
You're really something,
aren't you, Raijin?
Leave some for your Elder Brother!
Of course, I will!
Hey, you idiot brothers!
- Huh?
This is no time to be eating!
I'm telling you, it's foolhardy
to be fighting these guys!
I already know that!
Mizuki! Where are you?!
What's the matter... Iruka?
Weren't you gonna stop me?
Stop this foolishness, Mizuki!
Come on out, Mizuki!
Always be aware of
an attack from behind...
For a Shinobi,
isn't that a basic rule?
Nicely done, Iruka.
Pretty good!
Always read behind the surface
of your enemy's bluffs...
For a Shinobi isn't that a basic rule?
That's my line!
What's that?
A Smoke Bomb?
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
- Come on over! Catch us if you can!
Elder Brother, they're increasing!
They're increasing!
Raijin, this must be
super hide and go seek, don't you think?
Yeah. That's right!
A decoy strategy, huh?
You thought it through.
We can buy some time this way.
All right, now's our chance...
- Super, super hide and go seek!
There are,
there are two Old Lady Tsunades!
You're talking about
the idiotic strength, huh?
Haven't you come to
your senses yet?!
Shut up!
Why are you so obsessed with power!
Because that, if anything,
is everything!
Reconsider, Mizuki!
It isn't too late yet!
You are naive!
Don't you understand the situation?!
What's the matter?
Come on and attack, Iruka!
You're not my enemy!
You're my comrade from
the same village!
I told you, I'm tired of that kind of
song and dance!
And moreover...
you're my colleague!
You're a member of the same family
that inherited the same Will of Fire!
Will of Fire, huh?
Yes, that's right.
Therefore, please stop
the foolishness, Mizuki!
It irks me most when
you say things like that!
Mizuki!
Since we're old acquaintances
I was gonna kill you quickly.
But now I've decided against that.
You're gonna have some fun...
I'll give you a taste of how it feels
to be killed slowly by
your so called comrade!
Hey, Naruto... How long are you
planning to be like that?
It's just a matter of time till
those guys find you!
I found you!
What?! They found us!
All right! This is it!
Hide-and -go -seek!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Elder Brother,
super hide and go seek again?
I'm getting bored with this.
Shadow Clone again?!
As always,
you have no new tricks, huh!
Just leave it to me!
All right! Go!
- Okay!
- Go!
Wh What?!
What kind of game is this?
Wow, they're going so fast.
I see... Not bad.
I I feel sick... Elder Brother.
I'm woozy...
Now! Catch them!
Huh?!
You jerks...
What do you think you're doing?
The preparation's done!
Here it goes!
You fatso Herculean brothers!
Concentrate... I must concentrate...
Stop putting on airs!
A guy like you,
who's weaker than me!
Yeah! That's right, isn't it?!
You always excelled over
anything I did, didn't you... ?
I was always being helped by you,
wasn't I?
One year has passed already, hasn't it?
It's not so easy to laugh,
hiding your sadness.
Your teacher told me that
you are the center of the laughter.
I'm not sad at all!
It's an honor for Shinobi
to die during their missions!
My dad and mom...
are heroes who protected this village
from the Demon Fox!
And I am the child of those heroes.
That's why I'm not sad
even though I'm alone...
These tears are from the happiness...
Enough already.
I'm always aware that
you are feeling Ionely.
But you are not alone.
All of Leaf's Shinobi
have the "Will of Fire."
"Will of Fire?"
It means the will to protect the Leaf.
As long as you have
the Will of Fire,
you and people in this village
are all family.
Iruka, I wonder if you have that.
Yeah.
Huh?
Who's that over there?
Mizuki...
What are you doing there?
Well, I heard that Iruka
was depressed these days...
I was worried and came to look for him.
Everybody's... worried about you, Iruka.
Everybody's waiting over there.
Come on and play with us!
It's all right... Go on.
The Mizuki that I idolized was kind...
And he was a guy who was more
thoughtful of his friends than anyone else.
Yet...
Please remember! Mizuki!
You really are...
an idiot, aren't you?!
L Let go...
Here it goes...
S Stop please!
I I feel sick...
- Huh?
- Eh?
What?
Elder Brother, don't tell me that you...
Sorry, Raijin... I squashed...
our lunch!
What?!
Stay still, guys!
Now take this...!
- Give us back our lunch!
What?!
H-He's done it, huh...
It doesn't look like you understand me,
so let me explain.
The real reason I was kind to you...
Because it made me happy
more than anything
to see you in your misery!
Hey, Iruka!
We're gonna go play soccer right now.
Come join us, Iruka!
Sure! Okay!
I wonder if Iruka's okay
after all those things
that happened to him...
That's why we need to
try to cheer him up!
Why...only him...
Everybody makes a fuss about him
just because of his parents
getting killed by Nine Tail...
Serves you right...
Even Lord Hokage?!
Why...why is it?!
Who is it over there?
All right...
I'm gonna try to gain the favor
of Lord Hokage too...
What are you doing over there?
Well, I heard that Iruka has been
depressed recently so...
You're lying!
Treating a g uy who's weaker
than oneself with disdain
is the most pleasurable
feeling of all, Iruka.
You weren't that way in the past!
That's why I've been telling you...
you're naïve!
That kind of naiveté leads to fatal mistakes
on the battleground.
On the battleground, it's all about
how many enemies you can kill!
If you throw a Kunai blindly
in a bamboo grove,
all that will happen is that it'll bounce off
and its path will be errant.
If you're gonna take aim...
make it straight!
Don't think I'm gonna get fooled twice
with the same bait!
Damn... I'm at a disadvantage if
we fight in a place like this!
Mizuki...
You...
Mizuki!
I told you, it's useless...
If the path is going to be errant,
then one just needs to calculate
the path of the Kunai when throwing it!
So you've finally gotten serious, huh?
Follow me!
Where is this?
Looks like you're finally conscious.
You jerk...
You ruined our meal...
Don't even think
we're gonna let you leave here alive!
I'm going for his stomach!
I'm going for his head!
- One, two...
- Three!
Huh?
Huh?!
Wh What is going on?
Gimme a break,
what are you doing?!
Wh Who's that?
It's too much of a drag
to tell you my name, however...!
The most powerful support squad
assigned to this mission!
The most powerful trio from
the Village Hidden in the Leaves!
We're Ino Shika Cho!
Crappy news pass us by
And you become speechless
My voice is way too soft
So you don't answer
You're crying Crying alone
What can I do? I'm crying too
"Let my lonely scream ring out
through the night"
I'll thrash this confused era
with my speed Yeah
And I'll thrash this confused night
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar
and my speed Yeah
This sinking world and its evil bastards,
I'll kick their butt Yeah
What's with these guys?!
They have super ridiculous strength!
To think they can resist
Shadow Possession Jutsu
to this extent on sheer power!
If Shikamaru's Jutsu gets broken now,
we'll be in a hairy spot!
Our only choice is to
settle this right away.
Are you guys ready?
- Yeah!
Then let's go!
This is our trump card!
Next episode,
"A New Formation: Ino-Shika-Cho!"