Connecting old words
that have been used up
I just want to convey
my simple thoughts
That day's faint wind blows away
at the castle ruins of yesterday
I'll laugh with you
and live for the moment
Still that incident
will continue to trouble you, right?
That's why it must be good bye
Leaving nothing behind,
let us share what is left
In time, we'll realize
that it was everything
And sadness will touch our cheeks,
creating a river of tears
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex
and melting away
Okay! Drink! Sing!
Let's have fun!
Good grief... This is too much for...
a pre celebration.
Did you take care of the business?
Yes...
More importantly,
the rain's starting to let up.
Shouldn't you quickly put an end
to this farce of a race?
Fine.
Guess I'll go for a run!
A-Above here, huh?
Yeah...
It's a quite a long staircase,
believe it.
They're also called
the Stone Steps that Tear Hearts Apart.
Heh, cool!
Let's go at a sprint!
Hey, he's kidding, right?
What kind of stamina does he have?
Boss.
It seems Idate is heading this way!
He hasn't run away,
just like you said, Boss.
Of course...
I saw potential in him.
Now, it's just a little more!
Run Idate!
A Fierce Battle of Rolling Thunder
Hey... you!
Huh?
Let me tell you...
It's not like I trust you
or anything yet, okay?
Yeah, yeah whatever.
It doesn't really matter to me,
believe it.
There's a person
who still trusts you, right?!
During the Chunin Exam...
Huh?
You said that a tenth problem
appeared, right?
Yeah. It was a weird problem to determine
whether you'd take the problem or not.
Three years ago...
I got a similar problem...
Okay, now I'm going to
give the tenth problem.
The tenth problem...
What kind of problem is
Big Brother going to give?!
The tenth problem is a battle
with the Three-Man Squad
you were teamed up with.
The three of you will compete against
each other this exercise.
And among you...
one of you will be failed!
And the one who is failed
will remain a Genin for life
and we will never again
let them take the Chunin Exam!
N-No way...
Then for what purpose
were we together until now?
I make the rules here.
Back-talk is not allowed at all!
If you want to withdraw,
you should do so.
Withdrawing here and
waiting half a year is also a way.
If one person among
the three withdraws,
of course all three members
will be disqualified.
But you will be allowed
to take the Chunin Exam
one more time, in half a year.
So, what will you do?
One comrade will be dropped.
I have the confidence to pass.
But, one of them will remain
a Genin for life.
It's a choice between
comrades and your life.
If you're going to quit,
now's the time.
Is there nobody else
who's going to withdraw?
We're good, then.
Okay, to everyone who
has remained here...
I render you disqualified!
Wh-Why...?
H-Hold on a minute!
I prepared myself and remained here!
Such preparedness is below contempt!
Scums like you don't have
the qualifications to become Chunin!
That's all!
I see...
What kind of a test was it
for you guys?
I forgot...
I mean, it was explained to me,
but I didn't really get it.
Trusting in my big brother's words,
I remained in the classroom.
And yet I was failed!
No way could I take that.
I questioned my big brother.
Big Brother!
What's up with that test?!
A Shinobi reads the double bluff.
You should've understood
that was the test.
Even so, I can't accept that!
No matter how dangerous,
isn't it necessary to have
the courage to plunge into any mission?!
Idate.
Can you really not accept it?
Of course not, such a...
You... quit as a Ninja.
If you're telling me to quit,
then I will.
But tell me why I'm no good!
That's something you should
realize yourself,
with your own power.
To this day... I don't understand
the answer to that.
So after that,
you were deceived by Aoi, huh?
Yeah, that's right.
We made it... to the top!
I'm going by myself from here.
You rest!
Huh?! You still saying stuff like that?!
I can't be asking you guys
to help any more.
There's no point if I don't win by myself,
on my own strength!
Oh... hey! Idate!
I can make it! It seems
Sakura's special medicine has worked!
Blast!
This doesn't hurt!
I'm back in the game...
from here!
If we cross this suspension bridge,
it's Ouzu Island, huh?
We should hurry.
It seems Idate has made it
to the Modoroki Shrine.
What?!
It seems we underestimated
the Leaf Genin a bit...
You jerk!
You didn't finish them?!
Now's not the time to be talking
about stuff like that.
Please cross the bridge quickly!
Useless Ninja!
Hey! I'm only helping you
because it's the job.
I'll waste you if you keep
talking smart to me.
I-I'm sorry...
If you've understood,
then get a move on!
Y-Yes!
There he is! That Fukusuke jerk!
This is quite something
I never thought
you'd make it this far.
That's the...
Blade of the Thunder God!
Stop!
Stop kicking a dead horse.
Nobody is a match for
the legendary Blade of the Thunder God,
said to have been used
by the Second Hokage.
You should know this well.
After all, you're the man
who stole this for me.
Blast...
Mud balls, huh?
It's just like a kid's fight.
Sorry, I didn't have
any Kunai Knives.
Naruto...
But you won't be able to dodge
the next ball just with that.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
He's concentrating
the Chakra in his palm.
Here I come!
Once more!
I don't know what
you intend to do, but...
Ninja Art: Senbon Rainstorm!
Too bad.
This Blade of the Thunder God
cuts through anything
Even Chakra itself is no exception.
Naruto!
I have to make doubly sure
so that nothing troublesome
will happen again.
I'm your opponent!
Keep your hands off Idate!
Humph, are you still
saying such things?
Saving each other, protecting each other,
trusting each other.
It ticks me off!
The weak can't survive
if they don't support each other.
So they trust people easily
and are betrayed.
Weaklings like you guys
should just run about and away.
Right, Idate?
It was like that also
when you stole
this Blade of the Thunder God, right?
I can see it.
That's the Village Hidden in the Rain.
Aoi Sensei?!
Aoi Sensei!
Idate...
B-Big Brother...
You idiot!
Go back to the village immediately
and surrender yourself!
You?!
Do you know what
you have done?
What?!
Strict as always, eh?
And he's your cute little brother.
But it's truly perfect that
you've shown up here.
Aoi Sensei...
This forbidden Jutsu scroll
can't be deciphered
unless you're Jonin class.
I'll have the brothers
betray the Leaf Village together.
Ibiki, please decipher it already.
I refuse.
So are you choosing death,
together with Idate?
Such as he is,
he's also a Shinobi.
He's not afraid of death.
It doesn't seem so.
This face is one taut with fear.
I'm quitting as a Ninja!
So please don't kill me!
Please decipher it.
You don't want to see
your cute little brother killed
before your eyes, do you?
Little brother, you say?
That fool?
Big Brother...
Such a threat means nothing to me.
Hey, Ibiki, is the Village Hidden
in the Leaves that important?
Even if you protect it at
the risk of your own life,
you're nothing but a pawn!
So that's why
you became a traitor?
You're a pathetic man!
You punk!
Idate!
You, run away!
What about you, Big Brother?
I'll go, after I clean up
the mess here!
I don't think so!
Big Brother!
Go, quickly!
But Big Brother...!
Go! Having you stay is a burden!
I won't let you!
Go!
So appalling...
that he'd risk
his life for such an idiotic guy.
All you could do after that
was run.
You could've returned
to the village and called for help.
But you didn't do that.
Thinking Ibiki was dead
was no excuse!
The fact is, he was alive...
In that regard,
Ibiki was admirable.
Not only did he completely endure
repeated interrogation,
but he also retrieved
the Forbidden Jutsu scroll...
without having confessed to anything
And to think that he did
all this
for his good for nothing little brother.
You betrayed your village,
abandoned your older brother,
and came to think of only yourself.
Even Ibiki who is blood-related
and risked his life to save you,
you didn't trust him!
Afraid of being accused,
you didn't trust the Village Hidden
in the Leaves, your birthplace...
You trust nobody.
You're not trusted by anyone.
For me, there is no pupil
as excellent as you.
As a reward,
I'll let you die in one instant.
Idate!
Sasuke... Sakura!
Rest, Naruto!
I'll beat this guy!
Don't be acting cool, believe it.
You can't beat me, no matter
how many people show up.
Me, Aoi Rokusho,
the Rain Jonin who possesses
the Blade of the Thunder God.
Is that so?
Interesting.
The Blade of the Thunder God
and my Chidori!
Let's test which is better!
The rumors were true.
The survivor of the village's honorable
Uchiha Clan...
is just a good for nothing kid...
Sasuke!
Run, Sakura!
He'll show no mercy,
no matter who the person is.
Everyone will be killed!
No way!
Huh?!
We'll protect you,
no matter what.
We promised that, didn't we?!
Trust us!
Now all that's left is
the wounded rabbit
and the excellent pupil, huh?
You two together,
go to the next world.
Take it back!
What're you talking about?
What you said...
earlier!
Don't mess...
with the Uchiha...
with me!
Why you!
Sasuke!
Sasuke! Get up!
How very cold the bottom
of the ocean must be.
Stop!
Idate!
Sakura!
Once in a long while, once in a while
The remnants of a person
broken by dreams
Look like a mountain
Clinging to the Divine,
clinging to Buddha
The remnants of a person crying
Look like a mountain
Rendezvous with a happy dance circle
This is my victory pose, round and around
(round around)
Shake shake shake
Let's look
With a bye bye rhythm that never ends
Look like a mountain
What the heck should we do?
That sword of the Second Hokage
won't budge an inch
even with Sasuke's Chidori
or my Rasengan!
But I can't lose this battle.
I won't run away, no matter what!
If my techniques aren't going to work,
I'll just have to keep trying!
Next time: "The Last Leg:
A Final Act of Desperation"