Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
What do you mean by
monitoring Akamaru?
You know about the incident
where someone from outside
infiltrated the village, right?
Yeah, I know about that.
But I heard that Kiba and the others
resolved that incident without any trouble.
That's right.
Damn! That Kiba!
I want a mission where
I totally kick an enemy's butt.
To be exact, that's wrong.
What?
Before Kiba and the others
had the intruder in custody...
he swallowed a pellet
and killed himself.
What? Suicide...?
In the investigation that followed,
it was revealed that the enemy
was a Shinobi
from another land that uses
a unique tactic.
Perhaps he took his own life
in order to seal that power.
What's the "unique" tactic?
Something you would call
a biological weapon.
Biological weapon?
It's a particular pathogen...
a terrible weapon where someone
infected will gradually lose oneself
and have their body taken over.
But how is that connected
with monitoring Akamaru?
Could it be that Akamaru was...?!
There's a possibility he's infected.
He still doesn't look so well.
Y Yeah...
Since Akamaru's not
in his best condition,
I'm skipping training today as well.
Okay...
Oh!
Wh What're you doing, Shino?!
Shino, do something quick!
Shino!
The insects suddenly
stopped listening to me.
Jeez, give me a break.
I'm sorry.
We'll head back early
for the time being. See ya.
I hope... Akamaru gets better soon.
Shino?
It's the first time the insects
have attacked a comrade...
What is it, Akamaru?
Oh, shoot! I've been spotted!
What're you doing, Naruto?
Wh What, you ask?
I'm developing a new Jutsu,
believe it!
So as for me, I'm busy and...
Kiba's Long Day
Is there no mistake, Sis?
I'd say the possibility
at this point is around fifty fifty.
I still haven't been able to identify it,
but these are the lab results of
the blood drawn from Akamaru...
But! It could be some kind of mistake!
Do you think I, a veterinarian,
would make such a mistake?
Yeah... You're right.
What is it, Akamaru?!
Let go! Let go!
Akamaru, it's Naruto. It's okay to let go.
Hey, Akamaru!
Akamaru!
What did you do that for Akamaru?
I mean, what're you doing
in the front yard of my house?
Huh? Well, that's...
Anyway, come in.
For the time being, I have to fulfill
my responsibility as the owner.
What?
What?!
Geez! Biting a comrade
of the same village can't be allowed!
Are you training him properly, Kiba?!
All right.
It's finished! Perfect if
I do say so myself!
Sis! That looks just like
a surgical scar!
What? Really?
I thought it turned out well, though...
Sorry, Naruto.
Have Sakura or someone
patch them up for you!
Hm? Right...
See ya.
Right.
See you later too, Miss Hana!
Akamaru...
I'm telling you,
there's nothing else other than
my pants getting all torn up.
Shino's insects attacked Akamaru...
He even attacked Naruto, whom
he should know very well.
There's trouble, Lady Tsunade!
It seems they were attacked
by someone
in the middle of night training.
Looks like they launched
a sneak attack with quite a few men.
No, it seems there was just one culprit.
What?! All of this by one person?!
To be precise, that's not correct.
It's one animal.
There's no doubt.
There's trouble, Kiba!
You're talking about the incident
where Shinobi were attacked during
night training last night, right...?
It It can't be!
It seems it's as you said, Sis...
I can smell blood from Akamaru.
That's Kiba Inuzuka's
Ninja Hound Akamaru, correct?
You jerks.
What do you want with Akamaru?!
A warrant...?
Kiba...!
Yes, there's no mistake.
Kiba Inuzuka, by order of the Hokage,
the Ninja Hound Akamaru is to be kept
under the supervision
of the Anbu Black Ops.
- Damn it!
- Kiba!
We should obey
the Lady Hokage's order.
Damn it!
Akamaru...
Here.
Thanks, Sis.
This contains medicine that I prepared,
so give it to the vet over there.
Right. I'm off, then.
Naruto?
What's the idea of Akamaru
being detained?!
Akamaru is the culprit from
last night's incident.
We have sufficient proof as well.
At this point, it's an unavoidable measure.
The Medical Team is now desperately
looking for a way to save Akamaru.
Don't worry too much.
Lf... that doesn't work either,
what'll happen to Akamaru?
At that time...
there'll be nothing left to do
but to put Akamaru down!
Hidden Leaf Veterinary Hospital
You don't need to worry.
The Medical Corps will figure
something out soon.
Right...
Take care on your way home.
Right.
Akamaru...
I won't hand you over to anyone.
It seems Kiba Inuzuka
has taken Akamaru and fled.
Lady Tsunade, what shall we do?
In preparation for the worst,
have the Special Pursuit Corps
stand by here!
The Special Pursuit Corps...
C Could it be that you're really
going to kill Akamaru... Grandma?
Grandma Tsunade!
It's hard for me, too.
Damn it!
Did you find them?!
No!
Kiba!
He's rapidly getting worse.
Akamaru!
Where are they?
They should be around here.
I swore to protect him,
no matter what!
I swore never I'd never let him go through
that experience ever again...!
The Special Pursuit Corps
has assembled.
Show the team in.
Kiba!
Where are you?!
I guess I was able to hide
my tracks somewhat...
This is a serum for Akamaru
that the Medical Corps whipped up.
I can't guarantee the level of effect.
There's maybe a fifty percent chance
of survival.
There's also a risk of side effects
that would cause Akamaru
to go even more berserk.
In the event that happens...
It's an unavoidable measure,
but Akamaru must...
Reporting!
The Akamaru Pursuit Corps has
lost the trail of Kiba and Akamaru.
Lady Tsunade.
That way?!
Akamaru...
Kiba!
Wh What's that?
It's Akamaru...
But...
I won't hand over Akamaru to anyone!
What're you doing?!
Have you come to kill Akamaru?!
No! I just came out of concern!
You lie! The Lady Hokage said it,
didn't she?!
There'll be nothing else to do
but to kill Akamaru.
You came to dispose of Akamaru, right?!
I won't hand over Akamaru
to anyone!
This isn't the time
to be doing that!
Something called the Special Pursuit Corps
or whatever is coming after Akamaru!
What?!
The Pursuit Corps should
be here soon.
Akamaru will really be
in trouble if that happens!
You and I have to do
something before that!
This isn't the time to be fighting!
Shut up!
Why don't you get it, Kiba?!
All right! I've sighted Akamaru!
Kiba, Naruto! You guys step back!
C Could it be... the Pursuit Corps is...
Sis!
You gotta be... joking, right?
What're you going to do
to Akamaru with that?
This is medicine I received
from the Hokage.
I'm going to inject it into Akamaru.
Then Akamaru will be saved?!
The probability is fifty fifty.
If it fails and side effects are produced,
Akamaru's symptoms will
get even worse.
All we can do now is take
a chance on this.
If the worst happens and it fails...
You understand, right, Kiba?
Damn it...
Even if it's only fifty percent,
there's a possibility that Akamaru
will be saved.
We've gotta do this!
I'll also help out, miss!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Kiba, what about you?!
If you're not going to do anything,
you're in the way, so beat it!
Let's go, Kiba.
Just leave that coward be.
You're ready, right?
Let's go, Naruto!
We'll save you now, Akamaru!
Aim for the legs!
Immobilize Akamaru!
Right!
Since it's come to this,
I have no choice.
I must terminate Akamaru.
Stop!
I said stop... Akamaru.
Kiba!
Kiba?
Akamaru...
Have you forgotten... my scent?
We were always together from
when we were little, weren't we?
Akamaru...
Why... why... did you become like this?
Please remember... Akamaru!
Kiba!
I'm sorry, Akamaru...
I put you through nothing but
painful experiences.
I'm sorry, Akamaru...
I couldn't protect you...
I'm sorry... Akamaru...
I'm a terrible master.
But...
I'II... always be with you.
Kiba...
Kiba!
It really would've been touch and go
if the Medical Corps had been
even a little late in arriving.
Without a doubt,
he would've lost his life if Akamaru's attack
had hit Kiba's vital spot...
Really, it could have been
much worse.
That's wrong...
Huh? Kiba?!
When he came at me with
his final attack,
Akamaru just barely missed
my vital spots.
He drained all his remaining strength
in order to desperately control himself.
Akamaru was battling desperately
with himself.
That's admirable, Akamaru!
Thanks...
Akamaru.
Yesterday's Call Sign,
was all from my cell phone.
In a strange park,
I play the Fuzz Guitar without enthusiasm.
Yellow Moon.
Even now, counting to three,
I open my eyes
Shadow Moon I am still dreaming.
Look at my eyes, look at my eyes,
as we face one another's back
Look at my eyes, when can we meet?
EveryDay EveryNight
With every word I can think of
Right away, my messy feelings as is,
A magical chord change, in a restless city
A daily JAZZ Guitar played
in a soft minor key
In this world, there remain mysteries
yet unsolved.
We came to the Hidden Leaf Village
in search of mystery
and encountered a succession
of hair raising terror.
However, we charge forward
without being daunted
by the forest that bares its fangs.
And then at last...!
We witness with our own eyes,
the creature of the legend handed down
from generation to generation.
Next time:
"A Legend from the Hidden Leaf:
The Onbaa!"