Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
It looks like
the preparations are complete.
So this is the Land of Greens
you were talking about, brother?
Well, it's a small land,
but it could be a good stepping stone
for getting ahead in the world.
We've already bought off
half of the public officials.
This land will be overturned
on our signal.
As of today,
we're the feudal lords of this land.
Feudal lords, huh?
That has a nice ring to it.
Open for Business!
The Leaf Moving Service
This is a problem...
I thought about testing out
various combinations, but it backfired.
With these remaining members,
there's nobody who can take the lead...
But it's merchant protection this time,
so no matter who goes,
there probably isn't much to worry about.
Mission difficulty isn't the issue.
It's a commission from
the Land of Greens.
I wanted to send them
a respectable team.
The lord of the castle there
was good to me in the old days!
True indeed...
He generously assumed the debts
for the bundle you blew on gambling.
It's small,
but it's a nice and easygoing land.
There was an adorable princess,
and two boy Ninja looked after her...
At that time,
they both said they'd marry me...
I wonder if they still feel that way...
I don't think so.
I bet they've all gotten big...
We'll be at the border soon.
This is our last look at this scenery
for a while.
All right!
A mission, a mission!
Wait up, Naruto!
Everyone else was off on missions,
but I've been doing nothing but
odd jobs in the village!
I was sick of hearing stories
about everyone's adventures.
Still,
we're guarding merchants this time.
It's probably not something
to brag about.
Then I should exaggerate
the story a bit
and say that I took out
about a thousand bandits, right?
That's just lying...
Oh! There they are.
That's them!
Yahoo!
Who're you?
You guys are merchants
from the Land of Greens, right?
That's right.
We've come from
the Village Hidden in Leaves
to protect you guys.
Believe it.
The Village Hidden in Leaves?
See...?
This, this.
We were told to protect you
from mountain bandits...
It's for certain.
I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
And this is Hinata.
I'm Choji Akimichi.
Um, we received one more item
from the Hokage
to identify ourselves with.
Hey, Momiji.
Give it back.
Oh, it's true.
These people are from
the Village of the Hidden Leaf.
See...?
The Leaf Moving Service
Wh What's that?
Old lady Tsunade...
she's done it this time!
I see.
I'm Kikusuke.
This is Yurinoshin.
He's Shun.
I'm Momiji!
We'll be counting on you movers!
You sure eat a lot.
That's why you're so f...
Fa?!
...full figured.
For you.
I love people with great strength.
Something like this is a cinch.
See? Watch.
R oll-roll-roll-roll-roll-roll-roll...
Somebody help me!
That Choji, getting all carried away.
Move faster, mover.
We're rapidly falling behind.
We're not movers, I'm telling you.
Why don't you help out
before complaining?!
No, it's fine.
Our cousin Shun is in poor health.
You don't need to worry,
Kikusuke, Yurinoshin.
I had no intention of
listening to anything
this good for nothing has had to say
from the start.
Who's a good for nothing?!
Just you watch!
Honestly,
it's because you push yourself too far...
I'm sorry...
Shun's being unreasonable.
Water!
Oh.
Mine's empty, too.
Then there's some fresh drawn water.
Here!
Wow,
how'd you find water in a place like this?
My grandma taught me.
Your grandma?
It's this...
You can tell with this.
What?!
With those?
It's called dousing.
If you concentrate
on the item you're looking for...
these rods will react to that item
and will inform you when you're near it.
It's knowledge passed on
from our predecessors.
When I get back to the village,
maybe I'll try to find money
that people dropped with that.
Tasty!
It doesn't compare to the water
in the Land of Greens, but it's good water.
Come to think of it,
what kind of place is the Land of Greens?
The Land of Greens is...
a small land deep in the mountains.
Everyone in the land loves nature
and is warm -hearted.
It was indeed Shangri La...
Was...?
Oh, it's nothing...
But, you know, if it's such a great place,
why do you need protection?
It's targeted because
the people take peace for granted!
What do you mean by that?
Stuff like loving nature
and being warm hearted sounds nice.
But the bottom line is that the people
in the Land of Greens are all softhearted.
We live in a troubled time now.
Something like believing in people
is ridiculous.
Hey, the Land of Greens
is not something to speak ill of like that.
The lord of the castle there was kind
even to us merchants passing through.
To think he'd take up that kind of attitude
with an old lady...
He's kind of disagreeable.
He's your cousin, right?
Do something about him.
R-R ight.
He's probably a bit touchy
from the bad things that have happened.
I'm sorry...
Oh, i it's okay...
Hey, that's dangerous.
It's dangerous
to wander around alone.
Brother Choji, look at that...
Naruto!
What is it?
That.
Wh What is that?
That's in the direction of
the Land of Greens, right?!
I'm going to go check it out...
You take the others and go on ahead.
I'll be right back.
Listen.
What we saw here is a secret.
We don't want everyone to get worried.
Yeah.
Got it.
Huh? Where's Naruto?
Th The bathroom...
I'll give this to you
if you tell me what you saw earlier.
Black smoke...
was rising.
Black smoke?!
From where?
The direction of the Land of Greens.
Lord Shun...
It's finally...
I should be at the Land of Greens
border pretty soon.
Wh What was that...?
There was no presence at all.
Who're you guys!
Who're you guys?
That headband. You're with
the Hidden Leaf Village, right?
So what if I am?
Why are you targeting me?
I have no intention
of fighting you guys.
It seems the ones we are looking for
are heading this direction, you see.
Those who prowl around here will die.
Did we do it?
The Substitution Jutsu?!
The real one is over here!
These guys are pretty good.
Two left.
One of them is the real one!
What?!
Too bad!
Those two are also clones.
I'm going to turn back for now...
Choji! Hinata!
How'd it go, Naruto?
Actually, there's trouble...
Guys! Let's take a break here
for the time being!
Pursuers from the Land of Greens?
They said that...
The ones they were looking for
were headed in this direction.
But why would Ninja
be after this group?
These people are just merchants,
aren't they?
And they're not even people
from the Land of Greens to begin with...
Now that you mention it,
that's right.
But what will we do?
We're going to engage them if they come,
of course.
That might be impossible...
We have elderly people
and children with us.
You're right...
I know.
It could be that
they're not chasing after us!
What do you mean by that?
Basically, we're moving
in the same direction as their true target
and we could just be
in their battle ground... or something.
I see.
That means if we clear the path,
they'll let us go right by.
Alright.
Listen up, guys!
Some kind of troublesome guys
are heading this way.
Troublesome guys?
Naruto, I think everyone will feel anxious
if you say it like that.
I I see...
But you don't need to worry.
They're probably not after us...
It'll kind of be the long way around,
but we'll make it through
if we take a little side turn up ahead.
Does this feudal lord really have this little?
He's a feudal lord
who's a prestigious ruler of virtue.
So he would never line his pockets.
But we'll squeeze out a big pile
from now on.
More importantly, has
the young girl in question been found?
Nope...
But the two who were tracking her
got attacked.
We know the direction she fled in.
That young girl just would not be good.
If they get away, they may return
with forces from other lands.
If the sun were a little stronger,
I could burned down a whole mountain
with my Jutsu...
Then I'll go...
Lord Renga, I gathered all collaborators
in the hall as you ordered...
Oh, good work.
Without your guys' help, we couldn't have
brought down the castle this easily...
Then brother,
shall we go for the hall greeting?
Okay... I'll take care of things here.
So, about the thing you promised...
Oh, that's right.
Take as much there as you like.
R eally?
Honestly. It's so easy to deceive
softhearted people...
It really is exactly so.
Our lord believed in us
until the very end...
Come on.
If you stuff that much in there,
the ferry on death's river will sink.
I make it a habit not to believe in people.
Especially people
who have betrayed someone once...
Y You're joking, Lord Renga...
It's no joke.
C Could it be that you had me
gather the collaborators in the coup to...
You're also softhearted!
That should do it.
Yurinojou, it seems they're after us.
Yes.
I leave Lady Haruna to you.
What are you going to do?
If we wait here for their attack,
there will be too many to defend.
Since it's come to this,
I'll slow them down.
But according to the information,
they are three Janin
who use unknown Jutsu.
I know.
But my Jutsu will not be defeated
by the likes of them.
Very well.
Go, Kikunojou.
Yes, Lady Haruna.
Naruto.
I set a trap for the time being.
Jeez, Hinata.
You're such a worrywart.
You don't need to go that far.
Huh? Yurinoshin,
where's Kikusuke?
You're right.
Since when...?
Oh, he had some other business
and went on ahead...
Say what? Taking liberties like that
is really a problem...
Oh, I see.
So that's it, huh?
What is it?
Even Kikusuke makes sure
to go to the bathroom.
Naruto!
Lady Haruna, I shall protect you
with my life!
There!
Who're you...?!
I'm Ruiga.
To think you'd
just come right on out nonchalantly.
Then she must in that group, right?
If it's one against one,
I won't lose to a hired Ninja like you!
Can you do it?
Have a taste of
the Land of Greens' Flower Ninja Art!
Eat this! Flower Shuriken!
Flying Flowers: Falling Foliage!
Too easy...
I don't know about that!
Flower Ninja Art: Release!
Myriad of Flowers!
Ninja Art: Mirror Flower Water Moon!
Flowers made of Letter Bombs, huh?
Futile, futile!
And Genjutsu next, huh?
This is the finishing blow.
Flower Ninja Art: Bloom!
Myriad of Flowers!
Too bad.
The Ninjutsu of a Flower Ninja
can't beat me.
Now it's my turn!
Eat this.
Water Style: Liquid Memory!
Yesterday's Call Sign,
was all from my cell phone.
In a strange park,
I play the Fuzz Guitar without enthusiasm.
Yellow Moon.
Even now, counting to three,
I open my eyes
Shadow Moon I am still dreaming.
Look at my eyes, look at my eyes,
as we face one another's back
Look at my eyes, when can we meet?
EveryDay EveryNight
With every word I can think of
Right away, my messy feelings as is,
A magical chord change, in a restless city
A daily JAZZ Guitar played
in a soft minor key
A running ramen strategy, huh?
In other words, we split up
in order to avoid annihilation, right?
With this,
the protection burden will decrease.
But won't the soup spill if it runs?
This is an example.
It'd still be trouble
even if it's just an example, believe it.
Then, let's make it
the running-ramen -with -a -lid strategy.
If you say so, Naruto.
I mean, do you really understand
the strategy, Naruto?
Next time:
"Mystery of the Targeted Merchants."